"Remaining time until Prime
Minister Fujiwara's public execution"
Why is there no final
piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence
facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
"Episode 11 '50,000 Hostages'"
There has been another blast.
This one was in Kinshicho.
- Just as the warning told,
- Kanda, any word from Ogami?
- explosions are starting
all over the country.
- Kanda, any word from Ogami?
Nothing yet.
Did you find Hitomi?
Nope. Eden's information was no help.
At present, there have been
multiple bombings all over Japan.
Those who are outside,
please avoid areas of heavy traffic,
and return home quickly.
Just how many of them did he plant?!
If we could at least
find out where the bombs are,
we could send the bomb
disposal squad out to them.
Oh, no! There's a freaking
huge number of bombs planted!
Even if you know where they are,
they're in 1500 locations.
It would be impossible to
dispose of them all in one hour.
That's right. The people
have no choice but to wait in terror
for their destruction to come.
As well as yearn for the
justice of the Code: Breakers.
Boss! There was a blast
at the Kidake-gumi's building!
The Kisugi-gumi is safe!
Haven't you gotten through to
Sakura's cell phone yet?
I've been calling her again and
again, but nothing yet.
Your daughter's cell phone
GPS data just came in!
Sky Tower?
1 new message arrived
"From: Adam's Friend"
"Subj:  'Bomb Locations'"
Bomb locations?
But Sakura is...
Daisuke, contact all the
bosses across the country! Hurry!
"From: Adam's Friend"
"Subj: 'Bomb Locations'"
Another one?
Who is sending these?
Track down the signal source!
That's right,
both the maps, and the images!
Tokyo Tower, the Tsutenkaku Tower,
the Sapporo TVTower, Sky Tower...
check them all out! It's a facility
that can transmit a signal to a wide area.
And don't overlook
any relay stations, either!
Isn't this from Sky Tower?
What?!
I've been up there, for an inspection.
The roof had a place
like this, no doubt about it!
He's what?!
Toki, it's possible that the
Prime Minister is at Sky Tower!
Really?
They're ordering us to head
there to rescue him immediately.
"From: Adam's Friend"
"Subj: Prime Minister at Sky Tower"
I don't know who this is,
but it appears he's for real.
Hitomi and that Heike jerk
are there for sure, too.
The great Toki is gonna kick their asses!
Kanda, contact Ogami, too.
Right.
For crying out loud, Ogami would
go running off on his own.
Yuki, what's the matter?
Number four, you go on ahead.
I'm gonna do something about these bombs.
What?!
But!
I know. There's a whole mess of them,
and there may not be time
to disable them all individually.
But I can't leave them alone.
If I do, that many more people will get hurt.
Can you handle it, "Number three"?
Don't go selling "the Great Yuki's"
sound special ability short.
Now then...
Let's get this show on the road!
Yes, indeed...
What are you up to?
Ah, so that's it.
You're checking to make sure
there are no intruders.
That's most helpful, Heike.
It is an honor to be of service, Ace.
This sure brings me back, huh?
Being here with you reminds
me of when we fought side by side,
together as Code: Breakers.
Yes, it does.
Heike...
What is it?
Thank you.
Ogami...
I will take care of him.
No, there's no need for that.
You mean you're
taking him yourself, Ace?
Yeah. The last time, Ogami
was just coming out of being Lost.
I want to see Ogami's total power.
Still the same old Ace, huh?
Well then, I will secure the perimeter,
to make sure no one
interferes with your fight, Ace.
Ogami!
Miss Sakurakoji, are you all right?
How is it that you knew where we were, Ogami?
I wandered around
here and there, last night.
I even went to the riverbed.
I searched all of the places
where we'd spent time together,
one after another. To think
that you'd be here, though...
You did say that once
this place was completed,
a lot of people would come here,
with their families, and girlfriends.
But there's no one here.
Yeah. Ironic, isn't it?
I wanted to come here
under peaceful circumstances.
Hitomi, you have to stop the bombs!
Aren't you going to
contact Toki and the others?
It got ruined when
I was fighting Heike.
In that case, I can
speak to you for a while,
without anyone interrupting us.
Tell me how to stop the blasts.
There's no way killing people is okay,
even if it is to protect
those with special abilities.
Hitomi, what you are doing is wrong.
You almost sound like
a champion of justice, Ogami.
No, not justice. I am an evil,
who has killed many people.
I'm not telling you how to stop the blasts.
In that case, I will defeat you,
and force it out of you.
An eye for an eye; a tooth for a tooth;
evil for evil!
No you won't.
Ogami!
Ogami, what are you?
Ho...
So that's it.
You take in the electricity with
the katana, avoiding the shocks, huh?
Then, with the conductive
properties of your flames,
you release the electricity into the floor.
That's smart thinking, Ogami.
But you won't be able to beat me like that.
When you're attacked from
multiple directions at once,
your flames can't redirect all of it.
Ah! Another one!
Ogami!
Damn, if it weren't for this rope...
Puppy, chew through the ropes!
Hang in there, Puppy!
Well done!
O-Oh, no!
Puppy!
If that's the way it's going to be...
Ogami!
You're hanging in there, huh?
You're not, by any chance,
expecting me to go Lost, are you?
I'm not going Lost.
In fact, you're more
likely to go Lost before me.
Or you could be burnt up
by my electric shocks before that.
Ogami!
So, if you don't want to
get killed, give yourself up.
If you don't, you will end up dead.
I'm not giving up!
Why are you fighting so hard?
Swearing your allegiance to
the Code: Breakers...
...to the Prime Minister...
On that day...
...why did you try to
assassinate the Prime Minister?
Oh, so that's how the
story is being sold, is it?
W-What?
I went there to discuss things with him.
But I was rejected by the Prime Minister.
Then I ended up being pursued.
When he saw that I wouldn't back down...
...I was suddenly set upon, by some agents.
It's a shame that
I had to kill the agents
in the process of escaping.
Then, word that you
attacked the Prime Minister...
It's false information, sent out by Eden.
They made me out to be the villain,
and expelled me from the Code: Breakers.
Why?
Because my demand was something
they absolutely could not accept.
The Code: Breakers
live as people within society.
This means that the
existence of Code: Breakers
becomes known to the rest of the world.
Once that happens,
the world might become panicked.
Eden was afraid of that happening.
I ended up as someone who
was being pursued.
For me to change Eden now,
all I can do is apply
pressure from the outside.
But even so, for you
to do it by these means...
It is an awful thing, to be sure.
But there is no other way.
Besides...
I'm not doing this only out of
consideration for Code: Breakers.
Coming through.
We'll be taking the
children with special abilities.
The country has been
isolating those with special abilities,
and using them as research subjects.
Those who have high capabilities
were recruited as Code: Breakers,
but that just meant that
they were the state's dogs,
who carried out their killing for them.
As long as they are
overseen by the government,
those who have special
abilities have no freedom.
It's not just Code: Breakers
like you, Ogami, or Toki,
that I want to save,
but everyone who will ever be born
who possesses a special ability.
I realize that you are thinking
about those with special abilities.
If children like Chisa are
going to meet a fate like she did,
then I feel the same way
about wanting to make the world
such that they can live here happily.
But this isn't right!
It isn't right!
It isn't right to do this!
"Emergency Alert"
"...over 60 casualties. 6 explosions across Tokyo,
with over 200 fatalities. 3 explosions in Kanagawa..."
This is the only method
I have remaining to me.
After the state has walked all over us,
my grief over those who have
died is something you can't understand.
Hitomi, you are correct.
Perhaps I cannot understand it.
But even so, how can
you do something like this?!
To the people you once tried to protect?!
Because those people are
not worthy of being protected!
What's the matter, Ryo?
There was a man flying in the sky.
Okay, next one!
I'll take out as many as I can...
What is it?
He's what?!
"Welcome to Sky Tower"
The elevators are still working.
If Hitomi is sending out
electrical signals across Japan,
then he's in the control room.
Probably.
Oh, here it comes.
Heike!
What are you here for, Toki?
Ha! I'm here to kick
Hitomi's ass, and stop the bombs!
I'm afraid I can't allow that.
I won't let you interfere.
So you mean, you really
have turned traitor on us, Heike.
I'm just doing the job I'm
supposed to be doing.
Is killing people with bombs the
job of a Code: Breaker?!
I've always thought you
were a bit of a dark horse.
But when it came to wiping out
evil as a Code: Breaker,
I always felt you took pride in it.
And yet...
Toki...
Toki, I never knew
you thought so much of me.
But there's nothing I can do.
I must... Huh?
You know what this means?!
It means that after I defeat you,
I'll be Code 02, won't I?!
What?!
Thank you, Heike! And now, farewell!
For my sake, it's time to die!
An eye for an eye! A tooth for a tooth!
The hammer of justice for evil!
"It's Showtime" starts now!
Please stop this, Toki and Heike!
Straight Flush!
What?!
Now then, Toki,
how shall I bring you to pain?
You sick sadistic bastard!
You have a potty mouth.
You need to be spanked.
Heike's Ten-Mirror-Flower!
My light information
is flawlessly copied.
Which means my strength
and special abilities are also equal!
Damn it!
What's the matter, Toki?
I thought you were going to
flatten me, and become Code 02.
Shut up!
After I kick your glittery little asses,
I'm gonna come and kick your ass directly!
Ho?
Take your medicine, you sick pervert!
You are without beauty, Toki.
Oh, crap!
Take this!
Excellent!
But when compared to the speed of light...
Slowly!
Toki is using magnetism, and Heike
is using light power to fly!
The people are not worthy of protection?
Yes. They are all fools.
You're wrong! You're absolutely wrong!
The people are not fools!
Hey, you! Keep away from here!
Found it! Here it is!
All right.
You think the Young Lady is okay?
Right now, all we can do is let
the Young Lady take care of herself.
What are you doing?!
There's a bomb over here.
There's no telling when it will go off.
You guys are in danger, too, so stay back.
Ho, the police are taking action, too, huh?
How did you guys...
Somewhere in Tokyo,
our Young Lady is giving her all.
So we've gotta stick
our necks out, too, you know!
This is a dangerous area!
Please move to the park off of 3rd Street!
Don't go looking down on us.
Why do you think we do this job?
This area is dangerous!
Please move outside!
Where's the bomb squad?
It's no use. There are too
many places, and not enough men.
Oh, no. We're running out of time.
There are those who
do all that they can for peace.
But if they risk their
lives for the sake of those
who are unworthy of
protection, then they're fools.
Why? Why are they not worthy of protection?
You don't even know that?
Come on! Quickly, or the
time for the explosion will arrive!
Once the time comes,
the Prime Minister will die.
I said shut up!
Toki, why are you trying
to save the Prime Minister?
Because you're a Code: Breaker?
That's none of your business!
Damn you!
You're shaken up, Toki.
Are you unsure of yourself?
Shut up, you twinkling bastards!
Is that all you've got to say?
The people you protected...
the people you tried to protect...
...are now fools, Hitomi?
That's right. They're fools.
I don't accept that!
There's no way I accept you doing this!
You're using quite a bit
of your special ability, huh?
You're going to go Lost.
Toki, the end is near.
Now, to finish this!
Royal Straight Flu...!
Take this!
Whoa! That's far enough.
You've sure been on a spree, haven't you,
Yukihina?
But you're finished now!
Now that I'm here, there's
no way you're getting through.
So, you're alive.
I've come back from Hell for this!
One day, you, too, will know
where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city,
unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following
wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from
which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear; the answers
lie beyond the darkness
Next time,
"Code: Breaker" episode 12,
"Devils... God and Man...
Sakura Watching Over."
I am here to bring an
end to all of this, Hitomi!