Why is there no final piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
Kidnapped the Prime Minister?!
Damn it!
We've been tricked!
If he got us all together here, and used that opening to attack,
then he planned this carefully.
Even if we attempted to rescue
the Prime Minister now, we'd be too late.
Ha! There's no need to help him!
What are you saying, Toki-kun?!
The Prime Minister is your father, Toki-kun.
How about showing a little concern for him?
His father?!
Then we have all the more reason to save him!
Not interested.
Where are you going?!
On a date. See ya.
A date, at this hour?
Good grief, what is he thinking?
I'm sure he is thinking along his own lines.
It's all right. He will return.
We should be more concerned about what we will do next.
About Hitomi-san?
Yes, he...
he's always been the kind of guy who's difficult to predict.
The cat is talking?!
Ah, yes, Yuki-kun has gone Lost, as well.
Yuki-kun?
So you turn into a cat when you turn Lost?
That's right. It's a real hassle.
By the way, Sakurakoji-san,
after taking Hitomi's attack, did your body sustain any damage?
I'm perfectly fine.
Is that so?
I can hardly believe what a fool you are, exposing yourself to such danger.
W-What do you mean, fool?!
You could have been killed!
I just... didn't want anyone else to die.
That again?
How can you be so-
I won't have it!
I won't have... anybody dying.
King & Soldier, Child & House
Episode 8
Are you all right, men?
Boss, it'll take more than that to kill members of the Kizakura-gumi!
That's right!
We're fine!
Men...
I have to admit, though, that long-haired bastard...
He really did use a weird technique. Just who was he?
Hitomi has a special ability, which allows him to manipulate electricity.
Those corpses who showed up at the school yesterday...
Their bodies were controlled by Hitomi.
He is also a former Code:Breaker.
Three years ago, he disappeared off our radar.
Then, the Prime Minister is his former superior, is he not?
Why would he abduct him?
Revenge.
He did say revenge.
Does he hold a grudge against the Prime Minister?
Even supposing that Hitomi held some grudge,
if he wanted to get him back, he could just kill him,
without kidnapping him.
Some other objective, then?
Probably.
What could Hitomi-san be trying to do?
I don't know.
What I am sure of is that he used the Police Chief and that gang
to prepare for something.
The abduction of the Prime Minister may be the culmination of that.
Damn it!
Why did Hitomi-san betray us?!
Oji-dono...
Number one...
wasn't always the kind of guy who would do this.
The number one that
we all knew, is gone now.
You guys... thought a lot of Hitomi-dono.
Hitomi-san was the Code:Breaker's leader, respected by all.
Whatever the past may be,
I will burn all who fall into evil.
Even if they were once my friend!
Little sis!
Nobody is here today.
Sis.
Good, you're safe.
I'm all right, Toki.
You came because you were worried. I'm glad.
You don't mean... Your memories...
What do you mean? Also, who are you?
Oh yeah, I'm going shopping with Daddy tomorrow!
I can't wait.
I promise I'll save you from this.
Huh? What?
Nothing at all.
I won't have... anybody dying.
Why is she so insistent?
Could it be fate?
Yeah. It has turned out just as we feared.
Still...
It's all right.
No matter what happens, Sakura-chan is still our daughter.
Boss! The doctor has arrived!
Oh, glad to hear it! We have to go greet him.
Graduation Ceremony
What the...?
Father!
The doctor is...
Huh?
Ogami... What are you doing?
Ah, you're looking through that album, huh?
That sure takes me back.
What's this, here?
Finger-lacing.
Not finger-hooking?
Finger-hooking sounds painful, doesn't it?
Better to just lace them all up.
You do this, and by grasping each other's fingers,
it forms a handclasp that allows for an exchange of good cheer.
Ever since I was little, I would exchange good cheer over and over,
with Father, with Mother, and everyone else in the household.
It's a Sakurakoji family tradition.
I see.
You sure do love your family, don't you?
Both you, and your parents.
Although, there are no photos of you as a baby.
Have you always been so rambunctious that they couldn't take pictures of you?
Ah, that's not surprising.
I was abandoned as a child, after all.
Ogami-kun...
Do you have a moment?
Sakura is not our biological daughter.
She was left on our doorstep a long time ago.
She had blood spattered on her, and was a terrible sight.
Blood spatter?
Yes, but fortunately, she wasn't hurt.
She was just covered in a massive amount of blood.
Considering how gruesome her appearance was,
she must have experienced something awful.
That could have been the trigger
that made Sakura reject the deaths of others as strongly as she does.
Ever since that day, we have feared that the day would come
when Sakura would
be struck by tragedy again.
We wanted her to live a happy life, if possible.
However, it appears
that isn't on the cards for her.
Honestly, I don't understand the kind of powers you all have.
But I want you to protect Sakura!
I want you to protect her from any trouble!
I beg you!
What's the matter, Number five?
I was thinking about Hitomi-san.
Yeah, you two were close, weren't you, Number five?
You too, Yuki.
He just told me to do whatever I felt like.
That means he trusted you, doesn't it?
Hmm, maybe it did.
Hitomi-san always let things go without voicing his opinion, so he was pretty hard to get a handle on.
That's true.
Did he say anything to you, Number five?
When I was little, I lost my family in an accident.
I found it tough to be the only survivor.
I went through a wild period.
But when I met Hitomi-san, he said something to me.
What's that?
"If you've got time to run wild, you could always just sleep."
Huh?
Hitomi was complaining about being so busy, he had no time to sleep.
He was saying he couldn't believe that I let my wild behavior
cut into my sleeping time.
When I heard that, it made everything that was bothering me seem ridiculous.
That sounds like Number one, all right.
Number one sure has changed, hasn't he?
He sure has.
Whoops...
I fell asleep.
I've caused everyone a lot of trouble, haven't I?
What if he were to come to my place?
I'm such an idiot! There had to be some other, better way!
Man, how underwhelming.
Ogami!
For a Rare Kind like you to get discouraged,
like normal people do, is so disappointing.
I-I'm not discouraged.
It's absurd.
The reason this whole business started is because I went Lost.
Since it's me who should be feeling weak,
what reason do you have for being troubled?
D-Don't you act so stuck up!
Because if you start getting discouraged,
you're going to make fools out of those who believe in and follow you.
The boy has got it right, Sakura-jou!
Sakura-jou, injuries like these are no big deal!
You'd be treating us like strangers
if you didn't bring home your school pals
when they're being chased by bad guys!
Everyone!
The next time that bastard shows up, we'll turn the tables on him!
We're sorry to have let you face that kind of danger
while we were here with you, Sakura-jou.
We're really glad you're safe.
No! No!
If I face them like this, it will just make them worry!
It's my fault! I'm the one who needs more training!
Letting myself be caught by that scrawny man was a huge screw-up!
Daisuke-san, train me harder!
That's more like it!
We used to be like that once.
Yeah.
All centered around Hitomi-san.
I sure wish we could all fight like we did back then.
We can.
Oji, do you believe in Hitomi?
I'd like to. There must be some reason for this.
She's right.
Number one is acting
like a different person now.
Something happened to him.
Guys...
Hmph, what nonsense!
I'm not interested in what might have happened to Hitomi.
Toki-san.
No, no leads here either.
The great Toki will knock some sense back into that Hitomi jerk!
With that much settled,
let's all split up and search for Hitomi and the Prime Minister.
It's "Let's go-go time!"
Yeah!
Amazing, there's nothing left.
Eden takes care of things left behind.
Though I didn't think anything was left here.
What is it, Yuki?
No, no leads here, either.
All right.
Ogami, why did Hitomi-dono abduct the Prime Minister?
Since you've known each other for so long,
there must be something that comes to mind, isn't there?
Ogami...
Were you and Hitomi-dono-
That's none of your business.
Ogami!
Come on batter!
All right!
Come on, come on!
Come in.
Have a seat, Kanda-senei.
I see. So the Rare Kind's power is greater than we imagined.
Why didn't you tell me from the start,
that Sakurakoji-san was a Rare Kind?
Because you were once under Hitomi.
We wanted to avoid the risk of any information being leaked.
Because of your relationship with Hitomi,
we had to clean up some inconsistencies with our contacts.
We were also mistaken about Ogami
trying to immolate Sakurakoji Sakura.
Although, since she is a Rare Kind,
we weren't concerned about Ogami harming her.
You mean you suspected me?
Part of our job was to supervise you,
to make sure you weren't secretly communicating with Hitomi.
We thought Hitomi would try to make contact with you,
but that was a miscalculation.
I am...
Ogami Rei's agent.
I have nothing to do with Hitomi!
Then are you able to dispose of Hitomi?
Yes, I can.
I'll stake my pride as an agent on it.
The world that Hitomi seeks...
The world that the Prime Minister seeks...
I see.
I understand, Ace.
Have you found any leads on Hitomi?
It's no use. I can't find anything.
It looks like killing the Police Chief and that yakuza bunch is now working against us.
And the Prime Minister's home? Are you working to salvage it?
Of course.
Heike.
For you, this is pretty careless.
What do you mean?
You had to know that by gathering all the Code:Breakers together,
it would leave the area around the Prime Minister shorthanded.
I am not the one who called you.
I'm not so sure.
It was your arbitrary decision that sent Yuki in, right?
Do you suspect me?
You're surprisingly astute, aren't you?
Let's Illusion!
Why, you!
Huh?
It has begun.
This is the start of Hitomi's plan.
Another explosion!
Magnificent! Such is the power of Shadow!
A black Guardian Angel,
unique among the Code:Breakers, with the ability to protect life against all attacks.
What is the meaning of this, Heike?
I told you. Hitomi's plan has begun.
And with that, Oji,
I am going to need you to leave the area.
What?!
However excellent you may be at protecting, in this situation, you will be unable to avoid my attack!
Number five!
Is that... a fire?
Ogami, what happened to you?
Heike-senpai!
Sakurakoji-san, Ogami-kun was looking for you.
Ogami was?
You are being targeted by Hitomi, after all.
Please, come with me.
He's in here?
This is a secret base.
Oh! A Code:Breaker secret base?!
This is so exciting!
It sure is dark.
Aren't there any lights?
Prime Minister Fujiwara!
What's going on here, Heike-senpai?!
As promised, I have brought you the Rare Kind,
Ace.
Now you will allow me to
join you, won't you?
What are you saying, Heike-senpai?!
That's...!
I have decided to betray the Code:Breakers,
and ally with Hitomi.
You are a gift to that end.
Please be a good hostage, Sakurakoji-san.
One day, you, too, will know where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city, unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear. The answers lie beyond the darkness
Bullets of sorrow, sneering light, and a dark resolution.
Next time, Code:Breaker Episode 9: "Stopped Time."
Blue flame, light up the darkness of betrayal!