Your lunges are weak.
The point of your
sword is straying. See?!
You stopped moving.
I did it!
You must not let up on your attack
until your opponent is completely
immobilized. Got it, Ogami?
Please don't use that tone with me.
When you are able to surpass me,
Ogami.
"Final Episode:
'A Flower Blooming With God'"
He's supposed to be Lost.
What are these flames?
An eye for an eye; a tooth for a tooth;
evil for evil.
I'm astonished by you, Ogami.
You intend to interfere with me,
at any cost, don't you?
However...
Ogami!
You can't win.
Die under my electric shocks!
What?!
He swallowed up
Number one's special ability.
Then how do you like this?!
Is that?!
You can't possibly absorb this
much lightning with your flames
if you take it all at once!
Hitomi!
Take this!
Damn it!
Sakurakoji!
Come on, Ogami!
Get out of there, already!
Quit it, already, Number one!
The lightning...
He ate it!
Magnificent... Magnificent, Ogami!
What's going on, Ogami?
No, this is unlike anything else before!
Not yet. It's not over yet!
No matter the obstacle...
Don't do it, Hitomi!
I will fulfill...
Hitomi!
...my plans...
...and sacrifice 50,000!
Magnificent.
Imagine, it being this great...
Burn away.
- Hitomi!
Is it over?
Ogami!
Number six!
I am content, Ogami. And also, Ace.
Hitomi!
Kanda...
Ogami! Ogami!
Wake up, Ogami!
I see...
I failed, didn't I?
Hitomi, you should lie still.
Keep away from me.
Hitomi!
Sure enough, he's at Code: End.
Wha...? Hitomi is?!
Oh, no...
Hitomi...
Is that right? You all knew the
truth about Code: End already?
Number one...
Hitomi, you're...
It looks like I'm just about out of time.
The symptoms of my
going Code: End appeared
soon after Eden started coming after me.
I was afraid.
I thought, "I sure
would hate to die in solitude."
I realized that this terror
was what the fallen
Code: Breakers had also felt.
It's only natural that you
wouldn't understand how I feel.
There's no way you could.
If possible, I'd like to
have spent some more time
looking for a way to change Eden,
but when my Code: End
became a certainty,
my time became quite limited.
Just what could I do?
I could not forgive Eden.
But even more than that,
I wanted to save those
like us who had special powers.
I wanted to spare those
with special abilities this terror.
I wanted their lives to be complete,
like so many other people.
It all fell apart, though.
But... it's still not over.
It's not going to end here.
Stop, already, Hitomi!
I'll at least deal with
the Prime Minister myself!
Hitomi...
For what he did to the fallen
Code: Breakers, he will atone!
He, at least, is going to pay. I swear it!
Enough, already, Hitomi!
If I don't do it,
then who's going to do it?!
Even if it means
exterminating all those people?!
For the sake of special abilities?
For revenge against Eden?!
You killed so many people!
You sacrificed them!
You, the one who hated when people
became victims more than anything!
You, who worked so desperately
to save the lives of others!
You!
How did you end up doing this?!
How could you take things
into your own hands like this?!
I am... Code 01...
If I didn't do it...
He's taken everything upon himself.
Almost as though he...
As though he...
Hitomi!
Kanda isn't the only
one of Eden's observers;
it was carried out on
you Code: Breakers, as well.
There was a risk of upsetting
my plan if I contacted you.
There was a possibility that you'd
be dragged into being pursued, too.
That's why I...
Hitomi!
Number one!
Is that right? Even if
I did drag you into this with me,
I still should have met...
with you guys.
Hitomi...
Just like old times.
Yuki, you were the
earliest one to bulldog me, huh?
That's Code 03 for you.
Number one...
Toki...
Thanks for protecting Kanda.
You were right.
That was something
I shouldn't have done, huh?
Hitomi...
I'm sorry about that, Kanda.
Oji...
You fought Yukihina, and came
out unharmed. That's incredible.
It is too bad that we
didn't get the children, though.
I was just...
I'm not blaming you.
Heike, I trusted you all
the way through to the end.
Even that one time,
when you were acting suspiciously,
I thought I could trust you.
Yes, like the time we spent
together, as Code: Breakers.
If I had just kept control
of the transmit point,
my plan would not have
fallen through. You really had me.
If I had met with you all sooner,
the future would be different.
There'd be a better path...
one that I couldn't create on my own...
Ogami, your power astonished me.
But you didn't finish the job.
You're too lenient.
I told you before, remember?
You must not let up on your attack
until your opponent
is completely immobilized.
What is this?
What did you think you were doing?!
Why do you have to
look so ignoble to us now?
Why did you have to be
defeated by me? Why you?!
You, the mightiest
Code: Breaker, Code 01, Hitomi?!
Reaching Code: End, and
looking the way you do, about to die!
You were going to come
forward as a Code: Breaker for justice!
You can't be a champion of
justice if you're dead, now, can you?!
This way, it's like
you're dying for nothing, isn't it?!
You're right.
I wanted to see this through
to the end, no matter what.
But it doesn't look like this
body can do anything anymore.
Ogami, you could
always announce yourself.
You are, in very fact,
the Code: Breaker of justice
that put a stop to the ringleader
behind this incident, after all.
You, Toki, Yuki, Oji...
...not to mention Heike.
All of you, step out
into the daylight together.
Do that, and no longer...
...will anyone else have to die in solitude...
No one else... no one else...
That won't be possible.
With only this much harm done,
the people will soon forget.
If you were to come forward,
you would only make them fear
the presence of those with special
abilities, and Code: Breakers.
Very good. It looks like
everything has been settled.
How can you say such an awful thing?!
Why didn't you listen to what he had to say?!
Hitomi just went to you to talk!
He was just trying to
let everyone live happily!
That's easy for you to say.
Why do I have to listen to
anything the Code: Breakers say?
But, you're the one who chose Hitomi...
And now I wish I hadn't.
Who knew that he would
turn into a terrorist like this?
I must be more cautious
when selecting Code: Breakers, huh?
Starting next time.
Fujiwara!!
Hitomi!
Number one!
I will not allow you
to mess with anyone
with special abilities ever again!
You, at least...
...will pay!
Fujiwara!!
No. No more.
Let the rest of us take it from here.
Don't add any more evil to yourself.
I don't want to see you working evil.
Let us handle this.
I'll never forget what you taught me.
There's no way I'll ever forget you.
I see... Without me realizing it,
you've grown up, haven't you?
I am relieved... Rei...
You have fulfilled your role well.
Thank you very much, Ace.
He finally died, did he?
A problem child, right up to the end.
Enough out of you!
Why did it have to end up like this?
Hitomi took the lives of many people.
He got what he deserved.
Ogami!
Were there not other ways he could have...
It doesn't matter what you say now!
Those who are dead are not coming back.
Ogami...
I heard that the mad
bomber has been shot dead.
Serves the guy right.
The police all over Japan played a huge role, too.
The police sure do protect our towns, huh?
My, that was good work.
I just carried out my duty.
You're so modest. I have to say,
everyone fell for your "betrayal."
I'm surprised he left himself so vulnerable.
Yes, indeed.
Then there's Yuki and Hachioji.
You made good use of them.
The children with special
abilities escaped being taken,
and I avoided being blown up.
Hmph, I get it.
There was another reason why
you had those two work independently.
You wanted to have Ogami's
back to the wall as much as possible,
to draw out his true power, right?
With those other two there,
even Hitomi would
have been outnumbered.
That's why you had
them working separately, instead.
And as a result, you were able
to get Ogami to reveal his true power.
Nicely done, indeed! I'm impressed.
Why, thank you.
Your fight against Hitomi was
quite the brilliant act.
It was no act.
So, what do you think about Ogami's power?
Is it capable of going
up against the "Seekee"?
I see. So Hitomi is dead, is he?
In that case, she is going to be
used as a collar around his neck...
The girl...
Ogami's power worked
well enough this time around,
but I can't say for certain
that it won't run out of control later.
Hey, we've got the rarebreed.
As long as we use her power,
it will be possible for us
to extinguish those flames.
Extinguish those flames... meaning Ogami.
Our plan is moving forward with great success.
It was because of Ogami and the rarebreed
that Hitomi was chosen to
be a Code: Breaker to begin with.
We let the powerful special abilities of Hitomi
collide with those of the growing Ogami.
It ended up with Ogami's
powers being neatly drawn out.
Just like we planned.
Yes, indeed.
All right! We've got our pieces
to play against the Seekee.
We'll use fire to fight fire.
Fire, you say?
Still, this will be tough.
Hitomi's rebellion only caused slight damage;
but up next will be the real deal... the Seekee.
There's always something to worry about.
That is what I was about to say.
Putting yourself in front of Hitomi like that...
You protected me, didn't you?
Besides, it will take more than
that to bring me to harm, right?
I...
Prime Minister!
Looks like I've been
bitten by a cornered rat.
Hitomi...
Ogami...
Nyanmaru, you look down.
Yuki!
Number six is gone.
Nyanmaru, cheer up!
If anything's bothering you,
just call. I'll help out anytime.
M-My thanks.
Okay!
Yuki came to say his goodbyes.
His goodbyes?
We were all called in
over the Hitomi matter, you see.
Now that it's over, we've all
been given separate jobs of our own.
Thanks for everything.
Your mom's cooking was delicious.
Mother will be delighted to hear that!
That's a pretty smile.
You look good that way.
Oji... your smile is incredibly stunning.
Y-You dumbass!
W-Well, see you later.
What a nice person.
Everyone will be going away now.
W-What is it, Puppy?
It's not as though I miss them.
It's not as though...
What's the matter, there, Sakura?
I-I wasn't crying, or anything!
Both Oji and Yuki, huh?
What about you, Toki?
I'm going to enjoy
every day with you, Sakura...
My word, how shameless!
That was mean.
- And here I was thinking of telling
you about what Ogami is doing, too.
- What?!
- And here I was thinking of telling
you about what Ogami is doing, too.
Where is he? Tell me, Toki!
I cannot just let him go off on his own!
I must keep watch over him!
You're making me a little jealous.
You don't say.
Onto his next location, already?
The jerk really up and left
without saying anything to you?
The guy's so heartless,
for crying out loud.
If you're gonna leave,
you have to at least say goodbye.
I mean, really...
Whoa, Sakura!
Excuse me, but I want you
to stop the bus! I'm getting off!
Goodbye, Sakura.
Look, over here!
Ogami...
This one's mine!
- No you don't!
- Wait up!
Amazing! Amazing!
Ogami...
...even if Code: Breakers are those
whose existence the world knows not,
you are not someone who doesn't exist.
I know of your existence.
You exist within all of us.
You are not alone.
And as long as you, Toki,
Oji, Yuki,
Heike, and Miss Kanda are around,
Hitomi will continue to exist.
None of you are alone!
Ogami!
An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth; evil for evil!
Why is there no final
piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence
facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
(Still alive, so paint it black)
(Pickin' up the world, let it bleed)