An eye for an eye,
a tooth for a tooth, and a requiem of fury for evil.
Stay out of this!
They got away...
Are you going on a killing spree?
Why is there no final piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
I'm leaving.
I'm so confused on what's going on.
But there's one thing I'm sure of.
What he is doing is wrong!
Good morning, Sakurakouji-san!
Are you here to keep an eye on me?
Not at all. I'm just observing.
Ogami, you shouldn't forget that I'm also keeping an eye on you.
Furious Courage and Engraved Hammer
Episode 3
Aoba!
Good morning, Sakura!
I see you recieved quite a pile today again.
Hey Sakura,
you came to school with Ogami-kun today, didn't you?
Aoba...
It's alright, you don't have to say anything.
I'm sorry Aoba.
From now on I'll be going to and from school with Ogami.
You and I can no longer...
Congrats, Sakura!
It's really not something to celebrate.
If only I could keep an eye on him at all times...
Sakura, I'm so jealous!
I wish I could watch him all day long.
Indeed, it would certainly make my life easier.
Ogami-kun! Please take care of Sakura for me, okay?
Of course.
Ah, but you'll have to watch your back.
Ogami!
G-Get away from Sakurakouji-san!
All the guys who've been after Sakura will be after you now.
Don't lay a hand on him!
I'll be your opponent!
She's so cool!
Sakura...
Do you like him that much?
Sakurakouji-san, you don't have to protect me.
I'm a big boy, after all.
Ogami-kun!
You're on class duty tomorrow, so you'll have to go get the duty-journal from the student council room.
Student council room?
Oh that's right, you haven't been there yet.
What should we do?
I will show him the way.
You sure are nervous.
As long as you don't do anything suspicious,
I won't do anything at school.
I want to avoid things from getting complicated.
Well, you don't have to worry that I'm going to reveal your secret.
That's why, regarding...
Lefty and Righty, I've found you!
Fujiwara-senpai!
I really wish you would stop naming my breasts.
Ah, I see.
So your right boob is Righty and the left one is Lefty.
Don't think about it too much!
I love them, they're mine.
Senpai...
Nice, huh?
Ogami!
You think so too?
Sure.
So you think like I do, don't you?
Now I'm liking Ogami-kun too!
Why thank you.
Maybe I'll make an exception and show you my secret.
Her eyes have different colors.
Ogami!
I'm sorry, Senpai.
I mistook you for somebody else.
Ogami!
Wait, Ogami!
Mistaking her for somebody else doesn't excuse anything!
What's up?
A job with that guy? Fine by me.
In a Call
Unlisted Caller
Call Ended
I'm looking forward to this one.
What is it?
The preparations for tonight are complete.
The key is in the basket.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Right, I've got it.
What do you want, Sakurakouji-san?
Ah, w-what was that phone call about?
You aren't up to something no good now, are you?
W-What is that? Such a strange thing.
It's that Dog's pup.
She had a puppy?
They do look the same!
And this one is also a scaredy-cat.
So you are her puppy?
That dog's...
I'm so sorry. If only I had been stronger.
Your mom was protecting me!
They're so carefree...
A temporary peace.
What?
Will you be okay?
If you follow me,
you won't be able to come back to this peaceful world.
We're way past you having to tell me stuff like that.
Besides, my world was never peaceful to begin with.
Not locking the gates, how careless.
What, is this your home?
Are you really going in?
Let's just see what kind of place you live in!
Huh? Who're you?
Ogami, what on earth...?
What are you little shits doing here?
This is a Yakuza's den.
And this is...!
Is Ogami going to...
Ogami! The police are already here!
It doesn't seem like it's your show tonight!
Sakurakouji-san, the police are in on it as well.
What?!
Hey, hey, Nii-san,
aren't you being a little too full of yourself?
Do you think you can do something like this without-
There aren't as many of you as I expected.
Looks like I can finish this in no time.
Huh? What are you gonna do in no time?
Isn't it obvious? I'll kill all of you.
What?!
What the fuck are you talking about?!
Don't underestimate us you brat!
Do you know what you're getting yourself into, you little bastard?!
Shut up!!!
Nii-san, what group are you from?
I'm from class 1-B.
I'll let that slide.
You have some guts, Nii-san.
But saying that you'll kill us all isn't very sensible.
Mind telling us your reason?
Because I eliminated the G-Falcons,
who you used to do your
dirty work pushing your goods.
You've worked hard.
You did?
Who are you trying to fool?!
I told you to shut up, idiot!
I-I'm sorry!
Even if it's a bluff you've shown that you have some real nerve,
it might be in our interests to let you join us.
Alright, how about this?
Become my subordinate.
As you said, I've been lacking manpower since we lost G-Falcon.
Really? Is the work any good?
Ogami!
Won't you tell me?
You bet, it's great work.
This here, we could sell it, but the buyers would soon run out of money.
That's why we use it as bait.
When we lay out the bait, people do just about anything to get their hands on it.
This guy used do all kinds of dirty work for me, but lately he's become useless.
That's when...
His family...
That's right.
His wife and daughter will earn us some good money.
Kidnapping?
The G-Falcons were too rough and had their way with the girls.
You, on the other hand, could use sweet words to talk them into doing what you want.
We have a long list of families.
You'll have a guaranteed payout.
I see. And you've got the cops involved.
Exactly, so there's no worry about getting caught.
Right, Katou-san?
This is outrageous!
And you call yourselves Yakuza?
And you two! The police is supposed to be protecting people!
Don't you feel ashamed?
Feel ashamed?
What's so funny?!
Kid, these days people only care about themselves.
Miss, don't hate the players.
In the world of adults we all have to adapt to the game.
You'll understand when you've grown up.
However Nitta-san,
since she's seen us we can't
just let her walk out of here.
We have no need for her, do we?
You bastards!
Ogami!
Sakurakouji-san, words don't work on these guys.
We'll just have to suppress them by force.
Wait!
What's with the blue flame?
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth, and evil for evil!
Burn to ashes!
Nitta-san!
Don't! Ogami!
Let go!
Evil.
I got you..
Hot! It's hot! Put it out! Please!
Evil.
Stop it, Ogami! Don't!
Don't fuck with us!
The bullet...
What are those flames?
What are you?!
A m-monster?!
An eye for an eye,
a tooth for a tooth,
and evil for evil!
Officer Katou's taking his sweet time.
He probably got his hands on some woman, don't you think?
Should we head back to the station?
Yeah. I still have to finish the plans with Hitomi.
Ogami!
You didn't have to kill them!
There must have been another way!
What kind of way?!
There wasn't any other way.
If I hadn't killed them, they
would have just killed more.
But...
Give me some...
Besides, your words didn't reach them.
These days people only care about themselves.
This is how it works in the adult world.
We don't need her, do we?
You can only suppress evil by force.
Even so!
Even so...
Puppy?
Get a hold of yourself! It's alright now!
It's alright?!
Yes, let's get out of here!
Where do you live?
Live?
It's no use, I can't go back. Not like this.
I can't return home anymore!
What are you talking about?
My life is shattered.
My husband is like that...
I can't take it anymore! It's all over!
I'd be better off dead!
Better off dead!
Don't say such stupid things.
Ogami?
Then die!
Stop it, Ogami!
Don't, Ogami! Ogami!
I don't want to die...
I don't want to die!
If you think you're in so much pain, and feel like you want to die,
it's just because you've had an easy life.
If you don't want to die, then don't act like a baby!
Get through the pain, crawl around and live to the bitter end!
If you still want to die, look for me.
I'll kill you.
Ogami... Why would you go that far?
How much of you is evil?
How much is...?
Ogami!
How is it? Can you feel it?
I can feel your warmth.
Sakurakouji-san, what are you doing?
It's a hug. I'm communicating with our bodies through a hug.
I know that you are fighting.
I also know that you have your reasons.
But that's not something I can accept.
That's why I'll fight too!
I will come at you until my words reach you.
You say such strange things.
I wonder if that's because you are a "Rare Kind"?
What is that "Rare Kind" anyway?
Sakurakouji-san, sorry but, I don't understand people.
And I don't have any desire to be understood by anyone either.
What?!
It's me. I'm all done in here.
Come and collect Sakurakouji-san for me.
What do you want?
You're chief inspector Takata, right?
Too bad but I took the liberty of killing all your accomplices.
Where is that guy you've been hanging around with?
You shit, are you a Code:Breaker?!
Where's Hitomi?!
Hitomi-san! Please save me!
I'm being followed by a Code:Breaker!
That's a bummer.
Save me, please!
I've been cooperating, haven't I?
Yeah thanks, you were a great help.
But you know, what you're doing right now is undignified and I don't like it.
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Say goodbye to your Chief of Police job.
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi
In a Call
Hang         Up
Hitomi! You bastard!
I was cooperating with you!
I helped you with your plans!
What?
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth, and evil for evil...
Toki.
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth,
and a hammer of justice for evil.
Ogami!
You were nothing but my... opening act!
One day, you, too, will know where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city, unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear. The answers lie beyond the darkness
Next time, Code:Breaker episode 4:
"Voices of Time."
It feels better if you're not alone.
You do have friends, Ogami.