Why is there no final piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
Stopped Time
Episode 9
Maximum Clearance: 2.5 m
Explosions? What's going on?
I don't know any details yet.
Maximum Clearance: 2.5 m
Just that explosives were used in several locations around the city.
Master...
What?
It has to be Hitomi-san.
Kanda...
Yes?
I will stop Hitomi. Got it?
Yes.
He abducts the Prime Minister, and now, terrorist bombings...
Hitomi...
Currently, the confirmed casualty count from these bombings alone is twelve dead,
Bombings within the                                          city leave many dead
twenty four people seriously injured, with four reported missing.
The explosions took place during the evening rush hour,
and it is anticipated that the number of victims will continue to rise hereafter.
Yes. Victims!
I-It's terrible what's happening, isn't it?!
More worried about others than yourself.
That's just like you.
You look like you're enjoying yourselves.
What are you talking about?
We were discussing Sakurakoji-san's character.
I have to admit,
I didn't think you'd actually bring her here.
My role is to cater to your every desire, Ace.
That's how it has always been, right?
You've been under protection for a long time, you know.
Protection?
First, there was Heike,
then, more recently, Ogami-kun was transferred to that school to keep you guarded.
Ogami was?!
But,
Ogami-kun didn't seem to be aware of what his purpose was.
Isn't that right, Prime Minister?
All of it done to try to thwart my plans.
You were awfully well-prepared, but I still prevailed.
Plans? What do you mean?
What do you plan on doing with me?
I won't be doing anything.
You're a Rare Kind, after all.
I just wanted to keep you secured here, since you'd be a problem if you got in the way.
All you have to do is sit back and watch, without interfering with my plans.
Plans?
Deaths continue to rise after series of explosions
You don't mean these explosions?!
That's right.
Why would you do something like this?!
If I said it was to save the Code:Breakers,
would you believe me?
I'm sure you must have some reason.
I know your level of kindness better than anyone.
Hitomi-san...
Received 1 new message
Master, it's Kanda.
I received a text from an unknown sender that shows Hitomi-san's current location, and...
You got it too?
By the way, Ace, the bombs that were set around the city
aren't the end of this, are they?
The real plan has yet to be set in motion, right?
How obnoxious.
Sounds like you've been sniffing around, right, Heike?
You make it sound so vile. I was-
Heike...
it's not as if I 100% trust you.
Oh?
What kind of tricks did you pull to find this hideout so easily?
Perhaps you've been keeping an eye on me since before this began.
My information network has had this location flagged.
We were able to track you down just in time.
That is alarming.
But I've figured out what your true intention is.
I'd hate to have you be caught by Eden. I want to help you.
Which is precisely why I abducted Sakurakoji-san,
and reduced Hachoji Rui to a bloody mess.
Oji-dono?!
You, who cares more than anyone for the Code:Breakers, took out Oji?!
Why?
Because I understand your anger and grief better than anyone else.
Why would you hurt Oji-dono?!
You'll pay for this!
You do not know the feelings of someone who doesn't exist!
Ace, I don't blame you for not believing me.
However...
Do as you please.
But if you try anything funny, I'll kill you.
I will endeavor to live up to your expectations.
Oh, they're here.
If Kanda is here, that means Ogami-kun will arrive soon.
Sure enough, a conflict is unavoidable.
I know this is sudden, but Heike, would you do a job for me?
Hitomi-san... is in there.
I will stop Hitomi. Got it?
I'm sorry, Master.
Heike?!
What are you doing here?
I've always wanted to tie you up.
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
What did you say?
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Ogami-kun, isn't Sakura-kun with you?
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
Emergency Report
Series of
Bombings
She hasn't come home yet.
She's not answering her cell, either.
Could something have happened to her?
All right.
I think I know where to look.
I'll contact you if I find anything.
Number six!
Number two has turned on us!
Well, well...
Yuki-kun!
What did you do to Number five?!
Why, whatever do you mean?
Don't play dumb!
I saw the whole thing! You attacked Number five!
I see.
That was careless of me.
What's the meaning of this, Heike?
What do you think?
This is what it means!
Then you really have turned on us, Number two?!
It can be a pain how the sound special ability is invisible,
but if you can get a handle on its straight-line movement, it's not difficult to avoid.
Gah, you're pissing me off!
Stop running away!
Well, obviously I'm going to evade them.
Huh?
No mercy, I see, Ogami-kun.
Those who stand in my way don't deserve mercy!
Are you going to stick to that policy?
Number six! Watch out!
Just keep heading up, Number six.
I'll take care of Number two.
I see. Then I'll deal with you first.
Kanda, wasn't Hitomi here?
Don't tell me Hitomi got you...
Spot on.
Hitomi!
Sakurakoji-san!
Ogami! Kanda-sensei is being controlled!
You must help her!
I see, you're using electricity to send commands to her mind.
You're controlling her, aren't you?
It's not hard at all.
Much easier than controlling a corpse.
Hitomi...
Master...
I'm sorry, Master...
Hitomi-san has me...
No!
Master,
please run away.
Master...
Ogami!
How many more rounds?
I will take all the bullets you have.
Hurry up and empty the clip.
Amazing, Ogami-kun.
But even so, I think I'm going to take you out of the picture here.
I have given instructions to Kanda that her final bullet is to go through her own head.
What will you do?
If you avoid her shots, Kanda will keep shooting,
and with the last bullet, she will commit suicide.
But, if you take a bullet and die, my control over Kanda will end right there.
Kanda will not have to die.
Hitomi...
Master...
Can you look on as Kanda kills herself?
You coward!
This is beyond cruel, Hitomi-senpai-dono!
What a kindhearted girl you are.
Hitomi-senpai-dono, you used to be friends with Kanda-sensei and Ogami!
How could you do something like this?!
Don't let him get away with this,
Ogami!
I won't allow you to commit suicide.
I will end this, by my hand!
Ogami...
you don't mean...!
Striking back and eliminating an enemy who threatens you without hesitation.
You haven't changed, Ogami-kun.
But, can you really do it?
Master...
I'm so sorry...!
Ogami, wait!
Don't do it, Ogami!
Do not kill her!
What the...?
Sakurakoji-san!
Huh? What on earth happened?
Hmmm? You loosened the ropes?
Am I...?
Kanda-sensei!
Sakurakoji-san...?
Thank goodness! You're back to normal!
I'm glad.
Your desperate wish broke you free of Hitomi-senpai-dono's special ability!
That's a Rare Kind for you.
Sure enough, you seem likely to interfere in all sort of ways.
Now you intend to take Puppy hostage?!
Hitomi, what are you scheming?
Why are you doing this?
The old you would never do this sort of thing.
Why?
Do you still not know, even after looking at the clocks in this room?
Now that you mention it, this room...
has nothing but stopped clocks.
These are the times of each former Code:Breaker's death.
6:23,
the former Code 03 dies while on escort duty.
22:47,
the former Code 06 dies in a sudden accident
while passing judgment on evil.
Those who do not exist do not even get headstones erected in their name,
so it's the least I could do.
They all died judging evil that the law could not judge...
without anyone knowing about it.
Hitomi-senpai-dono...
This kind of thing... has to be brought to an end.
He's doing this for his friends that have died, all by himself?
The one who gave them their orders was the Prime Minister.
For this, he must pay.
I will have the Prime Minister accept the consequences with his death.
N-No, you can't kill the Prime Minister!
Nothing will come of you doing something like that!
Oh, something will come of it.
The Prime Minister will die while performing in his supreme role.
His supreme role?
There was an explosion just now! The smoke is tremendous!
Many people are down. It's terrible.
Many people will die before the Prime Minister's execution.
The situation is terrible!
he citizens will live in terror.
And then finally comes the main event.
The Prime Minister, along with even more people across Japan, will lose their lives.
How could you?!
Screw you!
For what reason are you doing this?
Killing people who are free of guilt?
To leave this memory.
To ingrain terror within the memories of the people of this country.
The reality that many people are being executed together with Prime Minister Fujiwara.
They should learn their lesson.
Those who live in a world of fabricated, temporary peace...
It's a temporary, fabricated peace.
Someone help! My child!
Somebody!
People who bask in peace will tremble in fear,
then, from the bottom of their hearts,
they will want someone to kill whomever brought this kind of atrocity upon them.
An absolute "someone," who will
eliminate evil, no matter the means.
Yes.
The Code:Breakers!
By doing so, the Code:Breakers will no longer have to die without anyone knowing about them.
This is for the Code:Breakers...
But-!
So when all of this is over,
you'll come forward as a Code:Breaker of Justice,
and judge evil, out in the open?
That's right.
It's true, I'm not comfortable being a lapdog of Eden.
Ogami...
I wouldn't mind moving out in the open.
By creating this much of a stink,
Eden might think so, as well.
Why don't you join me, Ogami-kun?
But do not forget...
Code:Breakers who judge evil are still killers!
There is no need to reward them!
Why don't you get it,
Ogami-kun?
You're the one who doesn't get it.
You killed innocent people to bring about this incident.
You! The one who hated innocent people dying the most!
Is that the best you've got, Yuki-kun?
What a spoilsport.
I'm just getting warmed up!
Then again, I've gotta hand it to Number two.
You haven't changed, Ogami-kun.
But there's no turning back now.
Now is the time for Code:Breakers to change into existent beings!
No longer as those who die in solitude, unknown to everyone!
Everyone can be who they wish to be!
By sacrificing the citizen's terror,
I liberate the Code:Breakers from Eden!
Hitomi!
Ogami-kun!
Yukihina?!
Here I was wondering what was taking you so long to come out.
What are you doing, Hitomi?
You could have just gone ahead without me.
This is no time for you to be messing around, you know?
All right, Yukihina.
Ogami!
You cannot melt my ice with your flames.
All right, Yukihina.
I'm going on ahead.
Hitomi-san!
Wait, Hitomi!
Sakurakoji-san!
It's over.
What are you doing, Ogami?
Putting Sakura-chan in danger, are you?
Toki-kun!
Hi, Sakura-chan!
The star has arrived.
After all, the hero has to show up late, right?
Ah! Hold it! Release the Prime Minister!
Let me tell you right now,
there are bombs in this building, too.
Getting out immediately would be good for your health.
What?!
Wait! Give his father, the Prime Minister, back!
Y-You idiot!
It's too dangerous, Sakura-chan!
This isn't good.
Yuki-kun, the fight is on hold!
Hey!
Number two!
Wow. Who would have thought you'd come along with us?
I won't let you kill the Prime Minister!
Nor will I allow you to kill anyone else!
Why is he doing this?
Exactly what took place in the past?
One day, you, too, will know where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city, unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear. The answers lie beyond the darkness
That day...
the night the city was choked by the smell of
death and gun smoke, is when I first met you.
Next time, "Code:Breaker", episode 10,
"The World People See."