Why is there no final
piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence
facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
There was a fire early this
morning at the private residence
of Diet member Tabata Shigeru.
Diet member Tabata killed
Was smoking in bed the cause?!
The fire burned the
bedroom and part of the hallway
before it was put out, but what
seems to be the body of Mr. Tabata
was discovered within the ashes.
This is a terrible shame.
I had been looking forward to having Tabata
work even harder with us in the future.
There is strong suspicion
that smoking in bed was the cause.
Was he a regular smoker?
I'd heard that he was a heavy smoker,
but it is too bad, in any case.
Prime Minister, the esteemed Toki is here.
All right, send him in.
I'm so glad you're here, Toki!
That was good work last night.
Come, take a seat! Come!
Wow, it has been too long
since we've had breakfast together.
Special ability research?
That is some pretty
nasty stuff you're up to, "Souri."
"souri: 'Prime Minister'"
Oh, please, don't be like that.
Being the "Souri," it's troubling
for you to "so re-fer" to me.
"Sorry."
I thought...
I thought, if I could take some of the burden
off of you Code: Breakers, even a little bit...
I'm placing hardship upon you.
As your father, I am
conscious of that above all else.
I wanted to do something
even the least bit fatherly, and so...
I'm a Code: Breaker.
You are not my father, nor am I your son.
You're still upset about Nenene.
It pains my heart, as well,
to have put her in that position.
You promised. I would become
your dog, and wipe out evil men.
We would lay off Sissy.
That's what we decided, right?
I heard. Apparently, you quietly
went to see her, huh?
How was Nenene doing?
Miserable coward.
"Episode 6: 'Lost One'"
"Diet member Tabata dead"
This is what government power can do, is it?
The government controls the Code: Breakers.
Nobody knows, do they?
Even with all that was being done.
What's this?
H-Hey...
Someone you know?
I need a favor from you.
O-Okay.
Could you give us a little space?
Eden is not happy about you
bringing Sakurakoji Sakura
into Tabata's residence,
and exposing her to danger.
Eden is concerned with Miss Sakurakoji?
Orders from Eden...
you are to be her escort.
Why me? I want Hitomi...
Spare me the song and dance!
Just work hard and smart! Got it?
I know that you're not a big fan of Eden.
Frankly, I don't like them, either.
But when you cop such a flagrant attitude,
it just makes it harder to act.
I'll have a look into the girl myself.
Being a rarebreed notwithstanding,
there must be some reason
why they're putting a
Code: Breaker on her as a guard.
Same as always, huh?
Rei...
You've been working too much lately.
You're about to go Lost, aren't you?
Be careful.
That was a pretty woman.
Is she a Code: Breaker, too?
There's Toki, and that woman just now...
Ogami, you've got quite
a few friends, don't you?
I don't have friends. I'm a
Code: Breaker, who doesn't exist.
Okay, fine. I am relieved.
It's important that you
have people that care about you.
Ogami,
since you're here anyway,
you should become friends
with everyone in the class, and not
just your Code: Breaker pals.
It will be more fun that way.
Not necessary.
Were I to become friends with my classmates
they could still not contribute
anything toward my objective.
It's a waste of time. It would
be foolish to get overly involved,
and let them become aware of who I really am.
Also, the Code: Breakers are not my pals.
We're just colleagues,
who have a common interest.
A good morning to you!
G-Good morning, Sakura!
What's going on?
Eh? N-Nothing at all! Right?
Yeah! Nothing, nothing! Nothing at all!
"Fire at Diet Member Tabata's Estate"
Hey! Don't mess up my desk!
Sorry, sorry.
It's just about time for class to start.
Pass these handouts around.
You've got thirty minutes.
Hey, Sakurakoji, no looking around!
R-Right! My apologies!
Nobody knows, do they?
Even with all that was being done.
If you tell my secret,
I will burn up your friends
without a second thought,
Miss Sakurakoji.
"In the dark, the young man held
his breath, concealing himself.
Harboring his doubts, the young man
stole his way into the
attic over the woman's room,
eager to ascertain the truth for himself.
"The Schoolmistress"
Squeak... Squeak...
The floor in the woman's room creaked.
The young man peered into the
room through a small gap in the planks.
The young man saw her...
the woman, stretched out upon the bed.
And so, with a rough rope in hand,
as she approached the woman,
the schoolmistress smiled
beguilingly, and said..."
Heike...
Oh, Miss Kanda.
W-Would you please stop reading
smutty novels aloud
here in the hallway?
It is not smutty.
It is a work of art by Kanno.
Y-You're reading it too loud!
How rude of me.
I was unable to contain the
overflowing adoration
I have for such artistry.
Ogami, you are within sight of the Dead Zone.
Miss Sakurakoji, I'd like to go
in the classroom to get my bag.
You must not enter right now!
What are you doing?
I-I'm doing something important!
J-Just wait a little longer.
Quite a shock, huh?
I'm super-surprised!
We have to make sure no one finds out.
Miss Sakurakoji, is that about me?
Ogami is outside! Everyone, shh!
Just wait, Ogami!
Ogami! Ogami!
What are you sneaking around about?!
"Ogami Rei"
"Welcome to Class 1-B!!"
Ogami, welcome to Class 1-B!
We're sorry your welcome party is so late.
Plus it's as late as it is,
once our club activities are done.
You can still make it to your job, right?
Come on! The guest of honor gets to wear this!
We all got this ready for you,
but we rushed, so it's not too pretty.
Here, Ogami. Your present.
"Takeshi Aoki"
"Let's go to the arcade across from the
station! I heard you once lived in Tokyo!"
Learn all our names, okay?
Why are you doing this?
Isn't it obvious? We're gonna be
in class together a whole year!
Best that we enjoy it together.
Besides, Ogami, you're always smiling,
but you seem to have trouble
talking to anyone but Sakura,
so we thought that maybe you
were forcing yourself to smile.
We were all worried about you.
Please accept our regards, Ogami!
- Regards!
I just found out myself this morning.
They asked me to keep
you out of the classroom,
so they could get ready.
Mitta... Yagi... Yusa... Watanabe...
They all care about you.
Being a little bit friendly
back to them wouldn't go amiss.
No need.
Whoa! What are you doing?!
After all they did for you!
I dislike things.
When a person dies,
their things are left behind.
I'd like to take care of mine ahead of time.
"Aoki Takeshi... Let's go to the arcade."
"Aoyama Yukio... My hobby is mountain climbing."
"Ijuin Hikari... Blond Love."
"Uesugi Hajime... Please teach me some English."
I've memorized all the data written on them.
After all, knowing that group,
they'd pester me if I forgot.
Ogami...
I won't forget.
Ever.
Ogami, you're not alone.
You're not a non-existent being.
Still...
Right now, I don't need any friends.
Wha...? Good grief, you! You're so defiant.
What a drag...
It can't be... This soon? Damn it!
The report from Agent Kamura
that said he had located the target
was cut off at the end.
That now makes forty-three
agents who have gone missing.
This former Code: Breaker,
Hitomi, is quite the piece of work.
Every bit the Code 01, you might say.
Now then, I wonder how they will strike this time.
Ah, good morning, Yukihina.
You've gotten quite a few of them together.
What are you going to use them for?
To begin a new world.
Do you think Ogami was pleased?
He never really is very expressive, huh?
Isn't that true. I wonder how
he and Sakura are getting along.
I intentionally left them alone with each other,
so if they're not getting along,
I'll be disappointed.
Oh, so the two of them are on the roof.
You don't suppose that right at this moment...
Right at this moment...
Ogami! If you don't make Miss Sakurakoji happy,
you're gonna pay!
Okay, Ogami, now that
you've learned everyone's names,
that's the end of that.
Let's go clean up...
Hold on, now! What do you... Who are you?
You can't just come
in here without permission...
Who are you folks?
Sure enough, they're...
W-Wait, Ogami! You can't!
You fool! These guys are already dead!
They're what?
These corpses are just being controlled!
The only one who could do this is...
Ogami!
Sure enough, taking measures was the right idea.
What's the matter, Ogami?
Not now!
Ogami!
W-Who might you be?
M-Miss Kanda?!
Is that... Hitomi's power?
What on earth is going on?
I'll tell you later. We're getting out of here!
Oh, no! Inside the school!
Oh, no! We must get everyone to safety!
Ogami!
Kanda! Keep Miss Sakurakoji protected!
Master!
I will burn up anyone who crosses these flames!
An eye for an eye!
A tooth for a tooth!
Evil for evil!
Ogami...
Ogami, are you sure that what
you really value more than anything
isn't everyone else?
Ogami!
Master!
Number six! I'm coming... to help!
Yu... ki...
W-Who are you?
Imagine, getting yourself this pinned down.
Points off for that, Ogami.
Heike?!
And as for you, Yuki,
it's nice that you're on time,
but your work is sloppy.
Huh?
What, you wanna go?
You're already within the Dead Zone!
An eye for an eye; a tooth for a tooth;
eternal rest... for the dead!
The light special ability is awesome.
Don't tell me Heike is a Code: Breaker, too!
Ogami!
Ogami...
Ogami! Ogami, wake up!
Ogami!
Ogami...
It can't be... It can't be...
Ogami!!
He's Lost.
Lost?
Yes.
It is the destiny of us Code: Breakers.
Such is our unavoidable... fate.
One day, you, too, will know
where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city,
unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following
wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from
which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear; the answers
lie beyond the darkness
Even if it is an unavoidable fate,
I cannot accept it.
Next time,
"Code: Breaker" episode 7,
"Sakura, In the Light."
Ogami! Ogami!