I was...
Why is there no final
piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence
facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
Father! Mother!
I was!
We were so worried!
F-Father?
Sakura! You're feeling better, huh?
All thanks to your nursing, Yuki.
Uh-hum! I can do anything
for my Sakura's sake, after all!
Mother... What happened to me?
You don't remember?
No.
Is that so? At the gate...
Daisuke is the one who
found you. He was startled.
You were chilled from head to toe.
Well, I'm just glad that you're feeling better.
Father, Mother, I have caused
you worry, and I am terribly sorry.
Lift up your face, Sakura.
Papa and Mama are
just relieved that you are all right.
That's right, Sakura.
We're as glad as can be.
Mm-hmm. However, I wonder,
just who was it that carried you there?
Do you have any idea who it was?
What's the matter?
Bring judgment to the wicked?
Yes. Is that something which can be allowed?
Whether it's revenge or anything else,
no, that isn't something to be permitted.
Your papa agrees with you.
Not even so much as a cinder, huh?
Burn away.
He... tried to kill me...
Episode 2: "The Spiral Blue Flower, Blossoming in Flame"
But why did he let me go?
Sakura! Good morning!
Y-Yeah, good morning, Aoba.
Come here, come here!
There's something I want to show you!
What? Is something wrong?
Are you in a bad mood?
Ogami, what are you trying to do to me?
Geez, Sakura, are you listening?!
Eh?
I don't care how interested
in Ogami you might be,
it's awful for you to be
ignoring your best friend.
Oh, no, I apologize, Aoba.
I meant not to...
What is it? Something you want
to share? I'll bet it's about Ogami.
As it happens, last night, in the park...
What is this, Miss Takatsu?
Telling secrets?
Geez, Ogami, don't startle me like that.
Sorry. You just seemed to
be enjoying yourself so much.
Please, tell me, as well.
Hmm, I get it. Ogami,
you're concerned about Sakura.
Huh? Why do you say that?
The fact that you joined the
conversation is proof enough.
Stop!
Aoba, do not let him touch you!
Sakura?
You must not come in contact
with Ogami! You'll be burned up!
What's this? Suddenly, it's a love triangle?
Is Sakurakoji jealous?
Ogami, you're not after
just Sakurakoji, but Aoba, too?!
Pandemonium, this early in the morning?!
Sakura, what are you talking about?
All he did was put his hand on my shoulder.
Wha...? It's not that!
Miss Sakurakoji...
What are you talking about?
Please, fill me in, as well.
Why, he...
He's doing this to monitor me,
so that I will not say anything!
If I talk, he intends to burn me,
along with everyone else.
All right! Isn't that enough racket?
Let's start class!
Come on, Sakurakoji,
hurry and take your seat.
T-Teacher!
What is it?
Never mind, it is nothing.
Sakura!
Hey, don't run off without me!
A-Aoba...
Oh, no! Being together places Aoba in peril, too...
Hey, Sakura!
Sure enough,
he is observing me. If I do nothing...
Sakura!
Geez, you're eating out here?
Let's eat together.
Aoba...
Aoba, get away from me!
Whoa, what's the matter, Sakura? Get away?
Just get away from me!
Aren't you being a bit mean?
Oh, forgive me. I did not mean it like that...
Ah, mm-hmm, well, it's fine
that you're interested in Ogami,
but why are you trying
to distance yourself from me?
No!
- You see...
- I don't get you!
Aoba!
You have it wrong! Aoba!
Ogami!
Is something the matter, Miss Sakurakoji?
I need a word. Just the two of us.
Would you walk me home today, after school?
Sakura is super-forward!
An after-school date!
What does Sakurakoji see in that guy?
Sure I will. Gladly.
Aoba, once this is over,
I shall tell you everything. Just wait.
Sakura...
Okay. You got it. Off you go, Sakura.
♪ Nyan-Nyan-Nyanmaru, friend to everyone... ♪
♪ Kind-hearted ally to all kitties... ♪
♪ Life disappearing... ♪
H-Huh?
Uh-oh, I can only play one more time.
There aren't any more
Nyanmarus, either. I'll go elsewhere.
Uh, sir! Please take these with you!
Don't want 'em. You can have 'em.
Huh?
I've already rescued all the Nyanmarus.
- Uh-huh...
- Never mind that, tell me,
if you were to burn, what color would you like?
Huh? Burn?
I like blue. Blue flames are the prettiest.
You don't have to be so wary.
Then you realize that there is
something about you to be wary of, huh?
So then, what did you want to talk about?
♪ Nyan-Nyan-Nyanmaru, friend to everyone... ♪
"Local Safety Campaign At Work"
♪ Kind-hearted ally to all kitties ♪
Nyanmaru...
Nyanmaru!
"Nyanmaru"
Nyanmaru! Nyanmaru!
Huh?
Time for work...
Code: Breaker Code 03...
Tenpoin Yuki.
This should do.
You can't try any funny moves here.
Not with this many eyes around us.
Answer me! You are the one
who killed that G-Falcon bunch, right?!
Using that blue flame?
- You cannot hide...
- That is correct.
I killed them. So what?
I'm not particularly hiding that.
Do you realize what
it is that you're saying?!
It's my job.
Besides, what's so wrong
about disposing of trash like them?
Trash?
Having that group around serves no purpose.
That is why you killed them?
They were murderers.
Even so, why would you kill them?
Do you fancy yourself to be a hero of justice?
I am evil. More so than anyone else.
Evil?!
If you believe that,
turn yourself in to the police!
Atone for your crimes!
Atone?
Yes. If you turn yourself in,
your offense will be lightened.
My offense will be lightened?
What is so funny? Why do you laugh?!
Ogami, do you truly understand
what it is that you have done?
You have taken the lives of those men.
Is that all you have to say?
All right, then, I'll be going.
Ogami, you...
After what you did, you...
...you don't feel anything?!
Ogami!!
Oh, Taku, what's the matter?
I-I apologize!
It's because I shouted...
Oh, please do not cry, I beg you!
You were looking for this, right?
Thank you very much.
There, Taku, lucky for you,
there was a nice boy, huh?
Just what exactly is going on with you?
Ogami, whatever reasons you have,
it is not right for you to
be judging and killing others.
Wait! Own up and be judged by the law!
Judged by the law?
That's quite impossible.
You see, the law is there to judge people.
I am one who does not exist.
I cannot be judged by the law.
Even if I were to kill you,
along with all these other people,
I couldn't possibly be judged.
I eliminate all witnesses.
Burn away, Sakurakoji Sakura.
What are you... saying?
In front of all these people watching...
...you couldn't burn me...
...you couldn't... burn me...
Stop!
- Whoa, what's that?!
- Hey, it just caught fire!
The bag is burning!
Burn away.
Stop!!
Just kidding.
Fascinating.
What are you doing?!
I have been observing you all day,
and there's no doubt about it.
You are a rarebreed, huh?
What is your story?
You killed those people yesterday so easily,
but today, when I think you're about to kill me,
you say you were watching me?
What is it that you're thinking?!
What, you ask? The same thing that you are.
You must have thought
that that G-Falcon crowd,
who killed the homeless old man,
then without any regrets,
went on to beat up another homeless man,
as well as beat that dog,
ought to die as a matter of course.
W-What sort of nonsense is that?!
It's only right that they be killed.
It is my job to exterminate that kind of vermin.
The evil to judge evil that the law cannot judge...
That's what it is to be one
who does not exist... a Code: Breaker.
Code... Breaker...
You've thought before that
you wanted someone dead, right?
Go on, in all honesty, tell me
the name of the person you want dead.
Stop...
That... cannot be allowed...
It's wrong to kill! No matter
who is involved, it's absolutely wrong!
Why are you so worked up?
Why, you ask?
Ogami!
If you say you're going
to watch me, then do as you like.
But I will be watching you, too.
I swear, by the name Sakurakoji Sakura,
that I shall follow you, to prevent
you from harming anyone again!
Prepare yourself for that!
Why do you laugh?!
Fascinating! You really
are fascinating, aren't you?
Very well.
But just remember this...
If you tell anyone about me,
then it won't be just you,
but the person you told,
and anyone around, that I will dispose of.
And I will not let you!
Stop... Stop!
Stop!
Anytime, anywhere, anyone. No exceptions.
I'll burn them away, no matter what.
Has something happened to Sakura?
It's not like her to not say anything.
You are incapable of stopping me.
Those eyes... Those are the same eyes he had
when he killed those
people without a second thought.
Ogami...
Trash? Exterminating vermin, you say?
Then, was it the same for you at that moment?
Did you kill her with those same cold eyes?
Ogami...
...what did your eyes look like at that moment?
Are you sure about this?
Letting Rei Ogami incorporate
someone like that into the plan?
He's hard to control,
but when used properly, highly effective.
Besides, I have insurance.
It is set up to engage
if he ever gets out of control.
What is it?
It's about Sakurakoji Sakura.
Yeah. I decided not to dispose of her.
She's a rarebreed,
and it would be a shame to kill her.
A rarebreed?
Who would have thought that girl...
There's no doubt. That girl will not burn.
Not even with my flames.
One day, you, too, will know
where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city,
unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following
wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from
which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear; the answers
lie beyond the darkness
Hey, what are you doing here?
You'd dropped out of sight.
To bring an end to this world.
You gonna go on a killing spree?
Imagine, you, the guy who hates to work,
taking the initiative here.
You've grown, huh?
Still, I thought Ogami
would be the first one to show up.
Hold up, Number One.
You want to judge me, Yuki?
An eye for an eye...
a tooth for a tooth...
a requiem of fury for evil!
To be continued
Next time, "Code: Breaker" episode 3,
"Angry Valor... A Graven Hammer."
Evildoers, I will burn you
until not even a speck
of dust remains of your bodies!