"Please watch your step"
I can give him something to eat today.
Stop the bus!
Huh? The next stop is just ahead.
Just sit down and wait...
People were being burned!
Call 110! Quickly!
You're the police officer?
There were people!
Right, so someone
was being burned, were they?
Your typical flames don't
burn things up so completely
that they don't leave any debris behind.
You're sure you didn't dream it?
No way!
I am...
...certain...
These scorches are from where
some homeless guy
built a fire or something.
It can't be.
Why is there no final
piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence
facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
"Episode 1 'God's Great Judgment'"
Full point! Break!
- Th-Thank you very much!
- Thank you very much!
Next up, Sato!
Yes, if you please!
If you please!
"Fortitude and Vigor"
Last night...
Just what was that?
Full point! Break!
Nicely done!
Sakurakoji, thanks so much,
for spending time with
our meager little club here.
Not at all.
The training of the club's
members is truly eye-opening.
Sakurakoji sure is fantastic, huh?
She's usually so neat and smart,
but when you see her doing aikido,
she really looks cool, huh?
On top of which,
she always earns top grades.
If I could have Sakurakoji as my girlfriend,
I wouldn't care if the
whole world turned against me.
Yoo-hoo! Good morning, Sakura!
A good morning to you, Aoba.
What's the matter, Sakura?
You seem kind of glum.
D-Do I?
Oh, it is no special matter.
All right, then.
Ah, Miss Kanda! Good morning!
Good morning, Takatsu, Sakurakoji.
Huh? Who's this?
Ah, this is a transfer student
who will be in our class starting today.
His name is...
I'm Ogami Rei.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
"Ogami Rei"
Hold the phone!
Ogami's pretty handsome, isn't he?
He has a cool and somewhat
mysterious air about him.
High points!
Okay, okay, quiet down.
For reasons having
to do with his parents' work,
Ogami is moving here by himself.
Everyone, let's all make him
feel welcome, okay?
There is no mistake,
that is him... the boy...
...from last night!
Overseas, huh?
You must have rocking English!
No, not at all.
What countries did you go to?
I was in Europe a lot for the last few years.
What is it, Sakura?
Taking an interest in Ogami?
That is not it...
Ogami!
What is it, Miss Sakurakoji?
I wish to speak to you alone.
Come along with me.
Very well.
Terrible news!
Sakurakoji is gonna declare her love
to the transfer student!
What?!
- No way!
- I don't believe it!
- My dream bride!
Sakura is amazing! How bold!
But those two would make the
perfect couple, wouldn't they?
- So, what did you need?
- I shall ask you point-blank.
Where were you and
what were you doing last night?
I was at my job.
Your job? Then I ask you, using that glove,
are you not concealing the burns you received
last night in the park when
you killed and burned those people?
What was that? I can't hear them!
Well? If I am wrong, then remove the glove.
There are no burns?!
This is a good-luck charm.
When I was a child,
I once hurt someone with this hand.
A certain someone gave me this,
to make sure it never happened again.
Is that all it is?
Yes, that's all it is.
But yesterday...
Anything else?
U-Uh, I apologize for having kept you.
No, it's all right.
I hope we can be friends
going forward, as classmates,
Miss Sakurakoji.
H-Hold on! Sakura, what happened?
Mm-hmm, this is an unexpected development.
Huh?! You don't mean...
...he turned you down?!
He what?! He rejected Sakurakoji?!
Who do you think you are, Ogami Rei?!
It's not possible for
him to cause Sakura grief!
Ogami! You've turned
the whole world against you!
Ah! This is exasperating!
However, I shall not give up!
Whoa... Sakura, this is the first time
you've been so wrapped up in a boy, isn't it?
I swear, I shall uncover the truth about him!
Wow, I have to say, no matter how often I see it,
your way of eating is so charming.
You're not gonna...
Ogami, you're so cool!
You really are infatuated, huh, Sakura?
Yeah. I cannot afford to take my eyes from him.
Mm-hmm. Ogami seems so nice.
It's no surprise that
you'd be interested in him, huh?
Nice?
Hmph, he eluded me, did he?
They say the culprit returns
to the scene of the crime.
I shall wait here for him...
Wait up! Wait up!
Wait up, I say!
Were there truly people burned here?
Was that some phantasm?
Here, eat this. I am sorry
I brought you naught yesterday.
When that old man
gave you food, he would do this...
Are you not ready to
take a liking to me, already?!
O-Ogami!
Sure enough, you talk
like that to everyone, don't you?
It's okay. I was just thinking,
it's the firm tone of a warrior.
What, are you saying it does not fit my image?
No, I was thinking,
it's cool how you're not submissive.
"C-Cool" is too much...
I am just a little...
My family is a bit odd, is all...
Oh, that dog is quite timid around people.
Come here.
The dog...
You just didn't have
enough trust in people, huh?
Whoa! Please, don't lick me so much!
Ogami seems so nice.
I hope we can be friends, as classmates.
Come on! Come on!
He is not a bad chap, is he?
Miss Sakurakoji,
what is this dog's name?
"Dog."
That's... a nice name, huh?
Is she a stray?
No... Her master,
a homeless old man... was killed.
The culprit is a group known as G-Falcon.
They seem to call themselves that
because of the falcon tattoos they
all wear on their bodies.
When this group commits their crimes,
the gang that is over
them keeps everything hushed up.
That is what Father says.
Your father?
Hence no one can bring them to justice.
Even the police pretend to see them not.
Do you want to take
revenge against these culprits?
Would you like to take up justice,
and bring the hammer down on them?
No!
I just... That old man...
He lived without anyone knowing him,
then died without anyone knowing.
It is something I cannot abide.
Miss Sakurakoji,
you can always remember him.
Even if the rest of the world forgets him,
you can remember him.
I will not forget. No matter what, not ever.
Besides,
you don't need the laws
of this country to judge them.
An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth; evil for evil.
The Code of Hammurabi?
The "evil for evil"
part is gratuitous, Ogami.
You finally smiled for me, huh?
I thought maybe you had taken a disliking to me.
I apologize for that, Ogami.
I had my doubts about you.
What has become of Ogami Rei?
His placement is complete.
All that remains is for
him to begin, Prime Minister.
Mm-hmm, good. All according to plan.
Assuming it wasn't Ogami,
then what exactly was it?
Was it a phantasm, after all?
Ogami, want to come
with us for some karaoke?
Sakura is coming, too.
No, I have something to take care of.
Hey, who do you think I'm doing this for?
Huh?
Don't "huh" me!
I'm sorry, but I have to work today.
Oh, you do?
Ogami, now that you mention it,
what work do you do?
I'm a cleaner. A trash man.
I see. Most admirable.
You see? It looks like
they're already calling me.
Hey, what is this?!
All of a sudden, you're on close terms?!
There is nothing especially
irregular about our contact, is there?
No way, no way,
that's a hyper-fast connection!
What is it?
It's about today's job.
Take out the trash, just as was planned.
What are you going to
do about Sakurakoji Sakura?
I'm not going to do much of anything.
Just like I was always going to,
I'm going to eliminate her.
When will you finally take a liking to me?!
Good grief...
Help me!
W-What is it?
Like I said, we haven't
been able to reach our pals
since two nights ago.
You guys hang out here, right?
I'm asking you if you've seen anything.
I-I don't know anything, really!
Ah, you're useless!
H-Help!
Stop that!
I have just dialed 110!
The police will arrive here shortly!
The police? Oh, right, the police!
Falcon tattoos... Then they're...
G-Falcon! The group
that killed that old man!
Young lady, you shouldn't go
sticking your nose into everything.
We're just concerned about
some of our pals that vanished here.
They vanished... here...
Huh? What is it, young lady?
You know something about it?
Was it two nights ago that
you say your pals vanished?
- Hey!
- Is she in on it?
Sounds like you really
do know something. Hey...
Now then, why don't you
tell me everything you know?
Two nights ago... they vanished...
Then it did happen.
What are you mumbling to yourself about?
Tell us what you know, now...
Now that I know it
really happened, that will do.
I have nothing more to say to you!
Why, you little!
Ow-w-w-w!
Turn yourselves in to the police...
If you won't answer us,
then we'll just have
to beat it out of you directly.
M-My body won't move!
Here, take this belt! Tie her up!
Stupid girl. You could
have left the homeless guy alone,
but you tried to help him,
and this is what you get!
What the hell is this?!
Dog!
Knock it off!
You're not getting me!
Ha! It's dog soccer!
Stop that!
- I'm open! I'm open!
- Here, I'm passing!
Nice! Nice!
Way to go!
Hey, hold it!
Stop, already!
She has nothing to do with this!
You will face me!
What's she talking about?
Is this any time to
be worrying about a dog?
Just you wait! I will get
you to a hospital right away...
Pesky girl.
If you wanna get pummeled that badly,
then you'll have your wish.
All you want, after you answer us.
Are you in pain?
Who are you?!
Ogami!
Your organs, and many of your bones...
There's no saving you, huh?
It's amazing that you're still alive at all.
You wanted to protect
Miss Sakurakoji, didn't you?
You did well.
What the hell do you want?!
Ogami! Hurry and get her to a hospital!
Ogami, please!
I will put you out of your misery now.
Ogami?
Ogami... You!
What? You killed it, did you?
That's no fun.
If you kill it, it won't respond,
and where's the fun in...
An eye for an eye; a tooth for a tooth...
and evil for evil.
Huh? What are you talking...
Burn away.
It's started, has it?
I'm waiting for you, Ogami.
W-What the hell did you do?!
What? My job as a trash man.
I'll ask you one final question.
Will you turn yourselves in to be judged,
or would you rather die here?
Which will it be?
Screw you! You're the one who's gonna die!
I see. Well then, die here.
An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth; evil for evil.
Ogami... Then it really was you!
It was as classmates that
I said I hoped we could be friends.
Burn away.
One day, you, too, will know
where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city,
unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following
wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from
which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear; the answers
lie beyond the darkness
Next time, "Code: Breaker" episode 2,
"The Spiral Blue Flower, Blossoming in Flame."
I will burn everything up,
until the end of my life!