You're here, Code: Breaker.
What happened to Heike?
I kicked that traitor's ass.
But never mind him, you're
sure looking good, Prime Minister.
You're a disgrace.
That's so unkind of you, Toki.
Now that you know, please
come and untie these ropes.
It's not as though I'm
here because I want to be.
What's the matter?
What if I were to choose
the option of forsaking you?
What did you say?
"Remaining time until Prime Minister
Fujiwara's public execution"
Why is there no final
piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence
facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
I'm not letting you have
the children with special abilities!
You want me to let these children
live their whole lives in a cage?
Your former leader, Hitomi,
wants to avoid having them do so.
For me to leave here together with you
would mean being pursued
for the rest of my life! As a criminal!
Hitomi said that if it meant
being kept as a dog of the state,
they would be better off
surviving out in the wilderness.
They won't become dogs!
We will not let that happen!
Are you saying you're forsaking Hitomi?
You're just...
You're just with Hitomi
under a temporary contract!
What would you know?!
We'll save the children
with special abilities.
And we'll save Hitomi, too!
We're not going to forsake anyone!
"Episode 12: 'Devils... God
and Man... Sakura Watching Over'"
Why are you trying so hard, Ogami?
Stop the bombs, Hitomi!
I can't do that.
It doesn't matter what I want,
they detonate when their time comes.
That's the way they are set up.
Hitomi!
Now, let's watch on together for
the moment when the world changes.
The moment when
the people are terrorized,
and yearn for those
of us with special abilities.
There is no longer any need
for anyone to face death in solitude.
A world where we can live
out under the sun is on its way.
Stop that, Hitomi!
My, what an adorable little renegade.
Puppy!
Ogami, you have a seat and watch, too!
Ogami!
Hitomi!
You still want to go at it?
Why are you getting up?
I told you, there's
no stopping the bombs now.
Hitomi!
Bombs? Sending all
those people to their deaths?
Is that you?! Is that
Code: Breaker, Code 01, Hitomi?!
Is that the Hitomi I know?!
Ogami!
Code: Breaker, huh?
What nonsense.
Ogami, you've realized, haven't you,
that all of the killing that Eden orders
ends up serving to give the state
and Eden the upper hand, right?
That bunch of gangsters that you burned up...
they were only targeted
because they were helping me out.
There are many other
groups of gangsters out there
who do terrible things, as well.
The same with Tabata.
He was killed because he
was providing me with information.
The same is true of G-Falcon.
They were chosen to be an
example to warn off other gangsters.
Eden ignores all sorts of evil,
and only chooses to label as evil
those who are inconvenient to them.
They then use Code: Breakers
to do their killing for them,
so they can keep their hands clean.
Do you take pride in that?
In being Code: Breakers,
who are kept by Eden?
Ogami isn't...
I don't want to die!
Live for all you're worth!
Ogami isn't...
Even if he is a Devilfiend,
he's still my papa.
Fireballman, you dummy!
Come after me to kill me.
Chisa, I'm sorry.
Burn away.
Ogami isn't...
Ogami...
Let's fight together.
Ogami, let's bring justice to a world
of those with special abilities, together.
Once again...
...together...
I get it. Eden is evil.
But Hitomi, you're also killing,
and assigning reasons
that are convenient to you.
You have killed innocent people.
You declared that
they're unworthy of protection,
and then killed many of those
people to achieve your own goal!
You are evil. And I am also
an evil, who has killed much evil.
Ogami...
Since we're both evil,
then I will fight until my last
moment to protect those people!
I would want to be someone
who would save others
until the very last moment.
I will not fight together with you!
I am a Code: Breaker!
That's too bad, Ogami.
At least let me be
the one to send you off.
Ogami!
That won't do any good.
Hitomi!
Ogami!
What's the matter, Ogami?
Can't you use your flames anymore?
Ogami!
You've gone Lost, huh, Ogami?
Lost?!
Does it hurt, Ogami?
O-Ogami!
The pain of those with
special abilities... Our destiny...
And yet, Eden doesn't...
Ogami!
No, wait, Hitomi!
I won't let you kill Ogami!
You really are a good girl.
You were raised by good parents.
Boss, is that really where the guys
who are sending
out the bomb signals are?
The bombs are where
they're marked on the map.
There's no doubt about it.
That's them, right?
There's no time! Hurry!
What are children doing here?
Can we really do it?
Hitomi said not to get involved with anyone,
but this is for the sake of
everyone with special abilities.
Hey there, boys!
What are you doing here?
It's dangerous here, so why don't you...
Stay back!
Daisuke!
They have the same kind of
powers as Ogami and the others!
Don't do this.
Don't do this anymore!
Don't do this anymore, Hitomi!
Are you going to defend Ogami by yourself?
Miss Sakurakoji...
I think your straightforward
feelings are fantastic.
But even so...
It takes more than
that to change the world!
If you interfere, I'll show no mercy.
Special abilities don't work
on you, so I'll have to do this.
Hitomi!
Ogami,
you don't have the strength
right now to save this girl.
You're powerless.
Hitomi!
The moment of the blast is getting near.
Hurry up and
save me, Code: Breaker.
Are you planning on watching me die?
I'll wait until after the Prime Minister's death,
as well as the slaughter
of the other 50,000,
before I kill this girl.
I've watched a lot
of Code: Breakers die.
You will experience it, too...
the sense of helplessness you
get from being unable to protect them.
Hitomi... Don't... Don't...
blow them up... This isn't...
Now, an age when those of
us with special abilities
can live out under
the sun is about to begin!
We can escape our destiny to die
without anyone knowing who we are.
Our days of solitude are ending!
This is our victory!
It was stopped, huh?
Is it over?
I'm not sure.
Are you all right?
Mm-hmm.
More or less.
What is going on?
I took some measures of my own.
Heike?!
Uh-oh...
It's over, Number two.
Under my direction,
I had Yuki go to work.
You won't have the children
with special abilities, either.
Almost there...
The explosions aren't happening.
Has the mission failed?
Hold it!
Under Heike's instructions,
we had the children
moved to another location.
Is that why you were buying time?
I pretended to have
been killed to fool Hitomi,
and put a halt to his plans.
Heike headed up the whole thing.
And so...
Oh, it's you, snow boy.
Are you still around?
Watch yourself, Yuki!
He ran away?
I see, so it was you after all, Heike.
You knew the reasons
why I set up this operation.
It was to save those
of us with special abilities.
It is over, Ace.
Heike!
Ace! If you use that much of
your special ability, you'll go Lost.
Please, don't use up too much power.
There are still some
things I need to have you do.
I... am not going Lost!
What did you just say, Ace?
Ace?
Do you think you've won, Heike?
You cannot make the bombs across
the country detonate any longer.
Toki is rescuing the Prime Minister.
Your plans have been ruined.
I asked you if you thought you've won.
Why do you think I chose
Sky Tower as the final location?
Here?
Even if you'd caught wind of where I was,
there's still one last measure in place,
to ensure that my plan does not fail.
That's right! Using my special ability,
I will emit my electrical waves from Sky Tower,
and detonate all of
the bombs across the country!
This is my final battle!
Do not do it, Ace!
I would like to have
avoided using this means,
if at all possible, Heike.
You don't mean... you're...
It's over!
Scared you good,
there, huh, Prime Minister?
You gave me quite a start.
Still, it looks like you
managed to prevent the blast.
Good work, good work.
Now, hurry and untie me.
What's wrong?
Right now, his fate is in my hands.
If I kill him, Sissy will be set free.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up and untie my ropes.
Toki, what are you trying to pull?!
I busted the camera.
The only one watching right now is me.
No one will know the truth
about what happens to you now.
S-Stop, Toki!
I-If I fall, I'll die! Stop it, Toki!
Please, Toki! Whoa... whoa...
I'm going to fall! I'm going to fall!
Listen to you panic! How disgraceful!
I'm going to fall!
Every once in a while, you need
to be put in your place like this.
Well, Toki? Do you feel relieved now?
I should get an award
for that performance, right?
Still, you had your chance,
and you didn't take it.
You're just a kept dog after all.
While you may have been able
to take advantage of
the bombing to forsake me,
you were too scared to do it yourself, huh?
You really are hopeless.
I guess I should have used
Nenene as the Code: Breaker, after all.
Why, you despicable father!
I'm going shopping with Papa!
Yes, that will do. Unless you
want to make Nenene into a killer,
you will obey me.
That was our agreement, wasn't it,
Code: Breaker, Code 04, Toki?
The fun is just getting started.
Back the hell up!
Something else you need?
I can kill you at any time.
But I'm not going to!
Hmph, you don't have the guts to kill me.
It's to keep me from becoming like you!
What?
I won't let being a Code: Breaker...
I won't use it for my own desires,
and become the same as you!
What nonsense.
What?
You can't, Ace!
You cannot do this, Hitomi!
With this...
What?!
That's enough, Hitomi!
Oji! Then you're all right!
And Yuki! Blasting me up here,
bike and all?! You're crazy!
What choice was there? It was
the only way to get here in time.
Yuki!
Hitomi, we won't let you go any farther.
If you interfere with me,
then I'll take you out first!
Number five!
Knock it off already, Number one!
Why have you changed so much?!
Where did the old Number one go?!
Ace!
Hitomi!
You are not anyone who
would do something like this! Why?!
What happened to you?!
Tell us, Number one!
You don't understand anything, do you?
Working together, as friends
helping each other was wonderful.
I miss those days.
Once, I was inside that circle, as well.
But as long as Eden is in
charge of the Code: Breakers,
and everyone else with special abilities,
our fate to die like dogs as
their pawns will never change.
Eden is just using our feelings
of sympathy toward our friends!
Why can't you see that your
actions are slamming the door
on the future of those
of us with special abilities?
Even if we are, there's no way
you can drag innocent people into this!
They're not innocent.
The people who I once
fought to protect are culpable.
They do not know that we have
been risking our lives for their peace!
They don't know how many
Code: Breakers have died.
They just enjoy their peace in ignorance.
They keep on living their
lives of peace and security!
They don't even realize
that they're being protected!
If that isn't a crime, then what is?!
It's too late now! From the day
that Eden started chasing me,
the world has changed!
Hitomi! I have been
watching how you fought!
How you've protected so many people!
I remember how you helped them all!
No you don't. That's something
you don't get to do, Hitomi.
That is not something you get to do.
Do not do it! Hitomi!
No more!
You interfere, right up to the end!
Don't do it, Hitomi!
Even if it means eradicating
the people of this country
who have indulged themselves in peace,
I will liberate those
who have special abilities!
An eye for an eye...
A tooth for a tooth...
Evil for evil...
You've... changed...
Hitomi.
It's over.
What?!
What the?
Hitomi...
You're steeped entirely in evil.
I'm gonna burn you out.
Outstanding! Such... power!
One day, you, too, will know
where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city,
unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following
wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from
which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear; the answers
lie beyond the darkness
Toki... Yuki... Oji... Heike... Hitomi...
Next time, "Code: Breaker" episode 13,
"A Flower Blooming With God."
Farewell, Ogami.