Why is there no final
piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence
facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
"Episode 9: 'Stopped Time'"
"Maximum Clearance 2.5m"
Explosions? What's going on?
I don't know any details yet.
Just that some powerful explosives
were used in several
locations within the city.
Master...
What?
It has to be Hitomi...
Kanda...
Yes?
I will stop Hitomi. Got it?
Yes.
He abducts the Prime Minister,
and now, terrorist bombings...
Hitomi...
Currently, the confirmed
casualty count alone
from these bombings is twelve dead,
Bombings within the city leave many dead
twenty-four seriously injured,
with four people reported missing.
The explosions took place
during the evening rush hour,
and it is anticipated
that the toll in human lives
will continue to rise hereafter.
Yes. "Toll."
I-It's terrible what is happening, is it not?!
More worried about others
than yourself. That's just like you.
You look like you're enjoying yourselves.
What are you talking about?
We were discussing
Miss Sakurakoji's character.
I have to admit,
I didn't think you'd actually bring her here.
My role is to cater to whatever you seek, Ace.
That's how it has always been, right?
You've been under
guard for a long time, you know.
Under guard?
First, there was Heike,
then, more recently, Ogami was
transferred to that school
to keep you guarded.
Ogami was?!
But then, Ogami didn't
seem to be aware of that.
Isn't that right, Prime Minister?
All of it done to try to thwart my plans.
You were awfully well-prepared,
but I still prevailed.
Plans? What do you mean?
What do you plan to do with me?
I won't be doing anything.
You're a rarebreed, after all.
I just wanted to keep you secured here,
since you'd be a
problem if you got in the way.
All you have to do
is sit back and watch,
without interfering with my plans.
Plans?
"Casualties continue to
rise after series of explosions"
You don't mean these explosions!
That's right.
Why would you do something like this?!
If I said it was to save the
Code: Breakers, would you believe me?
I'm sure you must have some reason.
I know your level of
kindness better than anyone.
Hitomi...
Received 1 new message
Subj: Hitomi's location
From: Adam's friend
Master, it's Kanda. I got a text
from an unknown sender
that shows Hitomi's
current location, and...
You got it, too?
Incidentally, Ace, the bombs
that were set around the city
aren't the end of this, are they?
The real plan is just getting started, right?
How obnoxious.
Sounds like you've been
sniffing around, huh, Heike?
You make it sound so sordid. I was...
Heike...
...it's not as though
I trust you 100 percent.
Oh?
What kind of tricks did you
pull to find this hideout so easily?
Perhaps you've been keeping an
eye on me since before this began.
My information network
had this location marked out.
You've just reached the end of your rope.
That is alarming.
But I have figured out
what your true intention is.
I'd hate to have you be
caught by Eden. I want to help you.
Which is precisely why
I abducted Miss Sakurakoji,
and reduced Hachoji Rui
to a bloody mess.
Oji?!
You, who cares more than
anyone for the Code: Breakers,
took out Oji? Why is that?
Because I understand your anger
and grief more than anyone else.
Why would you hurt Oji?!
You'll pay for this!
You do not know the feelings
of someone who does not exist!
Ace, I don't blame you
for not believing me. However...
Do as you please. But, if you try
anything funny, I'll kill you.
I will endeavor to
live up to your expectations.
Ho, they're here.
If Kanda is here now, that
means that Ogami will be along soon.
Sure enough, a conflict is unavoidable.
I know this is sudden, but Heike,
would you do a job for me?
Hitomi is in there.
I will stop Hitomi. Got it?
I'm sorry, Master.
Heike?!
What are you doing here?
I've always wanted to tie you up.
"Emergency report"
"Series of bombings"
What did you say?
Ogami, isn't Sakura with you?
She hasn't come home yet.
She's not answering her cell, either.
Could something have happened to her?
All right. I think I know where to look.
I'll contact you if I find anything.
Number six!
Number two has turned on us!
Well, well...
And Yuki, as well.
What did you do to Number five?!
Why, whatever do you mean?
Don't play dumb! I saw the whole thing!
You attacked Number five!
I see.
That was careless of me.
What's the meaning of this, Heike?
What do you think?
This is what it means!
Then you really have
turned on us, huh, Number two?!
It can be a pain how the
sound special ability is invisible,
but if you can get a handle
on its straight-line movement,
it is not difficult to avoid.
Gah, you're pissing me off!
Stop running away!
Well of course I'm going to evade them.
Ho!
Huh?
No mercy, I see, Ogami.
Those who stand in my
way don't require any mercy!
Are you going to stick to that policy?
What?
Number six! Watch out!
Just keep heading on up, Number six.
I'll take care of Number two.
Indeed. Then I will dispose of you, first.
Kanda, wasn't Hitomi here?
Don't tell me Hitomi got you...
Absolutely right.
Hitomi!
Miss Sakurakoji!
Ogami! Miss Kanda is being controlled!
You must help her!
Sure enough, you send out
electrical commands to her brain,
and control her with them, don't you?
It's not hard at all. Much easier
than controlling a dead body.
Hitomi...
Master...
I'm sorry, Master... Hitomi has me...
No!
Master, please get away.
Master...
Ogami!
How many more rounds?
I will take all the bullets you have.
Hurry up and empty the clip.
Amazing, Ogami.
But even so, I think I'm going
to take you out of the picture here.
I have given instructions to Kanda
that her final shot is
to go through her own head.
What will you do? If you avoid
her shots, Kanda will keep shooting,
and with the last bullet,
she will commit suicide.
But, if you take a bullet, and die,
my control over Kanda will end right there.
Kanda will not have to die.
Hitomi...
Master...
Can you look on as Kanda kills herself?
You coward!
This is beyond dastardly, Hitomi!
What a kindhearted girl you are.
Hitomi, you used to be friends
with Miss Kanda and Ogami!
How could you do something this mean?!
Don't let him get away with this, Ogami!
I won't allow you to commit suicide.
I will end this, by my hand!
Ogami... you don't mean!
Striking back and eliminating an
enemy who threatens you
without any hesitation.
You haven't changed, Ogami.
But, can you really do it?
Master... I'm so sorry!
Ogami, wait! Don't do it, Ogami!
Do not kill her!
What the?
Miss Sakurakoji!
Huh? What on earth happened?
Hmm? You loosened the ropes?
Am I?
Miss Kanda!
Miss Sakurakoji?
Thank goodness! You are back to normal!
Good.
Your desperate wish broke
you free of Hitomi's special ability!
That's a rarebreed for you.
Sure enough, you seem
likely to interfere in all sort of ways.
Now you intend to take Puppy hostage?!
Hitomi, what are you scheming?
Why are you doing this?
The old you was not someone who
would do this sort of thing.
Why?
Do you still not know,
even after looking at the clocks in this room?
Now that you mention it, this room...
...has nothing but stopped clocks.
These are the times of the
Code: Breakers' deaths.
6:23... the former Code 03
dies while on escort duty.
22:47... the former Code 06
dies in a sudden accident
while passing judgment on evil.
Those who do not exist do not
even get headstones erected to them,
so it's the least I could do.
They all died judging evil
that the law could not judge...
without anyone knowing about it.
Hitomi...
This kind of thing...
has to be brought to an end.
He's doing this for his
friends that have died, all by himself?
The one who gave them
their orders was the Prime Minister.
For this, he must pay.
I will have the Prime Minister
accept the consequences with his death.
N-No, you can't go killing the Prime Minister!
Nothing will come of
you doing something like that!
Oh, something will come of it.
The Prime Minister will die
while performing in his supreme role.
His supreme role?
There was an explosion,
just now! The smoke is tremendous!
- Many people are down. It's terrible...
- Many people will die before
the Prime Minister's execution.
- Many people are down. It's terrible...
- Many people will die before
the Prime Minister's execution.
- the situation is terrible!
The citizenry must be in terror.
And then finally comes the main event.
The Prime Minister, along with
even more people across Japan,
will lose their lives.
How could you?!
Screw you!
For what reason are you doing this?
Killing people who are without any guilt?
To leave this memory.
To ingrain terror within the memories
of the people of this country.
The reality that many people are being executed
together with Prime Minister Fujiwara.
They should learn their lesson.
Those who live in a world
of fabricated, temporary peace...
It's a temporary, fabricated peace.
Someone help!
My child! Somebody!
People who bask
in peace will tremble in fear,
then, from the bottom of their hearts,
they will want someone to kill
whomever brought about
this kind of atrocity for them.
An absolute "someone,"
who will eliminate evil,
no matter the means.
Yes, the Code: Breakers!
By doing so, the Code: Breakers
will no longer have to die
without anyone knowing about them.
This is for the Code: Breakers...
- But!
- So when all of this is over,
you'll come forward as
a Code: Breaker of Justice,
and judge evil, out in the open?
That's right.
It's true, I'm not comfortable
being a kept dog of Eden.
Ogami...
I wouldn't mind moving out in the open.
By creating this much of a stink,
Eden might think so, as well.
Why don't you join me, Ogami?
But do not forget...
Code: Breakers who
judge evil are still killers!
There is no need to reward that!
Why don't you get it, Ogami?
You're the one who doesn't get it.
You killed people who are
innocent to bring about this incident.
You! The one who most
hated when innocent people died!
Is that the best you've got, Yuki?
What a spoilsport.
I'm just getting warmed up!
Then again, I've gotta
hand it to Number two.
You haven't changed, Ogami.
But there's no turning back now.
Now is the time for
Code: Breakers to start to exist!
No longer as those who die
in solitude, unknown to everyone!
Everyone can be who they wish to be!
With this sacrifice of the citizenry's terror,
I liberate the Code: Breakers from Eden!
Hitomi!
Ogami!
Yukihina?!
Here I was wondering what
was taking you so long to come out.
What are you doing, Hitomi?
You could have just
gone on ahead without me.
This is no time for you
to be wrapped up in this, is it?
All right, Yukihina.
Ogami!
You cannot melt my ice with your flames.
All right, Yukihina, I'm going on ahead.
Hitomi!
Wait, Hitomi!
Miss Sakurakoji!
It's over.
What are you doing, Ogami?
Putting Sakura in danger, are you?
Toki!
Hi, Sakura! The star has arrived.
After all, the hero has to come in late, right?
Ah! Hold it! Give back the Prime Minister!
Let me tell you right now,
there are bombs in this building, too.
Getting out immediately
would be good for your health.
What?!
Wait! Give his papa,
the Prime Minster, back!
Y-You idiot!
It's too dangerous, Sakura!
This is not good.
Yuki, the fight is on hold!
Wha...?
Hey!
Number two!
Wow. Who would have thought
you'd come along with us?
I won't let you kill the Prime Minister!
Nor shall I allow you to kill anyone else!
Why is he doing this?
Exactly what took place in the past?
One day, you, too, will know
where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city,
unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following
wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from
which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear; the answers
lie beyond the darkness
That day, the night the city was choked
with the smell of death and gun smoke,
is when I first met you.
Next time,
"Code: Breaker" episode 10,
"The World People See."