Why is there no final
piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence
facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
"Fireballman vs. the Devilfiend"
Fireballman,
I'm going to get strong like you,
and be a hero of justice, like you are.
"Episode 5: 'Banquet of Wishes'"
Impressive. However...
You guys are now...
What?!
Tch, this is useless!
Hey, what are you
running away for?! Hold up!
You will be of service to me.
Mr. Tabata, the Code: Breakers
have infiltrated the building.
I don't care if they're the devil;
I won't let them interfere.
I have to wonder, why are they
doing research on these so-called
"special abilities" in a government facility?
Especially since Code: Breakers
are a government agency.
They're what?!
Ogami and I both operate
under orders from the Prime Minister.
Wha...? The Prime Minister?
That's right. So even in the
form of politicians or policemen,
evil can never escape from us.
Who are these children?
They're probably kids
who possess special abilities.
Gathered here from all over Japan,
and researched in all sorts of ways.
Just what exactly is
the government trying to do?
Who can say? But they are in
protective care, so no foul, right?
What's wrong?
Oh, it's those two large men earlier.
I was wondering why
their power ran out while fighting.
You don't think they went Lost?
You mentioned that before,
too. What is "Lost"?
Oh, Lost is when...
What is it?
Puppy!
It's almost like a hospital in here.
Well, just like in the report.
For a hospital, this is...
Well, well, Code: Breakers...
I welcome you.
You'd be Tabata, right?
Carrying on special ability research?
Those muscle-bound idiots were
the results of your research, right?
They're still no equal
for a genuine Code: Breaker.
This is Diet member Tabata Shigeru.
I'm sure you've at
least heard his name before.
He's the one in charge of this research.
Then the government really is...
The real matter is still to come.
How awful!
Uh-oh, the organs are missing.
Mr. Tabata, Eden is furious
about your unauthorized killing.
You weren't told to
traffic in their organs, right?
Why would you do such a thing?
That's none of your business.
How rude, referring to us as "such a thing."
What we're doing is helping people.
Those kids whose special powers are low
are useless, and good for nothing.
And as such, you see...
Making use of their organs,
at least, is for the greater good.
You can't be serious!
There's no way something like
this can be permitted!
My, such a spirited little girl.
Maybe we ought to take her apart.
Indeed...
...if they're no use, then who needs them?
Oh, you get it, don't you?
Are you of any use to me?
What?
If you're of no use, then who needs you?
However, I don't need your organs, either.
You don't have to be for the greater good.
Just burn away.
Take this!
He vaporized it?!
Ogami!
Sakura, keep back!
Take this!
Aww, so close! I even turned it to stone!
Watch it, will you!
We're not here for you guys anyhow!
Now that you've seen this,
we can't let you leave here alive!
Tch, that's a problem.
Your organs are all mine!
How embarrassing, for a
Code: Breaker to have to run away!
Damn, that's one pesky ability he's got.
Toki, there's something weird about him.
Why is he carrying that
heavy-looking thing around on his back?
That's a Code: Breaker for you, all right.
What are you waiting for?
Come on and turn up the power!
You know what becomes of useless children, right!
A sneak attack?!
Aren't you the coward, Code: Breaker!
Cheap shots, huh? How nasty!
Hmph, sure enough, there's some gimmick
to those things they're carrying around.
In that case, I'll just destroy it directly!
What?!
Gotcha!
Surprised? This is made from carbon fiber.
You can't destroy it
with your special ability, huh?
Tch, you really are a pest.
Coming from behind?
You really are a nasty boy!
Come on and make with the power!
Or I'll do to you what I did to your brother!
- Your brother?
- Don't take your eyes off of me!
You're through.
A child?
Power's used up, huh?
You really are useless, kid!
So that's how it is.
My word, little kids are hopeless!
Their power is all used up so quickly!
You truly are a waste!
Snap out of it! Are you all right?!
Kill... them...
They... cut up Brother... my brother...
...because their powers are weak...
I heard a voice... my little sister's voice...
...saying "Help me"...
But then I stopped hearing her...
I stopped hearing my sister's voice...
Kill... them... Get back for my brother...
Kill them... please! Kill the ones who...
...killed my sister!
Damn! How the...
Stop it!
How can this be?
An eye for an eye; a tooth for a tooth;
the hammer of justice for evil.
Thank you...
Brother...
Hey! Hey! No! Wake up!
Hey!
Why did this happen?
No!!
No! No! No!
No! Don't!
Burn away.
Thank you...
There's no need to thank me.
I'm just evil that kills off other evil.
It's not as though
it will take away your grief,
nor will the dead be brought back to life.
Even so... thank you...
Damn it! Damn it!
Lousy hypocrites!
S-Stay away!
Ogami!
No, Sakura.
But it's not right for
him to kill any more people!
Sakura, have you ever wondered
why heroes are able to be heroes?
What?
Heroes are heroes because
they kill those who are evil
for the sake of justice.
Besides, Sakura, your words won't
reach him while you're of two minds.
I'm not of two minds!
They cut up Brother.
Kill... them...
Thank you...
You don't know anything! Not you!
You don't know my pain!
Papa?
Papa, what's the matter?
Who are those people?
Chisa!
Tabata's daughter?
Chisa, that young man
is a hero of justice.
Really? Mister, are you Fireballman?
You really did come!
Papa told me that Fireballman
would come for my sickness,
and trade the bad part of
my tummy for something good.
Thank you for coming, Fireballman!
Once I'm all better, I'm gonna
be a hero like you, Fireballman!
You mean, Tabata was doing all this to find
a suitable donor organ for his own daughter?
You counted yourself lucky to be ordered
to oversee this special ability research,
since you could find a
matching organ for your daughter.
Even so, Mr. Tabata, though what you want
may be right before
your eyes, it's still wrong.
Shut up!
Chisa needs the organ!
How can she wait year
after year for a donor to show up?!
You'd kill other children
in your daughter's place?
How self-serving.
Shut up! Shut up! You have
no right talking to me about it!
You're killers, too, aren't you!
You use your special powers
to go on your killing sprees!
That's right! Those children
are just those who will end up
going around killing
people as the state's dogs!
So then, isn't it far better to
use their organs, to save people?!
What's wrong with sacrificing
dogs so that Chisa can survive?!
I want to save Chisa. Chisa is all I have!
For my daughter's sake, I would...
Even if it is for your daughter's sake,
it doesn't change the
fact that you are a murderer.
Don't you have any heart at all?!
Burn away.
Enough, already...
That boy had his brother killed,
and suffered so much,
he wished death on someone...
I don't care if you were
doing it for your daughter's sake,
walking all over others,
and sacrificing them...
You can just... You can just!
You can just... You can just...
Kill him...
You can just!
You can just...
That boy was warm.
His heart was beating, thumpity-thump.
But he quickly grew cold,
and his heart also went weak.
That's what it is for a life to vanish.
You are warm, too.
You are warm, just like that boy was.
You're alive, and there's no
reason why you should be dead.
There's no reason to kill you!
Papa...
So, Ogami, don't kill him!
Even a guy like this is alive.
Don't kill him!
You're right...
No matter what the reasons were,
I should not have killed them.
Look after my daughter.
There you are, Fireballman!
You have to face the Devilfiend!
I made lots of people suffer,
and killed them! Is that wrong?!
You stay out of my way!
- T-Tabata?!
- Papa, what are you...
Ch-Chisa, I'm sorry.
I killed for the sake of my own desires,
and turned into a Devilfiend.
Papa, that's not true!
Mister Fireballman here
has come to put me down.
Now, die! Fireballman!
No, Ogami!
Burn away.
Ch-Chisa...
Tabata...
Fireballman, you dummy!
Chisa!
How dare you hurt Papa!
Even if he is a Devilfiend,
he's still my papa.
I hate you, Fireballman! Die! Die!!
Ogami!
Die...
Are you resentful? If you're
resentful, then live through this,
then come after me to
kill me. I'll remember you.
There's no way I'll ever forget you.
Chisa!
She's just passed out.
She overexerted herself,
being sick and all.
I'll contact the medical team.
She'll be fine.
O-Okay.
Ogami... You said that on
purpose, to make her hate you.
Did you think that by hating you,
you'd become her purpose for living?
Your methods are problematic,
but Ogami, that was the act of a hero.
You call yourself evil, but...
I am evil.
No matter how evil those I face may be,
once I kill them,
I am no longer a hero of justice.
Yes, Tabata has been terminated.
Yeah, it's all right.
The research data is in its usual...
I wonder, who you could be funneling
the special ability children's research data to,
Mr. Tsuno. The secretary?
A Code: Breaker!
It sounds like the mastermind
is on the other end of that phone.
You want to give me your cell phone?
Please help me!
There's a Code: Breaker here!
Thank you for carrying out your duty.
Oh, no...
Don't tell me... he set me up, too!
No! I don't want to die!
What's this?
Mr. Tsuno committed suicide.
Is this your doing?
Hey, Toki. It's been too long.
I knew it. Code 0 is...
...you, Hitomi.
I look forward to seeing you, Toki. Later.
Prime Minister,
the unit has secured the children.
They are being moved to Laboratory 4.
Very well. Good work.
Well, well, letting Tabata
head up the special ability research
was a mistake.
Imagine, him resorting to what
he did for his daughter's sake...
It's utterly unfathomable, huh?
Those with special abilities
are not to be used idly.
Is your master also interested
in those special ability children?
One day, you, too, will know
where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city,
unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following
wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from
which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear; the answers
lie beyond the darkness
If something is going
to just disappear in time,
it's better that it
never was from the start.
Next time,
"Code: Breaker" episode 6, "Lost One."
Such is our destiny.