So you've come, Code:Breaker.
What happened to Heiki?
I kicked that traitor's ass.
Putting that aside, that's quite a state you're in, Prime Minister.
It's really unsightly.
You're so mean, Toki.
If you get the picture, then hurry up and untie me.
It's not like I'm stuck here because I want to.
What's wrong?
I'm actually thinking of leaving you like this.
What did you say?
Until Prime Minister Fujiwara's Public Execution
Why is there no final piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
I won't let you bastards have the children with special abilities!
So you'd rather have them live their whole lives, imprisoned in cages?
Your former leader wanted to avoid just that, you see.
If they leave here with you, they will be hunted
for the rest of their lives,
as criminals!
Hitomi once said,
rather than being brought up as a government dog,
they would be happier surviving out in the wild.
They won't become dogs!
We won't let them!
You mean you'll forsake Hitomi?
You're just...
You're just with Hitomi under a temporary contract.
What would you understand?!
We'll save these children.
And we'll save Hitomi as well!
No one will be forsaken!
Mao, God and Human, And
Sakura Who Watches over Them
Episode 11
Why are you trying so hard, Ogami-kun?
Stop the explosions, Hitomi!
I can't do that.
Regardless of my desires, they will explode when the time comes.
That's how they've been set up.
Hitomi-senpai-dono!
Now, let's watch the moment the world changes with our own eyes.
The moment when people are terrified and will seek those of us with special abilities.
No one will have to wait for death in solitude anymore.
A world where we can live out in the light of the sun, is slowly emerging.
Stop it, Hitomi-senpai-dono!
My, such a cute little rebel.
Puppy!
You should also have a seat, Ogami-kun!
Ogami!
Hitomi!
Do you still want more?
Hitomi...
Why are you getting up?
Didn't I tell you? The bombs can't be stopped.
Hitomi!
Bombs, you say?
Put all those people to death?
Is that you, is that really Code:Breaker Code: 01,
Hitomi?!
Is that the Hitomi I know?!
Ogami!
Code:Breaker? Rubbish.
Ogami-kun, I'm sure you've noticed.
In the end, the murders that Eden ordered...
are those which will become profitable to either Eden or the government.
The gangsters that you burned to ashes caught Eden's attention,
because they had lent me a hand.
Even though there are so many other gangsters doing awful things out there.
The same goes for Tabata.
He was killed because he provided me with information.
The G-Falcon thugs are no exception.
They were made an example of to warn other gangsters.
Ignoring the masses of evil
and only targeting those who are a nuisance to Eden.
And then they use the Code:Breakers to kill, thus keeping their own hands clean.
Are you proud of this?
To be a Code:Breaker, kept by Eden?
Ogami is...
I don't want to die!
Live through to the bitter end.
Ogami is...
Even if he's the Devil Man, he's still my daddy!
Stupid Fireball Man!
Come and kill me.
Chisa, I'm sorry.
Burn to ashes.
Ogami is...!
Ogami-kun, let's fight together!
Let's fight together.
Ogami-kun, let's fight together for justice in the world of special ability users.
Once again, together.
I know. Eden is evil.
But Hitomi,
making convenient excuses to kill people
is exactly what you're doing as well!
You've killed innocent people.
You keep saying things like "they didn't deserve to be protected",
and killed a lot of people to fulfill your own purposes!
You are evil.
I'm also evil, but I've killed a lot of evil people to make up for it!
Ogami...
We are both evil, but I'll fight to protect people, until my last breath.
This is the kind of spirit I need on my side.
I will not fight alongside you.
I am a Code:Breaker!
That's too bad, Ogami-kun.
At least I'll get to kill you with my own hands.
Ogami!
It's no use.
Hitomi!
Ogami!
What's wrong, Ogami-kun?
Can't use your flames?
Ogami!
Seems like you've gone Lost, Ogami-kun.
Lost?
Is it painful, Ogami-kun?
Ogami!
The hardships endured by special ability users shock me.
Even so, Eden is...
Ogami-kun!
Wait, Hitomi-senpai-dono!
I won't let you kill him!
You really are a good girl.
You've been brought up by good people.
Boss, do you really think that the one's who are sending out the bomb signals are actually there?
The bombs were at the places displayed on the map, so they must be here.
That must be it.
There's no time. Hurry!
Why are children...?
Do you think we can do it?
Hitomi told us not to get involved,
but for the sake of all those with special abilities...
Hey buddies,
why are you in a place like this?
It's dangerous, so why don't you move-
Stay away!
Daisuke-san!
They have the same powers as Ogami-kun and the others!
Don't do this.
Don't do this anymore!
Don't do this anymore, Hitomi-senpai-dono!
Are you going to protect Ogami-kun by yourself?
Sakurakouji-san...
I really do think that those straight forward feelings are amazing,
but you see,
that's not enough to change the world!
If you interfere, I will show you no mercy.
Because special abilities don't affect you, I'll have to do it like this.
Hitomi...
Ogami-kun,
In your current state, you don't have enough power to save this girl.
You're helpless.
Hitomi!
The time for the explosion is drawing near.
Hurry up and save me, Code:Breaker.
Do you plan to just stand there and watch while I die?
I'll wait until she's seen the death of the Prime Minister and the massacre
of 50,000 people with her own eyes before I kill her.
I have seen so many Code:Breakers die.
You wouldn't know.
The feeling of helplessness when you can't protect someone.
Hitomi-senpai-dono... you can't! You can't blow them up!
To do something like this...!
Now, the era in which special ability users can live out in daylight begins!
We will escape our fate of dying unnoticed by everyone.
The days of loneliness are coming to an end!
This is our victory!
Was the device tampered with?
Is it over?
I wonder.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Somehow.
What's going on?
I allowed myself to interfere.
Heike!
No way...
I'm finished, Number 2.
I had Yuki-kun work under my instructions.
They won't let you have the children with special abilities either.
A little more!
There are no explosions.
Did the operation fail?
Wait!
Under Heike's instructions, I had the children moved to another location.
So you were buying time for that reason?
I pretended to be dead, to fool Hitomi, and put a stop to his plans.
It's all Heike's idea.
Therefore!
Are you still fighting?
Look out, Yuki!
Did he... escape?
I see... Of course.
Heike.
You knew why I planned this operation...
Even though I did it to save all those with special abilities.
It's over, Ace.
Heike!
Ace!
If you use your abilities too much, you'll go Lost.
Please don't overuse your powers.
There are still things I need you to do for me.
I will not go Lost.
What did you just say, Ace?
Ace?
Do you really think you have won, Heike?
The bombs around the country cannot be triggered anymore.
Toki-kun has rescued the Prime Minister.
Your plan has collapsed.
I'm asking you, do you really think you've won?!
Why do you think I chose the Sky Tower as my final ground?
This place?
Even if I were to be betrayed, to make sure my plan
would not suffer a setback, I left one last resort.
That's right!
With my electric abilities, I'll emit an electric wave from here and set off all the
bombs in the country!
This is my last battle!
Stop it, Ace!
If I could, I wouldn't use these measures, Heike.
Surely, you're not...
It's over!
Are you freaking out, Prime Minister?
You really had me worried.
However, it looks like you managed to stop the explosion.
Well done, well done.
Now, hurry up and untie me.
What's wrong?
Right now, the fate of this guy is in my hands.
If I kill him, Sis will be free.
What are you doing? Untie the ropes right now!
Toki! What are you up to?
I smashed the camera.
I'm the only one who's watching this scene.
Whatever happens to you, no one will believe the truth.
Don't, Toki!
If I fall, I'll die!
Stop this, Toki, I beg you!
I'm falling! I'm falling!
Getting all panicky.
Embarrassing!
I'm falling...
Ouch...
I have to give you a scare like this every now and then.
Well, Toki? Are you satisfied now?
That was a nice little performance, right?
But, not taking the chance when it's presented to you,
I guess you're just a raised dog after all.
Even if you could take advantage of the explosion and forsake me,
is it too scary to do it with your own hands?
You're really no good.
As I thought, I should have used Nenene as a Code:Breaker instead.
You shitty excuse of a father!
I'm going shopping with daddy!
Yes, that's it.
If you don't want to turn Nenene into a murderer,
you need to stay obedient.
That's the kind of deal we have, right?
Code:Breaker, Code: 04, Toki.
The fun is still ahead of us.
Hold it!
Is there still something you need to say?
I could kill you anytime. But I don't.
You don't have the courage to kill me.
I don't, so I won't turn out like you!
What?
I won't turn out like you, who only uses the Code:Breakers for your own desires!
Such nonsense.
What's this?
Don't do it, Ace!
You can't do this, Hitomi-senpai-dono!
This will... Huh, what?
This is as far as you go, Hitomi-san!
Ouji-dono! You're safe!
Speaking of which, Yuki!
What the hell are you doing sending the bike flying like that?!
It couldn't be helped.
If I hadn't, then we wouldn't have made it in time.
Yuki-kun!
Hitomi-san, I won't let you go on with this.
If you interfere, then I'll take you down first!
Number 5!
Cut it out already, Number 1!
Why have you become like this? Where's the old Number 1?!
Ace!
Hitomi-san!
You would never do something like this! Why are you...?
What happened? Tell us, Number 1!
You really don't understand a thing.
You joined forces and the way you watch out for each other is amazing.
It's so nostalgic. I was also in that world before.
But as long as Eden is controlling the Code:Breakers and those with special abilities,
our fate to give up our lives and become private soldiers won't change.
Eden is taking advantage of our consideration for each other!
Why don't you realize that your actions are shutting the door on the future for all special ability users?!
That may be true, but it's still not an excuse to involve innocent people-
They're not innocent!
The people I was protecting before were criminals!
They're unaware!
They're unaware of how we're risking our lives so they can live in peace!
They don't know just how many Code:Breakers have died.
They're enjoying peace in ignorance.
They keep on living such different lives from us!
Not even realizing that they're being protected!
If this is not a crime, then what is it?!
It's too late now.
Since the day I was ousted from Eden, the world has changed!
Hitomi-san!
I was watching you!
I saw you fighting! I saw you protecting a lot of people!
I remember when you saved me!
You're out of line.
You can't do that.
Hitomi-san, you can't do something like that.
Stop it, Hitomi-senpai-dono!
No more!
You just have to interfere, right up until the end.
Stop it, Hitomi-san!
Even if I have to murder the people of this country who are immersed in peace,
I will set the special ability users free!
An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth;
evil for evil.
You have changed.
Hitomi,
it's over.
What?!
What on earth?
Hitomi, no matter how far you've fallen into evil,
I'll burn you to the ground!
Incredible. This... power!
One day, you, too, will know where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city, unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear. The answers lie beyond the darkness
Toki-kun, Yuki-kun, Ouji-dono,
Heike-senpai, Hitomi-senpai-dono.
Next time,  Code:Breaker episode 13.
"A Flower Blooming With God."
Farewell, Ogami!