That's far enough!
Nyanmaru will protect... the others!
Nyanmaru...
Why is there no final piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
Episode 7
Sakura, Inside the Light
Meow meow Nyanmaru, everybodys' friend...
He's not in any mortal danger?
Correct.
Kind-hearted, always on little kittens side...
More sorrowful than anyone else...
Code:Breakers use special abilities,
but if they overuse them, the abilities disappear,
and their bodies get thrown out of order.
Which is what "Lost" is.
Master has been using too much of his power lately,
About the fragility of lives passing away....
so I figured it was going to happen soon.
It's okay. It will take him a day to recover, but he'll get better.
Before long, he remembers everything...
Is that right? Mm, that is good!
Slicing good and evil asunder...
Heike-senpai, you mentioned something about destiny and fate, so I was stunned.
But in short, it's almost like he's gotten hungry, isn't it?
I have to admit, I'm surprised that you are a Code:Breaker, too.
Not to mention you being part of their team as well, Sensei.
As well as... Yuki...
What's his story?
I am an agent of Eden.
Our job is to support the Code:Breakers.
Support?
Ogami-kun is Code 06.
That makes him the lowest-ranking one among us.
As such, he has an exclusive support staff member assigned.
Ogami is the lowest ranked?
He puts on that tough-guy act, but he's actually the lowest ranked?
Yuki-kun here is Code 03.
He uses sound special abilities.
And while he's not here today, Toki-kun is Code 04.
Putting a Nyanmaru sticker on him won't make him any better.
I like Nyanmaru.
Number six, your Lost looks hard on you. Hurry and get better.
He is Freedom.
Ahh... Mm-hmm.
Yuki-kun is concerned about Ogami in his own way.
Oh, with that in mind, what number are you, Heike-senpai?
I am Code 02.
While I am a Code:Breaker, at the same time, I also judge the others.
Points off for that.
You don't say.
Which means, there is also a number 5 and a number 1, right?
I believe you have already met Code 05.
Oh, do you mean the girl on the bike?
I knew it! Then, number one would be...
W- Well... We'll be in deep if we're attacked again.
We should relocate, so we can keep Master protected.
Oh! That certainly is true.
You think this is his doing, too, don't you?
It's possible that they know the location of Master's apartment.
We'll have to think of somewhere else to take him.
What if he were to come to my place?
No! It's too dangerous!
Teacher, you know what kind of house
the Sakurakoji home is, don't you?
Welcome home, Miss Sakura!
Indeed. I am home.
The Kizakura-gumi...
the strongest and most preeminent "good-fella" organization in Japan.
And the daughter of the clan's chief, Sakurakoji Gotoku,
is Sakurakoji Sakura-san.
Wow.
Miss Sakura, who are these others?
Indeed, this is my upperclassman, my homeroom teacher, and some friends.
Friends?
Welcome home, Sakura-kun!
Ma'am!
Welcome home, Sakura-chan!
Boss!
W-W-What happened?
He fought for me, and for
the rest of our classmates.
I would like to look after him here until he recovers.
He is a dear friend, isn't he?
Sure, use the guest room!
Thank you very much, Mother!
He fought for all of us. That's why!
Nyanmaru...?
Oh yes, your friend is here!
My friend?
I asked him to wait in the guest room.
Sakura-kun is home! Wha-?
Who do you mean, my friend?
He said his name was Toki.
Toki?!
What are Yuki and Heike doing here, too?
You idiot!
Hey, stop that! Let me go!
- I found Number four.
- Let me go! Put me down!
That's Toki-kun?
Why does he look like that?
Hmph, he went Lost.
H-He gets smaller?
Lost forms vary from person to person.
Toki-san becomes a child when he is Lost.
What's this about being Lost and getting smaller?
M-Mother!
Th-Th-That is definitely, without a doubt, one-hundred percent my friend Toki-kun!
Hmm, in that case, okay.
The meal is in the great hall, so come as soon as you can.
Y-Yes, Mother!
So, I got word from Eden.
They said that Ogami was Lost, so I came to back him up.
Toki-kun, you too are Lost, are you not?
Have you informed Eden about your condition?
You haven't told them, have you?
Dah! Don't put stickers on me!
It'll help make you better, Number 4.
It will not!
You all get along well, don't you?
And with that, we welcome Sakura-kun's friends to our meal!
Ma'am, we thank you for this food!
What is it, Sakurakoji-san?
Uh, nothing...
Heike-senpai, why are you working?
Yes, why, indeed?
What did Ogami-kun say?
To wipe out evil.
Is that right?
Burn to ashes.
Though he gets hurt like this...
all alone.
Sakura-chan! Are you drinking?
Hmm? Toki-kun, underage drinking is wrong.
It's not alcohol! It's juice!
But you're drunk, aren't you?!
Huh? It's the effect of being Lost. I get drunk on juice.
You do?
Toki-kun, points off.
Uh-huh, you're just acting big, Heike.
And you don't even have any eyebrows.
No eyebrows!
Toki-kun, it sounds like you're going to need a spanking.
Huh? No, you don't have to get so serious!
Thanks for keeping Number 6 here.
It's no big deal. I have to return the favor for protecting our classmates.
Besides...
Ogami and Toki-kun are both in a tight spot. I will have to do what I can!
The others can't fight! Nyanmaru will have to!
You're Nyanmaru.
Let go!
Thanks so much for the food and the bath, Sakurakoji-san.
Oh no, I'm terribly sorry that the hospitality isn't that great.
I will protect you, Nyanmaru.
Such boorish clouds, to interrupt me while I'm reading.
Standing guard with your nose in the air, huh?
Yes, well, since you've become Lost, Toki-kun...
Toki-kun, I was watching everything that took place today.
They were clearly split into two groups:
A team that attacked Ogami-kun, and a team that attacked Sakurakouji-san.
Why do you think Hitomi would set up something like that?
You're saying that Sakura-chan was targeted, too?
Sakurakouji-san is a Rare Kind.
It's not surprising that
Hitomi would show interest in her.
But...
If he wants to kidnap Sakurakouji-san,
there must be simpler ways for him to do it.
I cannot fathom why he would intentionally go after her while Ogami-kun was there.
And instead, if his objective was to attack Ogami-kun,
I don't understand why he would divide his forces.
Good point. Ultimately, it just forced Ogami to go Lost.
Just forced him to go Lost. You're right...
Could there have been some other objective?
Sakurakouji-san...
Master, you're awake?
Kanda... Is this Sakurakouji-san's house?
Yes, it is.
I'm terribly sorry.
If I could have prevented those men from attacking...
No need to apologize. I was careless as well.
Master, those men were the agents who have gone missing.
What's more...
Yeah.
They were controlled by special ability powers.
Then, it would have to be...
No doubt about it.
The enemy is the former Code:Breaker, Code 01,
Hitomi.
What?
Code 05, head to Sakurakoji Sakura's house immediately.
What? I thought Yuki and Toki were over there.
Code 04, Toki, is Lost. He'll be no help.
Acknowledged.
What the hell are all the Code:Breakers doing?
You're interested in the katana?
You look like you're feeling better, Ogami-kun.
I'll let you borrow this.
You've seen too much death, haven't you?
I can tell.
Because I use to live in that kind of world.
You've lost the dread that comes with taking people's lives.
That means you've also lost the interest that comes with living.
Sakura is a good daughter.
If anything happens to Sakura,
there will be a price to pay, Ogami-kun.
Men!
Hitomi!
Sakura-chan!
I will protect Nyanmaru!
Watch it. You might hit Sakurakouji-san.
And is that all the power you've got?
Shut up!
No matter. Sleepy time, kitty.
Yuki!
And you just walk right back into going Lost.
As your teacher, I'm disappointed.
Ogami-kun!
Please let Sakurakouji-san go, Hitomi-san!
You think you can shoot me?
Hitomi-san...
Your swordsmanship has
gotten a lot better, hasn't it?
As your teacher, I feel honored.
However...
You can't beat me, Ogami-kun.
If you get in my way, it's sayonara.
Dance!
Oh, Toki-kun! Back from being Lost, huh?
It's the whole Code:Breaker lineup.
Hey! You're still Lost, aren't you? Stay back!
This is my prey!
Why have you fallen into evil?
What is your purpose?
Revenge.
Yes, revenge against Eden.
You've changed.
You used to hate revenge.
Is he a friend of his?
If you've fallen into evil...
I'll cut you down!
How did you come to be such a lapdog of Eden?
Eden has nothing to do with it!
I am doing this of my own will!
Eden put you up to this, admit it!
Ogami!
Don't act so relaxed!
You're not even gonna take
our hands outta your pockets?
You sure are spirited, Toki-kun. Hm?
Ogami...
I see, so your twenty-four hours are up, huh?
Hitomi, I don't know what kind of grudge you've got against Eden,
but what you're doing is just a load of crap.
You're the same old
straight-arrow as ever, huh, Ogami-kun?
An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth;
and evil for evil!
It's no use. Not against my lightning.
Ogami!
Toki-kun!
Now then...
Do you think you can beat me?
We won't know unless I try, will we?
That's far enough, former Code 01, Hitomi.
We cannot allow you to have the Rare Kind.
That's a name that takes me back. Code 01, huh?
Let me show you the reason...
Why I was called that, so long ago.
What power!
Death to those who stand against me.
Farewell, Code:Breakers!
No!
Sakurakouji-san!
Sakura-kun!
What the...?
Outstanding, Sakura-chan!
Better than I expected!
Sakura-chan...
W-What is so outstanding?!
Are you making fun of me?!
Hey, what are you doing?!
How can you be so reckless?!
Please, stay back!
I got a pretty good show out of it,
so maybe I'll give up on the Rare Kind for now.
Well, it was about time I left.
You're not getting away!
There's no need to fight you any longer today.
The moment you Code:Breakers all gathered yourselves here,
the battle was decided.
We all gathered...? You don't mean...!
Code 02! The Prime Minister has been abducted by someone with special abilities!
I'm in pursuit of the culprit!
Rendezvous with me! Hurry!
It's been fun. Good night, Code:Breakers.
Damn it!
The Prime Minister?
Hitomi!
Kidnapping the Prime Minister! You're really serious about this, aren't you Code 01?
One day, you, too, will know where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city, unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear. The answers lie beyond the darkness
This is bad. I was off my game before going Lost, all night.
I got beaten pretty easily.
Next time, Code:Breaker Episode 8:
"King & Soldier, Child & House."
I will burn all those who fall into evil.
Even if they were once my friend!