Why is there no final piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
Earlier today, at Congressman Tabata Shigeru-shi's private residence.
there was a fire
Congressman Tabata dead
Cause of fire: Smoking in bed?!
The fire was extinguished after it destroyed the bedroom and hallway,
but what is believed to be Tabata-shi's
body was found in the bedroom.
This is a terrible shame.
Going forward, I was expecting to work with Tabata-kun a lot more.
There's a strong suspicion that
the fire was caused by him smoking in bed.
Did he usually smoke a lot?
I've heard that he was fond of his cigarettes but,
what I can say, it's a tragedy.
Prime Minister, Toki-sama is here to see you.
Good, let him in.
I'm so glad you came, Toki!
You did a great job last night. Do sit down.
Go ahead.
Whoa, how long has it been since we last ate breakfast together?
Research on special abilities...
that's some nasty stuff you're doing, Prime Minister.
Oh, don't put it like that.
For a Prime Minister, that could lead to Prime Trouble~
Get it...?
If only just a little bit...
If I could, even just a little, I'd like to reduce the burden on you Code:Breakers.
As a father, I'm well aware that I'm putting you through severe hardships.
I invited you here because I wanted to do something, as a father.
I'm a Code:Breaker.
You're not my father, and I'm not your son.
I assume that you're still angry about Nenene?
My heart is aching too, you know.
To put her in that kind of position...
We had a deal,
I would become your dog and get rid of the evil.
Nee-chan would be left alone.
Wasn't that what we agreed upon?
I heard you went to see her without telling me.
How was she doing?
Bastard.
The Lost One
Episode 6
Fire at Congressman
Tabata's residence
The government sure knows how to cover things up, don't they?
The public doesn't know that the government
is controlling the Code:Breakers.
Even though something like this happened.
What's up with him?
Hey...?
Do you know him?
I have a favor to ask of you.
Yes?
Could you leave us alone for a bit?
Eden's displeased with you taking
Sakurakouji Sakura with you to Tabata's mansion
and exposing her to danger.
What does Eden care about Sakurakouji-san?
This is an order from Eden:
"You are to be her bodyguard."
Why would I? I have to find Hitomi...
Stop complaining!
Just get on with it, got it?
I know that you don't really care for Eden.
Honestly, I don't like them either.
However, openly oppose them and you'll
only find it getting harder to move around.
I'll try to investigate stuff about her.
She may be a "Rare Kind",
but there has to be some other reason why they would have a Code:Breaker guarding her.
You haven't changed at all.
Rei!
You've been working too much lately.
Is it possible that you're gonna be "Lost" soon? Be careful.
What a beautiful person.
Is he also a Code:Breaker?
Both Toki-kun and now him.
Ogami, I see that you have quite a few friends.
I have no such thing. I'm a non-existing being, a Code:Breaker.
Whatever you say. I'm relieved.
You have people around you who care about you, that's what's important.
Ogami! Aside from your Code:Breaker friends,
you might as well get better acquainted with everyone in class!
You'll have more fun that way.
There's no need for that.
Even if I were to get closer to them, they wouldn't contribute to my work.
It would be a waste of time.
It would be stupid to get involved
with them and have my identity revealed.
Also, the Code:Breakers are not my friends.
We only share the same interest and trade.
Good morning to you!
Good morning, Sakura!
What's going on?
Huh? Oh, nothing. Right?!
Eh, yeah, nothing, nothing. Nothing at all!
Hey, don't put your stuff on my desk.
Sorry, sorry.
The class is about to start!
Pass on the print-outs. You have 30 minutes.
Hey, Sakurakouji! Keep your eyes on your own paper!
Y-Yes! I'm sorry!
The public doesn't know that the government is controlling the Code:Breakers.
Even though something like this happened.
If you're spilling my secrets I'll torch
your friends without hesitation, Sakurakouji-san.
Hiding in the darkness, the boy held his breath and looked on.
Unsure of what he saw, he snuck up to the attic above the woman's room
to get a better view.
Creak, squeak.
The floor in the woman's room creaked.
The boy looked upon the scene in the room through a small hole in the floor.
The boy saw the figure of the woman lying on the bed...
And a female teacher holding a rope approaching the bed.
The female teacher said:
Heike-kun!
Oh my, Kanda-sensei.
Would you please stop reading
erotic novels out loud in the corridor?
It's not erotic; it's a so-called sensual art form.
Not so loud!
I do apologize.
The effusive poetry of the plot
got me carried away, and I couldn't help myself.
Jeez.
He's just too much.
Ogami-kun, you're heading for the Dead Zone.
Sakurakouji-san, I would like to get my bag from the classroom.
You can't go in there right now!
What are you doing?
It's something really important...
Just wait a little longer.
This is gonna be amazing!
He won't see this coming!
We have to make sure he doesn't find out!
Sakurakouji-san, did you...?
Ogami's outside! Everyone, hush, hush!
Wai- wai-
Wait, Ogami!
Ogami! Ogami!
What are you whispering ab...
Ogami-kun!
Welcome to
Class 1B!!
Welcome to class 1B!
Welcome to
Class 1B!!
Sorry for the late welcoming party!
And it's late in the evening 'cause we all had club activities!
You don't have to go to work yet, do you?
Oh right! The new guy has to wear a hat!
Everyone pitched in and made something, but there
wasn't much time, so it might not look all that pretty.
Here Ogami, a present for you.
Let's go to the game center in front of the station!
I Heard you lived in the Middle East!
Make sure to remember all our names!
Why did you do something like this?
Isn't it obvious?
We're gonna be in the same class for a year, so we should all get along well and have a great time!
And also Ogami-kun, you're always smiling to yourself,
but you don't really talk to anyone except Sakura.
We thought that maybe you were just pretending to like it here.
Everyone was worrying, you know!
Let's hit it off, Ogami-kun!
Yeah, me too!
I'm in!
I only heard about it this morning.
I was asked to keep you away from
the classroom so that they could prepare everything.
Niitai Aki, Yusao Watanabe.
Everyone cares about you.
It would be nice for you to get to know them better.
There's no need for that.
Wai- What are you doing?!
After everyone did this for you...
I don't like things.
Even though people die, their things remain.
That's why I want to get rid of them in advance.
Aoki Takahashi, "Let's go to the game center."
Aoyama Yukio, "My hobby is mountain climbing."
Ijuuin Hikari, "I love blondes."
Uesugi Hajime, "Teach me English, please."
I memorized all the data written on them.
It feels like those guys would let me have it if I didn't.
Ogami.
I will not forget. Never.
You are not alone. You're not a non-existing being.
Still,
for the time being, I have no need for friends.
Wha...? Oh, come on. You're not being honest with yourself.
Annoying...
So annoying!
I didn't think... it would be this fast.
Dammit!
We haven't heard from agent Kawamura
since he reported that the target had been discovered.
This makes the number of missing agents 43 in total.
Ex-Code:Breaker, Hitomi, he sure is something.
I suppose we can expect nothing less from Code 01.
Well then, I wonder what his next move will be.
Oh, good morning, Yukihina.
You've gathered quite the crowd.
What are you gonna use them for?
I'll start a new world.
I wonder if Ogami-kun enjoyed the party?
That's right. You can never read his expression.
I agree!
Do you think Sakura's having any luck?
We finally managed to give them some time alone, so it would be disappointing if she didn't.
Oh right, they're alone on the rooftop.
Possibly by now...
By now...
Ogami!!!
If you don't make Sakurakouji-san happy,
I'm not letting you get away with it!!!
Now that you've memorized everybody's names, all is settled!
Let's go and clean u...
Hey, hey! Who are you? What's going on?
You can't come in here...
What do you want?
These guys are... without a doubt...
Wait, Ogami!
Don't!
Fool! They're already dead!
What?!
Their corpses are being manipulated!
There's only one person who could do something like this.
Ogami!
As I thought. It was a good idea to take care of things beforehand.
What's wrong? Ogami!
Now of all times...
Ogami! Ogami...
Wh-Who might you be?
Kanda-sensei!
This is... Hitomi-san's power.
What is all this about?
We'll talk later.
We're getting out of here!
This is bad. They're going into the school!
Oh no! We have to get everyone to safety!
Ogami!
Kanda, protect Sakurakouji-san!
Master!
Anyone who crosses this line of fire will be burnt to the ground!
An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth;
and evil for evil!
Ogami...
Ogami... the people around you really are the most important thing to you, aren't they?
Ogami!
Master!
Number 6!
I've come... to save you!!
Yu... ki.
Wh-Who are you?
To allow yourself to be cornered like this,
you've lost some points, Ogami-kun.
Heike-senpai!
And Yuki-kun, it's good to be here
in the nick of time, but your work is crude.
What?
What? Wanna fight?
This is already a Dead Zone!
An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth;
and an eternal sleep for the dead.
Whoa, the power of light is incredible.
No way! Heike-senpai is also a Code:Breaker?
Ogami!
Ogami...
Ogami! Ogami, hang in there!
Ogami!
Ogami, this can't be...
He's Lost.
Lost?
That's right.
The fate of us Code:Breakers.
An unavoidable destiny.
One day, you, too, will know where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city, unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear. The answers lie beyond the darkness
Even if this is your destiny,
I can't accept it!
Next time, Code:Breaker Episode 7: "Sakura, Inside the Light"
Ogami.
Ogami!