Your lunges are weak.
The tip of your sword is quivering.
You're not advancing.
I did it!
You mustn't stop attacking until you've completely immobilized your enemy.
Got it, Ogami-kun?
Please stop addressing me as "Ogami-kun".
Only when you've surpassed me.
Ogami-kun.
A Flower Blooming with God
Final
Episode
I'm sure he went Lost, but...
these flames...
An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth;
and evil for evil.
You surprise me, Ogami-kun.
You just have to interfere, don't you?
However...
Ogami!
You cannot win.
Now, die before my lightning!
He consumed Number 1's special ability.
Then, how about this?!
That's...
If you're fed with this much electricity at once,
even your flames can't absorb it.
Hitomi-senpai-dono!
Eat this!
Sakurakouji!
Hey, Ogami!
Hurry up and get away from there!
Stop it already, Number 1!
The electricity...
He absorbed it.
Magnificent...
Truly magnificent, Ogami-kun.
What is this Ogami?
No, he's completely different to how he usually is.
Not yet.
It's not over yet!
No matter who stands in my way...
Stop it, Hitomi!
I'll definitely...
Hitomi-san!
carry out my plan!
And sacrifice 50,000 people!
Amazing.
Such immense power...
Burn to ashes.
Hitomi-san!
Is it over?
Ogami!
Number 6!
I'm extremely satisfied, Ogami-kun.
And you... Ace.
Hitomi-san, Hitomi-san!
Kanda...
Ogami! Ogami!
Wake up, Ogami!
I see...
I failed...
Hitomi-san, you shouldn't move.
Get away from me.
Hitomi-senpai-dono!
So it seems... you've reach Code:End?
Hitomi has?!
No way...
Hitomi-san.
I see.
You already knew the truth about Code:End.
Number 1...
Hitomi-senpai-dono has...
It seems like my time is almost up.
Right after I was forced out of Eden,
the signs of Code:End began appearing.
I was afraid.
After all, I didn't want to die alone.
I realized that the other Code:Breakers who died before me must have experienced the same fear.
I don't expect you to understand how I feel.
There's no way you could.
I hoped for some more time to find a way to change Eden,
but when it became clear Code:End was drawing near, my time became limited.
What could I possibly do?
I couldn't forgive Eden.
But more than that, I wanted to save my friends with special abilities.
I wanted to save them from this terror.
I wanted them to live fulfilled lives, like most other people.
I guess my plans fell apart, though.
However...
It's not over yet.
I can't stop here.
Stop this already, Hitomi-san.
I'll at least kill the Prime Minister with my own hands!
Hitomi-senpai-dono.
I'll make him pay for what he did to the fallen Code:Breakers.
I'll never forgive that bastard. Never!
Pull yourself together, Hitomi!
If I don't do it, then who will?!
Even if it results in you dying?
For the sake of the special abilities?!
To get revenge on Eden?!
You've killed and sacrificed so many people!
You, who despised nothing more than seeing innocent people get killed!
You, who tried so desperately to save people!
Why have you...?
Why did it have to end up like this?
Why did you decide to do something like this alone?
I am Code:01.
If I didn't do it...
He took everything upon himself.
That's just like...
Just like...
Hitomi!
Kanda wasn't the only one serving as eyes for Eden.
Every one of the Code:breakers were under surveillance.
If I'd contacted you, my plans would have been jeopardized.
If you had become involved, Eden may have pursued you as well.
That's why I...
Hitomi-san!
Number 1!
I see.
Even if it had gotten you involved, I still should have met with you.
All of you.
Hitomi-san.
Just like the old days.
Yuki.
You were the first one to pounce on me.
That's Code:03 for you.
Number 1...
Toki.
Thank you for protecting Kanda.
You were right. I was completely out of line.
Hitomi-san...
I'm sorry, Kanda.
Ouji.
You walked away from a battle with Yukihina unscathed.
That's incredible!
It's a shame that we couldn't procure those children, though...
I'm...
I'm not blaming you.
Heike.
I trusted you until the very end, you know?
Even that one time you were acting suspiciously,
I never lost faith in you.
Yes, just like the time we spent together, as Code:Breakers.
If only you hadn't taken control of the transmission point,
my plans would've come to fruition.
You really got me.
If we'd been brought together sooner,
perhaps things would've been different.
We would be on the path to a brighter
future that I couldn't create on my own.
Ogami-kun!
I was surprised by your power.
But you didn't deliver the final blow.
You're too soft. Didn't I tell you before?
You mustn't stop attacking until your enemy is completely immobilized.
What is this?
What's wrong with you?!
Why are you in such a disgraceful state?
Why were you defeated by someone like me?!
You!
The strongest Code:Breaker, Code:01, Hitomi!
To be in that state, on the brink of death, because of Code:End.
You dubbed yourself the Code:Breaker of justice, didn't you?!
If you die, you can no longer be an ally of justice, can you?
It's like you're dying for nothing, isn't it?
You're right.
No matter what, I wanted to see things through.
But it's impossible with my body now.
Ogami-kun, you should take on that name.
After all, you're the one who defeated the perpetrator of this incident.
You are the true Code:Breaker of justice.
You, Toki, Yuki, Ouji, and Heike, of course.
You should stand out under the light of the sun together.
If you do that...
nobody else will have to die alone.
No one.
That won't be possible.
An incident producing this much damage will soon be forgotten.
Even if you were to come forward,
it would only serve to make people fear those with special abilities, and the Code:Breakers.
Very well.
It seems everything is settled.
How could you do something so horrible?
Why didn't you hear him out?
He went there to talk to you!
He was doing his best to make everybody happy!
Even if you put it like that,
why should I have to listen to a mere Code:Breaker?
But, weren't you the one who chose him?
I'm regretting that decision now.
I never thought he would become a terrorist.
I'll have to choose the future Code:Breakers more carefully.
Starting with the next one.
Fujiwara!
Hitomi-san!
Number 1!
I won't allow you to toy with the special ability users anymore!
You're the only one I will never forgive!
Fujiwara!
You can't... do this anymore.
Leave the rest to us.
Please don't pile more evil upon yourself.
I don't want to see you do evil things.
Leave it to us.
I won't forget what you taught me.
I'll never forget you.
I see.
You grew up without me watching.
I'm relieved, Ogami.
You played your part well.
Thank you very much, Ace.
So he's finally dead.
A problem child, right to the very end.
You're such an asshole!
Why did it have to end like this?
Hitomi stole the lives of a lot of people.
This is what he deserved.
Ogami!
There must have been another way...
It's too late now!
The dead can't come back.
Ogami...
They said the bomber was shot to death.
Serves him right!
I heard that the Japanese police played a big part.
The police really are protecting our city!
I must say, you did a wonderful job.
I simply performed my duties.
You're being modest.
Nevertheless, who would've thought Hitomi would buy into your scheme so easily.
He was more naive than we expected.
Indeed.
I'm impressed by how you used Yuki-kun and Hachiouji-kun, as well.
Not only did they secure the kids,
but they also stopped the explosions.
I know.
There was another reason why you had them work independently.
You wanted to drive Ogami into a corner, so he'd be forced to reveal his true power.
Had those two been there, they would've been enough to overpower Hitomi.
That's why you separated them.
Thanks to you, we managed to see Ogami-kun's full potential.
You did an excellent job! As expected.
Why, thank you.
Your fight with Hitomi was a splendid act.
It wasn't an act.
So, what do you think of Ogami-kun's power?
Do you think it'll be able to combat the power of "The one we seek"?
I see.
So Hitomi is dead, huh?
Then, I assume she'll be used as a collar around Ogami Rei's neck.
That girl.
Ogami-kun was able to control his power this time.
But we can't say for sure that it won't go haywire next time.
Nonsense.
We have the Rare Kind on our side.
If we use her abilities, we can extinguish even those flames.
Extinguish the flames and Ogami-kun.
Our plans are progressing swiftly.
After all, Hitomi was only chosen as a Code:Breaker because of Ogami and the Rare Kind.
We let the strong special abilities user clash with the growing Ogami.
As expected, we were able to successfully unleash Ogami's power.
All according to plan.
Indeed.
Right. All the pieces we need to confront "The one we seek" have been set.
We're fighting poison with poison, so to speak.
Poison, huh?
Still, this will be troublesome.
Hitomi's outburst caused minimal damage,
but now we must deal with the inner circle, "The one we seek".
There's always something to worry about.
That's what I was about to say.
Exposing yourself to Hitomi like that...
You protected me, didn't you?
Also, there's no way he would've hurt me with that.
I'm...
Prime Minister!
I was bitten... by a cornered rat.
Hitomi.
Ogami...
Nyanmaru is looking gloomy today.
Yuki-kun!
Looks like number 6 isn't here.
Nyanmaru, cheer up!
If you're ever in trouble, just call me, okay?
I'll save you anytime.
Um, thank you.
See ya!
I suppose Yuki came by to say goodbye.
Goodbye?
We were all gathered here because of the incident with Hitomi-san.
Now that it's over, we'll be working individually again.
I owe you one. Your mom's cooking was delicious.
My mother will be delighted to hear that!
That's a great smile. That's the way you should look.
Ouji-dono...
your smile is beautiful, too.
F-Fool!
S-See you around!
She's such a good person.
Everyone is leaving...
What is it, Puppy?
It's not like I feel lonely without them.
I'm not lonely...
What's the matter, Sakura-chan?
I-I wasn't crying, or anything!
So both Ouji and Yuki left?
What about you, Toki-kun?
I'll be having fun with Sakura-chan all day lo-
For god's sake, you're completely shameless!
You're so mean!
And I was just about to tell you about Ogami.
Huh! What?!
Where is he? Please tell me, Toki-kun!
He can't be left alone!
I have to keep an eye on him!
I'm kinda jealous.
I see, he already left.
As I thought. He just left without even saying goodbye, huh? That asshole.
He's so heartless, dammit.
If you're gonna leave, you have to say goodbye, right?
Sakura-chan!
I'm sorry, but I want you to stop the bus!
I'm getting off!
Goodbye, Sakura-chan.
Hey, this way!
Ogami...
This one's mine!
No way!
Wait up!
Awesome!
Ogami...
Even if people are unaware of the existence of the Code:Breakers,
you're not a non-existent being.
I know of your existence.
You're existing among us!
You are not alone.
And as long as you, Toki-kun, Ouji-dono, Yuki-kun,
Heike-senpai, and Kanda-sensei are alive,
Hitomi-senpai-dono will also continue to exist.
No one is alone.
Ogami!
An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth;
and evil for evil!
Why is there no final piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy