Welcome to the Code:Breaker headquarters, Eden.
You are among the elite soldiers of the world,
and have been given great and authority.
With such ability, you are authorized to wipe out evil,
one of the six Code:Breakers,
Code 06, Ogami Rei.
Even though you were the last one to be appointed a Code:Breaker,
you've carried out your work swiftly,
and have progressed to the point that you
can hold your own against the other five.
We have high expectations for you in the future.
I don't need your worthless flattery.
Let's get down to business.
Watch your mouth, peasant.
Now now, don't be like that.
Ogami-kun, you are out of line, too.
File Downloading
The politician, Tabata Shige.
Your job is to eliminate him.
Is Hitomi also involved with this?
It's your job to find that out, peasant.
Son of a bitch!
If you're gonna talk big, don't use these empty threats,
and come face me in person.
Also, don't get the wrong idea,
I'm the one who will decide if I do your bidding or otherwise.
I'm not your lap dog. This is just a job.
Why is there no final piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
Once again, I'm back home without knowing how I got here.
Voices of Time
Episode 4
Sakura-chan, we have to talk about this.
You heard him, Sakura-kun.
This is the second time we've
found you sleeping by the front gate.
It's now a case of bad manners.
As you say, it's bad manners but...
What happened? Tell us what is going on.
Yes, please.
Th-The thing is...
I joined the mountain-climbing club!
That's why I've been practicing sleeping outside.
Oh, so that's what you were doing!
You'll have to work hard to do that! I'll support you, Sakura-kun!
I'm leaving!
Sakura-chan made the same face as she does when she's lying.
I wonder what really happened.
Me too, but whenever Sakura-kun
tells a lie, it's always to protect someone.
And only when she thinks she's doing the right thing.
We should trust her.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Father, Mother.
Who's that?
Good morning! You're Sakura-chan, aren't you?
I am, but who are you?
I'm Toki. I'm here to pick you up instead of Ogami.
Instead of Ogami?
He made a mess yesterday and couldn't make it today.
A mess? You mean at work?
Yup, a Code:Breaker job.
Then, you're... also...
I am Code:Breaker, Code 04.
Ogami is only 06, so I have to look after him.
Oh, so that's how it is? Where's Ogami now?
He got scolded by the guys in charge
and should be home sobbing by now.
He should... be sobbing?
What is it? Whatcha doing?
Sorry, it's nothing!
By the way, have you known Ogami for long, Toki-kun?
Uh, let's see... Well, we are pretty good friends.
Friends?
Yup, so you can ask me anything about him.
I'll let you in on all kinds of stuff.
That's great!
If you're friends, then you have to tell him too!
I want him to stop what he's doing!
You want him to stop?
Ah that's right, you're also a Code:Breaker.
Hmm? It looks like you have your reasons.
Okay! I'll hear you out.
Really?!
Well, this place won't do, so...
Couldn't we have talked without coming all the way out here?
The truth is, I have something I
wanted to say to you about Ogami.
Oh, is that so?
It's something that has to do with you too.
With me?
Yeah. Very important matters.
What's up with you, Toki-kun?
Ogami?!
What are you doing, Ogami?!
Don't listen to his nonsense.
You're too much, Ogami-kun.
It's been a long time since we last met.
That's right, Ogami! You're friends, aren't you?
Who's friends with who?
But...
We're friends, sure.
I kicked your ass, then we got close.
You wanna get your ass kicked again, Ogami-kun?
Stop fighting, both of you!
What do you want, Toki?
You're so rude. I'm here to tell you about our next job.
You've heard about tonight, haven't you?
The guys in charge are worried about you being on your own.
Yesterday, I had to settle things for you in the end.
That's why it's been decided that
the almighty me, will accompany you.
The only reason I came here this early in the morning,
is to warn you not to drag me down.
You should worry more about yourself than about others.
Who was it that got Lost at a
critical moment and dragged me down?
Shut up, asshole.
You're an eyesore, shitface.
Let's settle things right here then, Code 06!
Interesting.
You're going to regret this, Toki.
I'll kill you!
You're dead!
Stop it, both of you.
It's okay to let your fists talk, but first you have to calm down!
S-Sakura-chan... that hurts.
Oh, sorry! That was by accident.
It's your fault.
Running amok like that.
You're pretty funny.
The colors of his eyes are the same as Fujiwara-senpai's.
What is it, Sakura-chan?
Are you done feasting your eyes on me?
Don't get so full of yourself, Toki-kun.
I just noticed that your eyes have different colors.
As I thought, your eyes were eating me up.
See you later, Ogami-kun.
Good luck with work!
Wait, Ogami!
Tell me more about Toki-kun.
He's a straight-out liar.
Please, don't believe what he says.
You're being pretty harsh. Did something happen between the both of you?
By the way, he said something about work.
You're not going to kill people again, are you?
Oh, and what is that "Lost" thing you were talking about?
Does it have something to do with your ability?
Good morning, Sakurakouji Sakura-san.
Lovely mornings...
call for a lovely tea-time.
Care to join me?
He's having tea again.
Shhh! He'll hear you!
Good morning, Heike-senpai.
Thanks for inviting me, but I'll have to pass. Classes are starting.
I understand. I'll be looking forward to our next opportunity.
This grammar will be on the next test, so be sure to remember it.
I'll have to question Ogami more closely during next break.
Now for the next example, Aoyama...
What is it, Sakurakouji?
Teacher!
I'm feeling unwell. Could I go to the nurse's office?
Eh? Wha..? Sakurakouji?!
Toki-kun!
Hey, Sakura-chan! What's going o-
That's my line! What are you doing here?!
What a thing to ask? I came to check out your school.
You're a liar.
You're probably just here to cause trouble.
Well well, skipping classes are we?
You're such a delinquent, Ogami-kun.
There you two go again.
That uniform belongs to another school.
Why aren't you there?!
Teacher!
I'm here... on a field trip... today...
Oh, you are?! Welcome to our school!
That's obviously a lie.
Huh, Ogami-kun is being suspicious of me.
You can go ahead and check with my school if you want.
That badge...
N-No way...
That really tough school with a T-score of 70...
The school with the highest acceptance rate into Tokyo University,
The school where the sons of the créme de la créme attend!
That's Heisei Academy?!
Japan's Top Elite
Ah, yeah I guess.
You say that so casually...
Well, I only chose that school because it was the closest to home.
So, Toki-kun from Heisei Academy will join our class today!
Everyone, let's get along and study hard!
Okay!
Hey, he's kinda cool!
He looks posh.
Well, if he's honestly here to study, all is good.
It's finally lunch! I'm starving!
Ogami, come with me.
Let's talk over lunch.
What? Did she make lunch for him?!
Are they already that close?
Sakura is getting on with him.
I'd rather not.
Wait, what?!
Wait, Ogami!
You come too, Toki-kun.
Let's eat lunch together.
But I actually have some things to do.
Enough! Just come with me!
I have something to tell you.
Okay, if you insist.
What's going on here?!
What, what? Are they already in a love triangle?!
Darn you Ogami, sneaking away like that.
I'm sorry for making you come with me, even though you were busy, Toki-kun.
That's okay, I was only gonna take a look at her face anyway.
Her face?
Anyway, Sakura-chan,
what did you want to talk about?
He's so cool!
Emm, Ah...
Maybe you're not the right
person to ask, but as I said this morning,
I want to know if there's any
way to stop Ogami from killing people.
He's hurting himself and I don't
understand why he would go so far...
All Code:Breakers have goals.
And in order to accomplish these
goals, they take on all kinds of dirty work.
Ogami as well, probably has one.
Ogami's... goal?
For example,
to protect someone... or whatever.
You care so much about Ogami.
That really makes me jealous, you know.
Has he already touched you here?
To touch a woman's breasts without permission, how shameful!
That hurt!
Why is it okay for my big sis but not for me?!
Your big sis?
Oh! Then you and Fujiwara-senpai really are siblings!
No wonder you look so alike!
What's this?!
So Ogami-kun wanted to eat Sakura's bento after all.
Ogami!
Don't get the wrong idea.
She's a real airhead, so I'm just
making sure she's not being fooled by you again.
What do you mean, "airhead?!"
Come on, let's go.
Wait up, Ogami!
So, what did you want to talk about, Sakurakouji-san?
It's about you and the Code:Breakers!
Special friendship!
A friendship beyond gender issues.
You're worried about Ogami-kun, aren't you?
That's sweet.
What's wrong, Sakurakouji-san?
Judging by the look on your
face, it seems you don't want me here.
Huh? Not at all!
Fujiwara-senpai!
Lefty and Righty, welcome!
I wanted to see you!
Senpai!
It doesn't look like there will be much talking done today.
What's wrong, Sakura-chan?
Oh, it's nothing!
Ogami-kun, just letting you know, Lefty and Righty are mine!
I won't let you have them!
It can't be helped, I'll just have to give them up for today.
Oh, that's right!
Fujiwara-senpai, your little brother is here to see you.
My little brother?
That's right, he's over here... eh?
Where did he go?
Sakura-chan, what are you talking about?
I don't have any siblings.
Code:Breaker, huh?
Didn't I tell you not to follow me?
I'm keeping an eye on you
to make sure you won't kill anyone.
What's going on with Toki-kun and Fujiwara-senpai?
Code:Breakers are non-existing beings in this society.
Our existence has been completely erased,
and nobody knows about us.
Nobody?
Even if Toki has a family,
as long as he's a Code:Breaker, they will have no ties.
That's just...
Why is it okay for my big sis but not for me?
I was just gonna take a look at her face.
I actually have some things to do...
Toki-kun...
Oh!
'Sup? Sakura-chan, you came too?
Toki-kun, about Fujiwara-senpai...
Oh, that. I was just messing with you.
What? You really believed that we were siblings?
Ogami's gonna let you have it again.
That was no lie.
Fujiwara-senpai is your older sister.
When you said " to protect someone", wasn't that about her?
You became a Code:Breaker in order to protect your sister, didn't you?
I'm an ally of justice, you know.
That's why I became a Code:Breaker!
Toki-kun!
For the time being...
I want to protect Lefty and Righty here.
Who are you trying to fool with your nonsense?
Anyways,
it's almost time.
Shall we get started?
What?
Don't change the topic!
What did you do?
There will be a ruckus if the alarm goes off,
So I shut down the security system.
What?!
Next up is...
H-H-How did you do that?!
It's his special ability.
He can manipulate magnetic fields as he wishes.
Special ability?
Magnetic fields?
Toki-kun's ability.
Wait! What are you planning to do here?
I told you I'll teach these scum a lesson!
That's insane! This is a residential area!
They seem to be up for a fight too.
What'd you expect?
They wouldn't just sit quietly and let you kick in the door!
Sakurakouji-san, would you please go home?
But...
All right, let's get to work!
Toki-kun!
Hold it right there! Who are you, bastards?!
I'll finish off the target, so just stay out of my way.
Right back at ya, don't drag me down.
Moron!
What should I do?
So you showed up, Code:Breakers.
I won't let you get in my way!
Shoot!
Aaah, aiming at my head, you sure can't wait to kill me!
He... stopped the bullets?
They can even do that...
Code:Breakers...
Bullets are nothing against my ability.
Don't, Toki-kun!
Return to sender.
Toki-kun!
What? They tried to kill me first!
However...
Let's finish this.
What on earth...?
Special abilities, huh?
My, my...
We don't need those useless guys, do we?
Were you surprised?
Code:Breakers aren't the only ones with special abilities.
Do those two also have mysterious abilities?!
This is a research facility that the government has contracts with, for those with special abilities.
The government?!
These two are some of the results of that research.
One day, you, too, will know where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city, unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear. The answers lie beyond the darkness
Next time, Code:Breaker episode 05:
"A Banquet of Wishes."
What you're doing is unforgivable.
But you cannot die, Ogami!