An eye for an eye...
...a tooth for a tooth...
...a requiem of fury for evil!
Don't interfere!
They ran away.
Is he going on a killing spree?
Why is there no final
piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence
facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
I, Sakura, am off!
I understand none of this.
Still, there is one thing that I'm certain of.
What he is doing is not a good thing.
Good morning, Miss Sakurakoji.
Is your intention to surveil me?
Nope; just observe.
Ogami, don't you forget...
I will be keeping my eye on you, too.
"Episode 3:"
"'Angry Valor... A Graven Hammer'"
Aoba...
Good morning, Sakura.
You got another heaping pile today, huh?
"My beloved Sakurakoji"
Hey, Sakura, you came to
school with Ogami today, huh?
Aoba...
Look, I get it.
You don't have to say anything.
Apologies, Aoba,
but from now on, I will be coming
and going to school with Ogami.
I won't be able to go with you,
like we have up to now.
Sakura, congratulations!
No, this isn't much cause for celebration.
I will have my eye
on him for the whole day.
Whoo-hoo! Sakura,
I'm a little bit jealous!
You really do want to watch
Ogami for the whole day, huh?
Mm-hmm. If I can do so, I will rest at ease.
Ogami, you take good care of Sakura, now!
Of course.
Ah, but watch yourself, okay?
Ogami!!
Y-You stay away from Sakurakoji!
You're going to have boys chasing
after Sakura coming after you.
Take no action against him!
If you act against him,
you will have to face me!
Sakura, you're so cool!
Sakura...
You care that much about Ogami...
Miss Sakurakoji, it's okay,
you don't have to defend me.
I am quite strong, after all.
Ogami...
...you've got daily cleanup tomorrow,
so come to the student council
room for the duty checklist, okay?
The student council room?
Right, you don't know where
that is yet. What do we do?
I shall show him!
You really are a worrier, huh?
As long as you don't try anything funny,
I'm not going to do anything at school.
I'd like to avoid any trouble, myself.
And I am not about to have you suspecting
that I have told anyone your
secret when you are not around.
That's why I'm accompanying...
I spy Hi-tan and Mi-tan!
F-Fujiwara! I thought I asked
that you stop naming my breasts.
Oh, I see. The right breast is Mi-tan,
and the left one is Hi-tan.
Don't think too hard about it!
I love my very own...
Easy, Nenene!
Isn't this nice?
Ogami!
Ogami, do you think so, too?
Yes.
Ogami, you're like me!
I like you now, too, Ogami!
Why, thanks.
I think I'll reveal my secret,
especially for you, Ogami.
The colors of her eyes are different.
Ogami!
I'm sorry, Nenene,
I mistook you for someone else.
Ogami! Wait, Ogami!
Mistaken identity is not going to cut it!
Yeah, what is it?
Team up with him for a job? Sure thing.
"Number blocked"
I can't wait.
What is it?
Everything is in place for tonight.
The key is in the basket,
if you wouldn't mind.
Yeah,
very well.
Do you need something, Miss Sakurakoji?
W-What was that phone call about?
I hope you are not thinking of
doing anything ill-wrought again.
W-What is that?!
Nothing funny, right?
It's the pup of that other dog.
She had a puppy?!
True enough, your face looks just like hers.
And you are just as timid as her, too.
I see, so you are her child, are you?
Her...
I apologize.
If only I had been stronger...
Your mother... tried to protect me!
It sure seems peaceful, doesn't it?
It's a temporary, fabricated peace.
What?
Are you sure about this?
If you're going to come with me,
then you will never be able to
return to this peaceful world again.
Why wait until now to say this?
I have not been in a
peaceful world from the first.
The door isn't locked. How careless.
What, is this your place?
Are you sure you want to come with me?
Hmph, I think I'll see
for myself the way you live.
Who're you?
Ogami, what on earth?
Who the hell are you?!
This is...
...a Yakuza office?
Then this... couldn't mean...
Ogami is taking on the Yakuza!
Ogami!
Those gentlemen from
the police are here, are they not?
It looks like you won't be needed today!
Miss Sakurakoji, the police are in on it.
Hey, there, son,
you're pretty full of yourself, huh?
Don't think you won't pay for what you're...
There are fewer of you than I thought.
This shouldn't be much trouble.
Huh?! What shouldn't be much trouble?
Isn't that obvious?
Killing you all won't be much trouble.
- What did you just say?!
- You've got a smart mouth, kid!
- You wanna get your ass kicked?!
- Do you know the trouble you're in, squinty?!
Be quiet, would you?!
Son, what's your affiliation?
I'm with Class 1-B.
With backtalk like that,
you've got a lot of guts, son.
But saying you're going
to kill us isn't very friendly, is it?
Why don't you tell me what you're up to?
I fear that my wiping out G-Falcon,
and forcing you to conduct your business directly,
has put you out.
You?
Hey, don't try peddling that bill of goods, kid!
I told you to keep quiet, you idiot!
S-Sorry, Boss!
You've got spunk, even if you are full of crap.
Can't ask for a better sales pitch than that.
Okay, fine. Come work under me.
Like you said, son, with
G-Falcon gone, I'm shorthanded.
Oh? Is it good work?
Ogami!
Why don't you tell me more?
Hmm, that's right, it's choice work.
Selling this stuff here is fine,
but times being what they are,
the buyers' funds run out quickly.
So we use it as bait.
People will do anything to get their bait.
I had this one do a
number of risky jobs for me,
but he's not much use for anything anymore.
Which is why...
His family.
Right. His wife or daughter will bring a fine sum.
Kidnapping?
Those G-Falcon boys were
so rough. They damaged the goods.
On that point, son,
you'd be a natural at fast-talking
people into their abduction.
There are a number of
families we've already slated.
It rewards handsomely.
I see. And you've got policemen, to boot.
That I do! We don't have
to worry about being arrested.
Right, Mr. Kato?
Mm-hmm.
Surely you jest!
You call yourselves hoodlums?!
Huh?
That goes for you, too!
The police are normally
supposed to protect people!
Don't you believe that
you are acting immorally?!
Acting immorally, she says!
What is so funny?!
Kid! That stuff doesn't fly these days!
Young lady, like they say, fight fire with fire.
In the grown-up world, this is how things work.
Once you grow up, you'll understand this.
Then again, Mr. Nitta,
now that she has seen us,
we can't allow her to leave.
We don't need the girl, right?
Why, you!
Ogami!
Miss Sakurakoji, you can't
get through to them with words.
You can only make them submit by force.
Wait!
W-What kind of flames are those?!
An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth; evil for evil!
Burn away.
Mr. Nitta!
Stop that!
Ogami!
Why, you!
Why, you little... Let me go!
Evil...
I'll snap your neck!
Hot! Hot!
- Put me out! Please! Please!
- Stay away from me!
Evil...
Stop that, Ogami! Stop it!
Screw with us, will you?!
Th-The bullet!
What is with those flames?!
Who the hell are you?!
Y-You monster!
An eye for an eye!
A tooth for a tooth!
Evil for evil!
Officer Kato is sure taking a long time.
Hmph, he's probably up
to no good with a woman again.
Should we go back to the station?
We'll go see Hitomi.
We have some plans to finish up.
Ogami...
Ogami!
You didn't have to kill them!
There must have been a way
where you didn't have to kill them!
What way is that?
What other way was there?
If I hadn't killed them,
more people would have
kept falling victim to this group.
But...
Give me... Give me...
What's more, your words
didn't get through to these evil men.
That stuff doesn't fly these days!
In the grown-up world,
this is how things work.
We don't need her, right?
Evil men can only be brought
under submission by force.
Yeah, but!
But...
Puppy?
Wake up! You're all right now!
All... right?
That's right! Let's walk out of
here together. Where is your home?
My home?
No... I can't go home.
Not after what I've become.
I can't go home.
What are you saying?
My life is in shambles.
You've seen my dad.
It's hopeless now...
I can't... It's all over!
I'd rather be dead!
That's ridiculous!
Ogami!
Okay, die.
Don't, Ogami!
Don't do it, Ogami!
Ogami! Ogami!
I... don't... want... to... die...
I don't want to die!
Your suffering, and your displeasure,
and your desire to die,
are all liberties you
have because you are alive.
If you don't want to die,
then don't be presumptuous.
Endure the suffering,
crawl around on the ground,
and live for all you're worth!
If you still want to die
after that, then come to me,
and I'll kill you.
Ogami, why would you go that far?
For you, where does
the evil end, and where does...
Ogami!
Well? Do you feel that, Ogami?
I can feel you... your warmth.
Miss Sakurakoji, what are you?
A hug. A hug, where body speaks to body.
I understand why you fight.
I know you have your reasons why, too.
But I am unable to bring
myself to acknowledge them.
That is why I will fight, too.
I will come at you, again and again,
until my words get through to you!
That's so unusual.
I suppose that would have to be
because you're a rarebreed, right?
Like I've asked you,
what do you mean, rarebreed?
Miss Sakurakoji, unfortunately,
no one can understand me,
nor do I care to be understood.
What?
It's me. I'm done inside.
Please come retrieve Miss Sakurakoji.
What do you want?
You're Police Chief Takada, right?
Forgive me,
but I had to kill all of your pals.
Why don't you tell me the
location of the man you're working with?
Don't tell me you're a Code: Breaker!
Where is Hitomi?!
Hitomi! Please help me!
I'm being chased by a Code: Breaker!
That is terrible news, huh?
Please help me! I worked with you, didn't I?!
Mm-hmm, thank you. That was very helpful.
But what you are doing now
is inelegant, and I'd rather not.
"Hitomi"
Farewell, corrupt police chief.
Hitomi! Why, you!
I worked with you!
On your plan! I worked with you!
What?!
An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth; evil for evil!
Toki?!
An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth;
the hammer of justice for evil.
Ogami!
You are the great Toki's...
...warm-up act.
One day, you, too, will know
where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city,
unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following
wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from
which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear; the answers
lie beyond the darkness
Next time,
"Code: Breaker" episode 4,
"War Cry."
One can rest at ease when one is not alone.
You do have a friend, Ogami.