Why is there no final
piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence
facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
Kidnapped the Prime Minister?!
Damn it! He played us like a fiddle!
If he got us all together here,
and used that opening to attack,
then he prepared this carefully.
Even if we went to his
aid now, we'd be too late.
Ha! There's no need to help him!
What are you saying, Toki?!
The Prime Minister is your father, Toki.
How about a little concern for him?
His father?!
Then that's all the more reason, is it not?!
Not interested.
Where are you going?!
On a date. See you.
A date, at this hour?
Good grief, what is he thinking?
I'm sure he is thinking along his own lines.
It's all right. He will return.
We should be more concerned
about what we will do next.
About Hitomi?
Yes, he...
...is someone who's never let
any of us know what he's thinking.
The cat is talking?!
Ah, yes, Yuki has gone Lost, as well.
Yuki?
So you turn into a
cat when you go Lost, do you?
That's right. It's a real hassle.
By the way, Miss Sakurakoji,
after taking Hitomi's attack,
are you physically all right?
I'm perfectly fine.
Is that right?
For crying out loud, what a fool
you are, exposing yourself to that.
W-What do you mean, fool?!
You could have been killed!
I just... didn't want anyone else to die.
That again? How can you be so...
I won't have it!
I won't have... anybody dying.
"Episode 8: 'King & Soldier, Child & House'"
Are you all right, men?
Boss! It'll take more than this
to kill those of us in the Kizakura-gumi!
That's right!
We're fine!
Men...
I have to admit, though,
that long-haired bastard...
He really did use a weird technique.
Just who was that guy?
Hitomi has a special ability
over the power of electric shocks.
Those dead men who showed
up at the school yesterday?
Their bodies were controlled by Hitomi.
He also is a former Code: Breaker.
Three years ago,
he disappeared from our sight.
Then, the Prime Minister
is his former superior, is he not?
Why would he abduct him?
Revenge.
He did say revenge.
Does he have something
against the Prime Minister?
Even supposing that
Hitomi held some grudge,
if he wanted to get him back,
he could kill him outright,
without any kidnapping.
Some other objective, then?
Probably.
What could Hitomi be trying to do?
I don't know.
What I am sure of is that he
used the police chief and that gang
to get ready for something.
The abduction of the Prime Minister
may be the culmination of that.
Damn it!
Why did Hitomi turn on us?!
Oji...
Number one...
...didn't use to be someone who did this.
The Number one that
we all know is gone now.
Guys... You thought a lot of Hitomi.
Hitomi was the Code: Breakers'
leader, respected by all.
Whatever the past may be,
I will burn up all who fall into evil.
Even if they were once my friend!
Sissy!
Nobody is here today.
Sissy...
Good, you're safe.
I'm all right, Toki.
You came because you
were worried. I'm delighted.
You don't mean... your memories...
What do you mean?
And also, who are you?
Oh yeah, I'm going
shopping with Papa tomorrow!
I can't wait!
I promise I'll save you from this.
Huh? What?
Nothing at all.
I won't have... anybody dying.
Why is she so insistent?
Could it be fate?
Yeah. It has turned out just as we feared.
Still...
It's all right. No matter what happens,
Sakura is still our daughter.
Boss! The doctor has arrived!
Oh, glad to hear it!
We have to go greet him.
"Graduation Ceremony"
What the?
Father!
The doctor is... Huh?
Ogami... What are you doing?
Ah, you're looking
through that album, huh?
That sure takes me back.
What's this, here?
Finger-lacing.
Not finger-hooking?
Finger-hooking sounds
painful, does it not?
Better to just lace them all up.
You do this, and by
grasping each other's fingers,
it forms a handclasp that
allows for an exchange of good cheer.
Ever since I was little, I would
exchange good cheer over and over,
with my father, my mother,
and everyone in the household.
It's a Sakurakoji family tradition.
I see. You sure do love your family, huh?
Both you, and your parents.
Although, there are no photos of
you as a baby, considering.
Have you always been so rambunctious,
that they couldn't take any pictures of you?
Ah, that's not surprising.
I was abandoned as a child, after all.
Ogami...
Do you have a moment?
Sakura is not our biological daughter.
She was laid at our
main gate a long time ago.
She was a terrible sight,
and had blood spattered on her.
Blood spatter?
Yes, but luckily, she was unhurt.
She was just covered
in a massive amount of blood.
As terrible as she appeared,
she must have
experienced something awful.
That could have been the trigger
that made Sakura reject the deaths
of others as strongly as she does.
Ever since that day, we have been
anxious that the day would come
when Sakura would
be struck by tragedy again.
We wanted her to live a happy life, if possible.
However, it appears
that isn't in the cards for her.
Honestly, I don't understand
the kinds of powers you all have.
But I want you to protect Sakura!
I want you to rescue her
from any mishap! I beg you!
What's the matter, Number five?
I was thinking about Hitomi.
Yeah, you two were close, huh, Number five?
You, too, Yuki.
He just told me to do whatever I felt like.
That means he trusted you, right?
Hmm, maybe it did.
Hitomi always let things go
without clearly saying anything,
so he was hard to get a handle on.
That's true. Did he say
anything to you, Number five?
When I was little,
I lost my family in an accident.
I found it tough to be the only survivor.
I went through a wild period, too.
But when I met Hitomi,
he said something to me.
What's that?
"If you've got time to run wild,
you could always just sleep."
Huh?
Hitomi was complaining about being
so busy, he had no time to sleep.
He was saying he couldn't
believe that I let my wild behavior
cut into my sleeping time.
When I heard that,
it made everything getting
on my nerves seem ridiculous.
That sounds like Number one, all right.
Number one sure has changed, huh?
He sure has.
Whoops...
I went and fell asleep.
I've gone and put everybody out, haven't I?
What if he were to come to my place?
I'm such an idiot! There had
to be some other, better way!
Man, how underwhelming.
Ogami!
For a rarebreed like you to get discouraged,
like normal people do, is so disappointing.
I-I'm not discouraged...
It's absurd.
The reason this whole business
started is because I went Lost.
And if it wasn't enough
that I feel small about this,
why should you have to be
troubled by it, too, Miss Sakurakoji?
D-Don't you act so stuck up!
Because if you go getting discouraged,
you're going to make fools out of those
who believe in and follow you.
The boy's got it right, Miss Sakura!
Miss Sakura, injuries
like these are no big deal!
You'd be treating us like strangers
if you didn't bring home your school pals
when they're being chased by bad guys!
Guys...
The next time that bastard shows up,
we'll turn the tables on him!
We're sorry to have
let you face that kind of danger
while we were here with you, Miss Sakura.
We're really glad you're safe.
No! No! If I face them like this,
it will just make them worry!
It's on me! I'm the one
who needs more training!
Letting myself be caught by
that scrawny man is a huge screw-up!
Daisuke, train me harder!
That's more like it!
We used to be like that once.
Yep. All centered around Hitomi.
I sure wish we could all
fight like we did then again.
We can.
Oji, do you believe in Hitomi?
I'd like to. There must be some reason for this.
She's right. Number one is
acting like a different person now.
Something happened to him.
Guys...
Hmph, what nonsense!
I'm not interested in what
might have happened to Hitomi.
Toki...
I'm just pissed off, and I won't
rest until I've slugged him one.
The great Toki will knock some
sense back into that Hitomi jerk!
With that much settled,
let's all split up and search
for Hitomi and the Prime Minister.
It's "Let's go-go time!"
Yeah!
Wow, there's nothing here.
Eden takes care of things left behind.
Though I didn't think anything
was left here in the first place.
What is it, Yuki?
No, no leads here, either.
All right.
Ogami, why did Hitomi
abduct the Prime Minister?
If you know him going back,
there must be something
that comes to mind, is there not?
Ogami, were you and Hitomi...
That's none of your business.
Ogami!
Ogami...
- C'mon batter! C'mon, c'mon!
- All right!
Come in.
Have a seat, Miss Kanda.
I see. So the rarebreed's
power is greater than imagined.
Why did you not tell me in advance
that Miss Sakurakoji was a rarebreed?
Because you were once under Hitomi.
We wanted to avoid the risk
of any information being leaked.
Because of your relationship with Hitomi,
discrepancies in our contacts arose,
and we were also mistaken about Ogami
trying to immolate Sakurakoji Sakura.
Although, since she is a rarebreed,
we did not think there was any
concern about Ogami harming her.
You mean you suspected me?
Part of our job was to supervise you,
to make sure you weren't
secretly communicating with Hitomi.
We thought Hitomi would
try to make contact with you,
but that was a miscalculation.
I am... Ogami Rei's agent.
I have nothing to do with Hitomi!
Then are you able to dispose of Hitomi?
Yes, I can. I'll stake
my pride as an agent on it.
The world that Hitomi seeks...
The world that the Prime Minister seeks...
So that's it.
I understand, Ace.
Have you come up with any leads on Hitomi?
It's no use. I can't find anything.
It looks like killing the
police chief and that yakuza bunch
is now working against us.
And the Prime Minister's home?
Are you working to salvage it?
Of course.
Heike,
you're being awfully negligent,
considering, aren't you?
How do you mean?
You had to know that by getting
all the Code: Breakers together,
it would leave the area around
the Prime Minister shorthanded.
I am not the one who called you.
I'm not so sure.
It was your arbitrary
decision that sent in Yuki, right?
Do you doubt me?
You're surprisingly sharp-witted, huh?
Let's Illusion!
Why, you!
Huh?
It has begun.
What?!
This is the start of Hitomi's plan.
Number five!
Another explosion!
Magnificent! Such is the
shadow special ability for you.
A black guardian angel,
the only one among the Code: Breakers
that can defend lives against all attacks.
What is the meaning of this, Heike?!
I told you. Hitomi's plan has begun.
And with that, Oji,
I am going to need you to leave the area.
What?!
However excellent you may be at protecting,
in this situation, you will
be unable to avoid my attack!
Number five!!
Is that... a fire?
Ogami, what happened to you?
Heike!
Miss Sakurakoji, Ogami was looking for you.
Ogami was?
You are being targeted by Hitomi, after all.
Please, come with me.
He's in here?
This is a secret base.
Oh! A Code: Breaker
secret base?! This is so exciting!
It sure is dark. Are there no lights?
Prime Minister Fujiwara!
What's going on here, Heike?!
As promised, I have
brought you the rarebreed, Ace.
Now you will allow me to join you, right?
What are you saying, Heike?!
That's!
I have decided to turn on the Code: Breakers,
and side with Hitomi, instead.
You are a gift to that end.
Please be a good hostage, Miss Sakurakoji.
One day, you, too, will know
where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city,
unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following
wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from
which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear; the answers
lie beyond the darkness
Bullets of sorrow, sneering light,
and a dark resolution laid bare.
Next time,
"Code: Breaker" episode 9, "Stopped Time."
Blue flame, light up
the darkness of betrayal!