That's far enough!
"Nyanmaru"
Nyanmaru will protect... the others!
Nyanmaru...
Why is there no final
piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence
facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
Episode 7: Sakura, In the Light
- ♪ Nyan-Nyan-Nyanmaru, friend to everyone... ♪
- He's not in any mortal danger?
- Correct.
- ♪ Kind-hearted ally to all kitties... ♪
- Code: Breakers use special abilities,
- ♪ More sorrowful than anyone else... ♪
- but if they overuse them, the abilities disappear,
- and their bodies get thrown out of order.
- ♪ More sorrowful than anyone else... ♪
- ♪ about the fragility of lives passing away... ♪
- Which is what "Lost" is.
- Lately, Master had been using his power too much,
- ♪ about the fragility of lives passing away... ♪
- so I figured it was going to happen soon.
- It's okay. It will take him a
day to recover, but he'll get better.
- ♪ Before long, he remembers everything... ♪
- Is that right? Mm, that is good!
- ♪ Slicing good and evil asunder... ♪
- Heike, you mentioned something
- about destiny and fate, so I was stunned.
- ♪ Slicing good and evil asunder... ♪
- But in short, it's almost like he's gone hungry, right?
I have to admit, I was surprised
that you are a Code: Breaker, too.
Not to mention you being
part of their team as well, Teacher.
As well as... Yuki?
What's his story?
I am an agent of Eden.
Our job is to give support
to the Code: Breakers.
Support?
Ogami is Code 06.
That makes him the
lowest-ranking one among us.
As such, he has an exclusive
support staff member assigned.
Ogami is the lowest ranked?
That maddeningly polite Ogami
is the lowest ranked?
Yuki here is Code 03.
He uses sound special abilities.
And while he's not
here today, Toki is Code 04.
"Nyanmaru"
Putting a Nyanmaru sticker on
Ogami won't make him any better.
I like Nyanmaru.
Huh?
Number six, your Lost looks
hard on you. Hurry and get better.
He is Freedom.
Ahh... Mm-hmm.
Yuki is concerned
about Ogami in his own way.
Oh, with that in mind,
Heike, what number are you?
I am Code 02. While I am a
Code: Breaker, at the same time,
I also judge the others.
Points off for that.
You don't say.
Which means, there is also a
number five and a number one, right?
I believe you have already met Code 05.
Oh, do you mean, the girl on the bike?
I knew it! Then, number one would be...
W-Well... We'll be in
deep if we're attacked again.
We should relocate,
so we can keep Master protected.
Oh! That certainly is true.
You think this is his doing, too, don't you?
It's possible that they
know about Master's apartment.
We'll have to consider where to take him.
What if he were to come to my place?
No! It's too dangerous!
Teacher, you know what kind of house
the Sakurakoji home is, right?
Welcome home, Miss Sakura!
Mm-hmm. I am home.
The Kizakura-gumi...
the strongest and most preeminent
"goodfella" organization in Japan.
And the daughter of the
clan's chief, Sakurakoji Gotoku...
is Sakurakoji Sakura.
Wow...
Miss Sakura, who are these others?
Mm-hmm, this is my upperclassman,
my homeroom teacher, and friends.
Friends?
Welcome home, Sakura!
Ma'am!
Boss!
W-W-What happened?
He fought for me,
and for the rest of our classmates.
I would like to look after him
here at home until he recovers.
He is a dear friend, right?
Sure! Use the guest room.
Thank you very much, Mother!
He fought for all of us. That's why!
Nyanmaru?
Oh, yes, your friend is here!
My friend?
I asked him to wait in the guest room.
Sakura is home! Huh?
Who do you mean, my friend?
He said his name was Toki.
Toki?!
What are Yuki and Heike doing here, too?
You idiot!
Hey, stop that! Let me go!
- I found Number four.
- Let me go! Put me down!
That's... Toki?
Why does he look like that?
Hmph, he went Lost.
H-He gets smaller?
Lost forms vary from person to person.
Toki becomes a child when he is Lost.
What's this about
being lost and getting smaller?
M-Mother! Th-Th-That
is definitely, without a doubt,
one-hundred-percent my friend Toki!
Hmm, in that case, okay.
There's a banquet in the
great hall, so come right away.
Y-Yes, Mother!
So, I received word from Eden.
They said that Ogami was Lost,
so I came to back him up.
Toki, you are Lost, too, are you not?
Have you told Eden about you being Lost?
You have not told them, have you?!
"Kagemaru"
Dah! Don't put stickers on me!
It'll make you better, Number four.
It will not!
You all get along well, don't you?
And with that, we welcome
Sakura's friends to our banquet!
Ma'am, we thank you for this food!
What is it, Miss Sakurakoji?
Uh, nothing...
Heike, why are you working?
Yes, why, indeed?
What did Ogami say?
To wipe out evil.
Is that right?
Burn away.
As hurt as he gets...
...by himself...
Sakura! You drinking?
Hmm? Toki, underage drinking is wrong.
It's not alcohol! It's juice!
But you're drunk, are you not?!
Huh? It's the effect of being Lost.
I get drunk on juice.
You do?
Toki, points off.
Uh-huh, you're just acting big, Heike.
And you don't even have any eyebrows!
No eyebrows!
Toki, it sounds like you're
going to need a spanking.
Huh? No, you don't
have to get so serious!
Thanks for keeping Number six here.
It is no big deal.
I have to return the favor
for protecting our classmates.
Besides...
Ogami and Toki are both in a tight spot.
I will have to do what I can!
The others can't fight! Nyanmaru will have to!
You're Nyanmaru...
Let me go!
Thanks so much for the food
and the bath, Miss Sakurakoji.
Oh, no. I'm terribly sorry
that the hospitality isn't that great.
I will protect you, Nyanmaru.
Such boorish clouds,
to interrupt me while I'm reading.
Standing guard with
your nose in the air, huh?
Yes, now, since you're Lost, Toki.
Toki, I was watching everything
that happened in today's event.
They were clearly split into two groups...
a team that attacked Ogami,
and a team that attacked Miss Sakurakoji.
Why do you think Hitomi
would set up something like that?
You're saying that Sakura was targeted, too?
Miss Sakurakoji is a rarebreed.
It's not surprising that
Hitomi would show interest in her.
But...
If he was going to
kidnap Miss Sakurakoji,
there must be simpler
ways for him to do it.
I can't fathom why he
would intentionally go after her
while Ogami was there.
And instead, if his
objective was to attack Ogami,
I don't understand why
he would divide his forces.
Good point. Ultimately,
it just forced Ogami to go Lost.
Just forced him to go Lost. You're right...
Could there have been some other objective?
Miss Sakurakoji...
Master, you're awake?
Kanda... Is this
Miss Sakurakoji's house?
Yes, it is.
I'm terribly sorry.
If I could have prevented
those men from attacking...
No need to apologize.
I was careless, as well.
Master, those men were the
agents who have gone missing.
What's more...
Yeah. They were controlled
by special ability powers.
Then, it would have to be...
No doubt about it. The enemy is
the former Code: Breaker, Code 01,
Hitomi.
What?
Code 05, head to Sakurakoji
Sakura's house immediately.
What? I thought Yuki
and Toki were over there.
Code 04, Toki, is Lost. He'll be no help.
Acknowledged.
What the hell are all the Code: Breakers doing?
You're interested in the katana?
You look like you're feeling better, Ogami.
I'll let you borrow this.
You've seen too much death, haven't you?
I can tell. That's the
world you've been living in.
You've lost the dread that
comes with taking people's lives.
That means you've also lost
the interest that comes with living.
Sakura is a good daughter.
If anything happens to Sakura,
there will be a price to pay, Ogami.
Men!
Hitomi!
Sakura!
I will protect Nyanmaru!
Watch it. You might
hit Miss Sakurakoji, right?
And is that all the power you've got?
Shut up!
No matter. Sleepy time, kitty.
Yuki!
And you walk right into going Lost.
As your teacher, I'm disappointed.
Ogami!
Please let Miss Sakurakoji go, Hitomi!
You think you can shoot me?
Hitomi...
Your swordsmanship
has gotten a lot better, huh?
As your teacher,
I feel honored. However...
You can't beat me, Ogami.
If you get in my way, farewell.
Dance!
Oh, Toki! Back from being Lost, huh?
It's the whole Code: Breaker lineup.
Hey! You're still Lost,
aren't you? Keep back!
This kill is mine!
Why have you fallen into evil?
What is your purpose?
Revenge.
Yes, revenge against Eden.
You've changed.
Before, you used to hate revenge.
Is he a friend of his?
If you've fallen into evil...
...then I'll cut you down!
How can you become such a dog of Eden?
Eden has nothing to do with it!
I am doing this of my own will!
I'll bet Eden has just put you up to this!
Ogami!
Don't go acting so poised!
You're not even gonna take
your hands outta your pockets?!
You sure are spirited, Toki. Hmm?
Ogami...
I see, so your twenty-four hours are up, huh?
Hitomi, I don't know what kind
of grudge you've got against Eden,
but what you're doing is a load of bunk.
You're the same old straight-arrow
as ever, huh, Ogami?
An eye for an eye...
a tooth for a tooth...
evil for evil!
Take this!
It's no use. Not against my lightning.
Ogami! Toki!
Now then...
Do you think you can beat me?
We won't know unless we try, right?
That's far enough, former Code 01, Hitomi.
We cannot allow you to have the rarebreed.
There's a name that
takes me back. Code 01, huh?
Let me show you the reason...
...why I was called that back in the day.
What power!
Death to those who stand against me.
Farewell, Code: Breakers!
No...
No!
No!!
Miss Sakurakoji!
Sakura!
What the?
Outstanding, Sakura!
Better than I expected!
Sakura...
W-What is so outstanding?!
You're being facetious!
Hey, what are you doing?!
How can you be so reckless?!
Please, stay back!
I got a pretty good show out of it,
so maybe I'll give up
on the rarebreed for now.
Well, it was about time I left.
You're not getting away!
There's no need to fight you any longer today.
The moment you Code: Breakers
all gathered yourselves here,
the battle was decided.
We all gathered? You don't mean!
Code 02! The Prime Minster
has been abducted by
someone with special abilities!
I'm in pursuit of the culprit!
Rendezvous with me! Hurry!
It's been fun. Good night,
Code: Breakers.
Damn it!
The Prime Minister?
Hitomi!
Kidnapping the Prime Minister...
You mean business, huh, Code 01?
One day, you, too, will know
where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city,
unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following
wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from
which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear; the answers
lie beyond the darkness
This is bad. I was off my
game before going Lost, all right.
I got beaten pretty easily.
Next time, "Code: Breaker" episode 8,
"King & Soldier, Child & House."
I will burn up all who fall into evil.
Even if they were once my friend!