As decided by Eden Supreme Council I hereby appoint you a Code:Breaker.
『Hitomi : Age 16』
Thank you.
We have high expectations of you, Code 06.
The World That People See
Episode 10
An eye for an eye; a tooth for a tooth;
the thunder of judgment for the evil.
code:06     『Hitomi』
You filthy dog!
The newly appointed Code:Breaker...
seems to be doing a very good job for us.
Indeed, we predict that he'll be climbing the ranks.
It seems that you did manage to find a good talent there.
Yes.
Everything's alright now.
You can't catch me!
Wait up! Wait up! Wait up!
What are you looking at, Hitomi?
I'm watching these children.
I want to create a world where the children can smile forever.
A place free from the cries of grief, a peaceful world.
My abilities might be insufficient but I'll lend you a hand.
Sure! Together, as Code:Breakers.
『Hitomi : Age 20』
The target is heading west at the third block intersection.
I'm still chasing him.
Roger, I'll be on standby at the fourth block.
No! It's a trap!
05! Haruya!
1:20 AM
What happened to Haruya was a shame.
Hitomi, prior to his death, as of today, you are promoted to Code: 05.
Onii-san, over here!
Wait up!
In order to protect their smile...
Code: 03, you and Code: 06 enter from the right.
code:03     『Hitomi』
Roger.
This time we're facing a somewhat worrying enemy.
『Hitomi : Age 26』
They're special ability users who have turned against Eden.
We found out that they're plotting a terrorist attack through clandestine investigation.
Tonight, you are to exterminate them.
Shit! Is everyone okay?!
Everyone's burnt to crisp.
Bastard!
01!
How dare you do this to them!
So you're the Code:Breaker called Hitomi, huh?
You're as strong as the rumors say.
No wonder my crew was done in.
However, do you really think you can take me down while holding on to that corpse?!
Everyone...
Everyone's dead!
You should be happy you got out of there alive.
Although one of the enemies got away, we still accomplished our objective.
The terrorist group is virtually annihilated.
There's no point in declaring victory, with this many casualties...
It's true that the situation is grave.
Only us two are left since those four Code:Breakers were defeated.
It will be necessary to recruit new talents to replace them.
Heike.
How well does Eden understand our special abilities?
What do you mean?
Code: 06's abilities went haywire.
She uses water abilities, but the water turned back on her like a beast.
It wasn't the enemy that killed her.
Sounds similar to how Code: 04 die previously.
Exactly.
Look into it for me. I want to know what happened.
Understood, Ace.
Ace?
As of today, you are Code:Breaker Code: 01.
In other words, you're the Ace.
I understand, Heike.
Then, I won't let anyone die...
For as long as I'm the Ace.
c
co
cod
code
code:
code:0
code:03
code:03        Ten
code:03        Tenpou
code:03        Tenpouin
code:03        Tenpouin Yu
code:03        Tenpouin Yuki
c
co
cod
code
code:
code:0
code:04
code:04         Toki
c
co
cod
code
code:
code:0
code:05
code:05      Ha
code:05      Hachi
code:05      Hachiouji
code:05      Hachiouji Rui
c
co
cod
code
code:
code:0
code:06
code:06      Oga
code:06      Ogami
code:06      Ogami Rei
Work diligently, friends.
Why is there no final piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Code:Breakers?!
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
An eye for an eye; a tooth for a tooth; evil for evil.
Burn to ashes.
Ogami Rei-kun. He sure has some stunning abilities.
Indeed, Eden's data shows that he has great talent.
However, he's dangerous.
Why?
He's too caught up with his will to extinguish evil.
A trap?
Whatcha' doing, Ogami?
This is why you're stuck as Code: 06, you know.
Toki!
Hey, what's with that greeting? And here I came all the way to help you out.
You should at least say: "Thank you, Toki-sama".
Right, Ogami-kun?
You can't get careless, Toki-kun.
I wasn't getting... Huh?
You too, Ogami-kun. Your mission was to rescue this child.
You can't just put all effort into burning evil away and forget about the more important thing.
Well now, let's go home.
This way!
Wait!
Ogami-kun, why did you become a Code:Breaker?
To burn evil to the ground.
What if you felt death drawing close to you during a fight,
and knew you didn't have much time left, what would you do?
I'd fight to burn every enemy to the ground until my last breath.
You're really something else.
I'd like to fight to my last breath in order to save someone.
Why would you go so far for the sake of others?
That's just how I am.
Ogami-kun,
Code:Breakers punish the evil, but that's not all.
We also protect the people that the law cannot.
Since we have these strong powers, we must protect the weak.
That's why these special abilities were bestowed on us.
That's how I feel.
Even if you might lose your life in battle?
If it means that someone is saved, then I don't mind.
Besides,
even if I die, as long as you remember me, I will still live on.
That would be enough for me.
But, what if I die before you?
I won't let that happen.
I'll protect you.
01!
Did he go Lost?
This is...!
Yes.
The special ability user that killed our friends
and wiped out almost all of the Code:Breakers...
has returned.
Can we fight him, Ace?
Of course.
It's time.
Begin the operation.
Roger.
You better not hold me back, Ogami!
As expected, there are enemies in all the rooms.
Take them down at once.
This is already a dead zone!
Come out, filth.
You're just doing what pleases you, huh?
I don't need to hear that from you.
Huh? Are you that dog from back then?
I'll take revenge for my dead comrades.
You may have those strong special abilities, but aren't you still just a dog of Eden?
You're so boring.
01!
Oh, the dogs keep rumbling in.
How's this: Why don't all of you join me?
Join you?
You can use your special abilities and live freely!
When you are as powerful as us, you can have all the money and women you desire.
You really don't have to be Code:Breakers to fight evil, you know.
You're such a fool.
What?
We manage to find bastards like you because we are Code:Breakers.
Anyway, the government pays all of our expenses.
You dog...
They sure are useful people.
The Code:Breakers destroy evil.
If we were to commit atrocities like you do
we would be killed by other Code:Breakers.
You can use your special abilities in whatever way you like.
However, we Code:Breakers do no tolerate evil.
Don't act like some white knight!
Oi oi, who's next?
I'll send all of you to the other side!
Too bad, but that isn't going to happen.
What?!
I will not let you kill another Code:Breaker.
Don't fuck with me!
My body...  Is moving on its own...
When I touched you, I sent commands to your brain.
You'll be burned to death by your own ability.
Die in regret for using your special ability for evil.
Work is finally over!
Is everyone all right?
Aren't you the one who's hurt?
I'm fine. If everyone else is all right, this wound is nothing.
I've rinsed it with water, please use it to cool down your hand.
Ah, thanks.
01, you beat up the meanest bad guy again, you're so awesome.
It's because I'm the Ace. It's only natural.
Uh, is that how it is?
When I retire, I'll have you work to the bone instead.
Aw, that'll be a pain.
Ogami-kun did well too.
Ogami-kun!
What is it? Our work is done...
I'll be counting on you, Ogami-kun.
Yeah.
With these members, we're going to be the strongest team of all.
No one will lose their life from now.
No one.
It's alright now, everyone.
I'm over here!
Wait!
Come on, come on!
What's so funny?
I'm just happy.
Don't you understand, Ogami-kun?
It's not a riddle, so please just say it straight.
Also, could you drop the "kun"?
I'll stop it when you become stronger than I am...
Ogami-kun.
What is this all about?
It's the case about the abilities going haywire, the one you told me to investigate.
The intervals between when they become Lost gradually increases,
until they are eventually unable to become Lost anymore.
Their abilities go haywire and they die.
This kind of phenomenon has occurred many times before.
Code:End?
That's what they call it at Eden.
Heike, did Eden know about this?
Most likely.
And they kept this hidden from us!
This is ridiculous.
I've tried so hard because I don't want anyone to die again...
Even so...
Code:End? Is this supposed to be the fate of a Code:Breaker?!
If this is true, it's just too miserable.
Hitomi-san, what's going on? Why did you call me out here?
Did something happen?
When that has been completed...
Is there something wrong with the Sky Tower?
When it's completed, I suppose a lot of people will come to visit with their lovers and families.
Indeed.
Since you called me here, I brought this for you.
It's the documents for tomorrow's work.
Don't slack off.
A Code:Breaker's work...
Ogami-kun, would you...
What?
Would you go far away with me?
No, nevermind.
Ogami and the others can't escape from Eden.
Even if they managed to run, they would just be chased by Eden until their death.
They can only live as Code:Breakers.
Telling them the truth about Code:End would be like handing them to their death sentence.
I will let them live normal lives.
With no parents or siblings, they will die being
unable to express their feelings to their loved ones.
That's far too miserable.
Even if I have to negotiate with the Prime Minister directly...
Thank you for the documents, Ogami-kun.
Why did you want to meet me here?
Let's do our best together on tomorrow's job.
Yeah.
I am Code: 01.
The one who bears the title "Ace".
I have to do it for these kids.
What's up?
Master!
Hitomi-san has... Hitomi-san has...
What happened?
Last night, he attacked the Prime Minister, killed many of the guards, and fled.
His wherabouts are unknown.
Code: 01, Hitomi tried to assassinate the Prime Minister.
Fortunately, the Prime Minister was unharmed, but Hitomi's crime is grave.
From this day on, Hitomi is stripped of his authorities as a Code:Breaker.
Therefore, he is to be considered as a wanted criminal.
Even though you said that we would fight together, you broke your promise.
Doing something like this...
Why would he do something like attack the Prime Minister?
Didn't he go to talk things over with him?
What happened, Hitomi-senpai-dono?
Well then, let's start!
I will rebuild this broken world.
Bitten on the hand by my own pet dog, how ironic.
Until Prime Minister Fujiwara's Public Execution
Greetings, dear citizens!
As you can see, in 60 minutes I'm going to execute Prime Minister Fujiwara.
Until Prime Minister Fujiwara's Public Execution
At the same time, the explosives that are set up all over the country,
will take 50,000 of you with him.
It's futile to escape.
Hitomi!
One day, you, too, will know where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city, unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear. The answers lie beyond the darkness
The disaster widens, the terror runs wild, now the pages of our destiny are being written.
Next time: Code:Breaker Episode 11:
50,000 Hostages.
As decided by the Eden Supreme Council, I hereby appoint you a Code:Breaker.