Please watch your step
I can't give him something to eat today.
Stop the bus!
Huh?
The next stop is just ahead. Just sit down and wait-
People are being burned!
Call 110! Quickly!
Are you a policeman? There's people-!
So someone was burning, but where is he?
Standard flames can't burn things completely that they don't leave a trace behind.
Are you sure you didn't dream it?
No way!
I'm...
certain.
Maybe those scorches are
from some homeless guy's fire or something.
It can't be.
Why is there no final piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
God's Great Judgment
Episode 1
Ippon! Break!
Th-Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
Next up, Sato!
Yes, if you please!
If you please!
Fortitude and Vigor
Last night...
Just what was that?
Ippon! Break!
Nicely done!
Sakurakouji, thank you
for spending time with our meager little club here.
Not at all.
Training with the club members is truly eye-opening.
Sakurakouji-san sure is fantastic, huh?
She's usually so neat and smart,
but when you see her doing aikido, she really looks cool, huh?
On top of which, she always earns top grades.
If I could have Sakurakouji-san as my girlfriend, I wouldn't care if the whole world turned against me.
Yoo-hoo! Good morning, Sakura!
A good-morning to you, Aoba.
What's the matter, Sakura? You're looking kind of tight-lipped.
D-Do I?
No, there's nothing wrong.
All right, then.
Ah, Kanda-sensei! Good morning!
Good morning, Takatsu-san, Sakurakouji-san.
Huh? Who's this?
Ah, this is a transfer student who will be in our class as of today.
His name is...
I'm Ogami Rei. It's a pleasure to meet you.
Hold the phone! Ogami-kun's pretty handsome, isn't he?
He has a cool and somewhat mysterious air.
High points!
Okay, okay, quiet down.
For reasons having to do with his parents' work,
Ogami-kun is moving here on his own.
Everyone, let's all make sure he feels welcome.
There is no mistake, it's him...
The boy from last night...
Overseas, huh? You must rock at English!
No, not at all.
What countries did you go to?
I've been in Europe a lot the last few years.
What is it, Sakura? Taking an interest in Ogami-kun?
That is not it...
Ogami!
What is it, Sakurakouji-san?
I wish to speak with you alone. Come with me.
Very well.
Terrible news! Sakurakouji-san is gonna declare her love to the transfer student!
What?
No way!
I don't believe it!
My dream bride!
Sakura is amazing! How bold!
But those two would make the perfect couple, wouldn't they?
So, what did you need?
I shall ask you point-blank.
Where were you and what were you doing last night?
I was at my job.
Your job? Then I ask you:
By using that glove, are you not concealing the burns you received last night
in the park when you burned those people to death?
What was that? I can't hear them!
Well? If I am wrong, then remove the glove.
There are no burns?!
This is a good-luck charm.
When I was a child, I hurt someone with this hand.
A certain person gave this to me to make sure it would never happen again.
Is that all it is?
Yes, that's all it is...
But yesterday...
Anything else?
U-Uh, I apologize for bothering you.
No, it's all right.
I hope we can get along as classmates.
Sakurakouji-san.
H-Hold on! Sakura, what happened?
Indeed, this is an unexpected development.
Huh?! You don't mean-?!
He turned you down?
He what? He rejected Sakurakouji-san?
Who do you think you are, Ogami Rei?!
It's not possible for him to cause Sakura grief!
Ogami! You've just turned the whole world against you!
Ah, this is exasperating!
However, I shall not give up!
Whoa... Sakura, this is the first time you've gotten so worked up over a boy, isn't it?
I swear, I will uncover the truth about him!
Wow, I have to say, no matter how often I see it, your way of eating is so charming.
That jerk-!
Ogami-kun, you're so cool!
You really are infatuated, huh, Sakura?
Yeah, I cannot afford to take my eyes off of him.
Ogami-kun seems so nice.
It's no surprise that you'd be interested in him.
Nice?
He eluded me, huh?
They say the culprit returns to the scene of the crime.
I shall await him here.
Wait up! Wait up!
Wait up, I say!
Were there people really being burned here?
Was that some sort of illusion?
Here, eat this. I am sorry I brought you nothing yesterday.
When that old man gave you food, he would do this-
Are you really still not used to me?!
O-Ogami!
You really do talk like that to everyone, don't you?
It's okay. I just thought it was the firm tone of a warrior.
What? Are you saying it doesn't fit my image?
No, I was thinking it's cool how you're not submissive.
C-Cool is too much.
I'm just a little... My family is a bit odd, is all...
Oh, that dog is quite timid around people.
Come here.
The dog...
You just didn't have enough trust in people, huh?
Whoa! Please, don't lick me so much!
Ogami-kun seems so nice.
I hope we can get along as classmates.
Come on! Come on!
I guess he's not a bad person.
Sakurakouji-san, what's this dog's name?
Dog.
That's a nice name, huh?
Is it a stray?
No. Her master, a homeless old man… was killed.
The culprit is a group known as G-Falcon.
They seem to call themselves that because of the falcon tattoos they all have on their bodies.
When this group commits a crime,
the gang that is over them keep everything hushed up.
That's what Father says.
Your father?
Hence no one can bring them to justice.
Even the police pretend not to see them.
Do you want to take revenge against these culprits?
Would you like to take up justice, and bring the hammer down upon them?
No!
I just... That old man...
He lived without anyone knowing him,
and died without anyone noticing.
That's something I can't tolerate.
Sakurakouji-san, it's okay as long as you remember him.
Even if the rest of the world forgets him, you should remember him.
I will not forget. No matter what. Not ever.
Besides,
you don't need the laws of this country to judge them.
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth, evil for evil.
The code of Hammurabi?
The evil for evil part is gratuitous, Ogami.
You finally smiled at me, huh?
I thought maybe you had taken a disliking to me.
I apologize for that, Ogami. I had my doubts about you.
What has become of Ogami Rei.
His placement is complete.
All that remains is for him to begin, Prime Minister.
Good. All according to plan.
Assuming it wasn't Ogami, then what was it exactly?
Was it an illusion after all?
Ogami-kun, want to come with us for some karaoke?
Sakura is coming, too.
No, I have something to take care of.
Hey, who do you think I'm doing this for?
Huh?
Don't ''huh'' me!
I'm sorry, but I have to work today.
Oh, you do?
Ogami, now that you mention it, what work do you do?
I'm a cleaner. A trash man.
I see. Most admirable.
You see? It looks like they're already calling me.
Hey, what is this?! All of a sudden, you're on close terms?!
There is nothing specially irregular about our contact, is there?
No way, no way, that's a hyper-fast connection!
What is it?
It's about today's job.
Take out the trash, just as was planned.
What are you going to do about Sakurakouji Sakura?
I'm not going to do anything much.
Just like I always have,
I'm going to eliminate her.
When will you finally take a liking to me?
Good grief...
Help me!
W-What is it?
Like I said, we haven't been able to get in contact with our pals since two nights ago.
You guys hang out here, right? I'm asking you if you've seen anything.
I-I don't know anything, really!
Ah, you're useless!
H-Help!
Stop that!
I have just dialed 110! The police will arrive here shortly!
The police? Oh, right, the police!
Falcon tattoos... Then they're...
G-Falcon! The group that killed that old man.
Young lady, you shouldn't go sticking your nose into everything.
We're just concerned about some of our pals that vanished here.
They vanished... here...
Huh? What is it, young lady? You know something about it?
Was it two nights ago that you say your pals vanished?
Hey! Is she in on it?
Sounds like you really do know something. Hey...
Now then, why don't you tell me everything you know?
Two nights ago... they vanished... Then it did happen.
What are you mumbling to yourself about? Tell us what you know, now-!
Now that I know it really happened, that will do.
I have nothing more to say to you!
Why, you little...!
It hurts!
Turn yourselves in to the police-
If you don't answer us then we'll just have to beat it out of you directly.
M-My body won't move...
Here, take this belt! Tie her up!
Stupid girl. You could have left the homeless guy alone,
but you tried to help him, and this is what you get!
What the hell is this?!
Dog!
Knock it off!
You're not getting me!
Stop that!
I'm open! I'm open!
Pass it to me!
Nice! Nice!
Way to go!
Hey, hold it!
Stop it already! The dog has nothing to do with this!
I am your opponent!
What's she talking about?
Is this the time to be worrying about a dog?
Just you wait! I will get you to a hospital right away-
Pesky girl.
If you wanna get pummeled that badly, then you'll have your wish.
All you want, after you answer us.
Are you in pain?
Who are you?!
Ogami!
Your organs, and many of your bones... There's no saving you, huh?
It's amazing that you're still alive at all.
You wanted to protect Sakurakouji-san, didn't you?
You did well.
What the hell do you want?!
Ogami! Hurry and get it to the hospital.
Ogami, please!
I will put you out of your misery now.
Ogami?
Ogami... You...!
What? You killed it, didn't you? That's no fun.
If you kill it, it won't respond, and where's the fun in-
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth,
evil for evil.
Huh? What are you talking-
Burn to ashes.
It's started, hasn't it?
I'm waiting for you, Ogami-kun.
W-What the hell did you do?!
What? My job as a trash man.
I'll ask you one final question.
Will you turn yourselves in to be judged,
or would you rather die here?
Which will it be?
Screw you! You're the one who's gonna die!
I see. Well then, die here.
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth, evil for evil.
Ogami… Then it really was you!
It was as a classmate that I said I hoped we could be friends.
Burn to ashes.
One day, you, too, will know where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city, unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear. The answers lie beyond the darkness
Next time, Code:Breaker Episode 2,
"The Spiral Blue Flower, Blossoming in Flame."
I will burn everything up, until the end of my life!