Why is there no final piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
Fireball Man VS Devil Man
Fireball Man!
I'll get stronger and become a hero of justice, just like you.
A Banquet of Wishes
Episode 5
Impressive, however...
You won't be able to handle this!
What?!
You're useless.
Hey! Why are you running away?!
Wait!
Make yourselves useful.
Tabata-san,
the Code:Breakers have entered the premises.
I don't care if they're the devil;
I won't let them get in my way.
I still don't get why they would conduct research on special abilities at a government institution.
Well, the Code:Breakers are also a governmental entity.
What did you say?!
Ogami and I both get our orders from the Prime Minister.
Wh-, the Prime Minister?
That's right.
That's why not even politicians or the police can escape us.
Who are these children?
Probably kids with special abilities.
They're gathered from all over Japan and subjected to all kinds of tests.
What in the world is the government up to?
Beats me.
But it seems like they take good care of them, so it should be okay.
What is it?
Nothing...
I just wonder why those two guys outside suddenly ran out of power.
Didn't they get Lost?
You said that before.
What do you mean by "Lost"?
Ah, "Lost" is...
What's wrong?
Puppy!
It's almost like a hospital...
Well, that's what we've been told.
This is... for a hospital...
My, my, Code:Breakers,
welcome.
You're Tabata-san, aren't you?
How's your research on special abilities coming along?
Are those two muscle-bound guys we met earlier the fruit of your work?
They're no match for a real Code:Breaker yet.
That's Tabata Shigeru, a congressman.
I suppose you've heard his name at least.
So that means he's in charge of the research, eh?
Then, the government is really...
The issues starts from here.
How cruel.
Oh my, all the internal organs are gone.
Tabata-san, Eden is furious...
about you killing without their consent.
They never told you to trade with internal organs, did they?
Why did you do something like this?
It's none of your business.
You make our work sound so nasty.
Saving people is what we are doing.
There's no need for useless kids with weak special powers.
If so, then...
If we could at least put their organs to good use, it'd be best for everyone.
Screw you!
There's no way anyone would agree to that!
My, what a lively child.
Shall we take her apart?
As you say,
if you're useless, then there's no need for you.
See? You understand what we're talking about.
Would you two be of any use to me?
What?
If you can't make yourselves useful, I'll have no need for you.
However, I don't want your organs.
It doesn't have to be what's best for everyone.
Just burn to ashes!
Take this!
He evaporated it?
Ogami!
Sakura-chan, stay back.
Take this!
Ah, so close!
Even though I turned it to stone for you!
Hey, that's dangerous!
We didn't even have any business with you two to begin with!
You've seen too much, there's no way I can let you leave here alive!
Tsk, what a pain!
I'm gonna have your organs!
A Code:Breaker wouldn't try to run now, would he?!
Ugh, his powers are really annoying.
Toki-kun, there's something strange about him.
Why is he carrying around that large contraption?
As expected from a Code:Breaker.
What are you doing?!
Stop slacking off and give me more power!
You do realize what happens to the useless kids, don't you?
A surprise attack?!
That's low, Code:Breaker!
Attacking from behind, that's so dirty!
So that thing on his back does have some kind of function.
Then I'll just hit it directly!
What?!
Just kidding.
Are you surprised? This is made of carbon fiber.
You can't destroy it with your special ability.
You're really pissing me off.
Attacking from behind, you really are a naughty one!
Give me more power!
Or you'll end up like your brother!
Brother?
You're losing focus!
It's over.
A child?!
No more power, huh?
Such a useless child!
So that's what it was.
I do say, these brats are just no good.
They run out of power so quickly.
Bastard, you're the useless one!
Hang in there! Are you all right?
Kill them...
They said that my brother was weak, and cut him into pieces!
I could hear her voice.
My little sister was crying for me to save her.
But then I couldn't hear her anymore.
I couldn't hear my little sister's voice anymore!
Kill them...
Avenge my brother!
Kill them... I'm begging you!
Kill the ones who killed my little sister.
Damn! This is... Stop! Stop it!
This is just...
An eye for an eye; a tooth for a tooth;
and a hammer of justice for evil.
Thank you.
Brother...
Hey... Hey!
You can't! Open your eyes!
Hey!
Why did it have to come to this?
No!
No, no, no!
No, stop!
Burn to ashes.
Thank you.
You don't need to thank me.
After all, I'm just a demon killing other demons.
I can't erase your pain, nor can I bring the dead back to life.
Even so...
Thank you.
Shit! Shit!
You hypocrite!
Stay away!
Ogami!
Don't, Sakura-chan.
But, if he kills more people...
Sakura-chan, have you ever
thought about why heroes become heroes?
What about it?
Heroes are heroes, because they
kill evil people for the sake of justice.
Besides, your words filled with uncertainty won't reach him.
I'm not filled with uncertainty!
They cut my brother to pieces...
Kill... them!
Thank you.
You wouldn't understand...
Not someone like you!
Bastards like you can't understand my pain!
Daddy?
Daddy, what's wrong?
Who are these people?
Chisa!
Tabata's daughter?
Chisa-chan!
This guy here is a hero of justice, you see.
Really?!
Onii-chan is the Fireball Man?
You really came to see me!
Daddy told me that the Fireball Man would come and change the bad part in my stomach for a good one!
Thank you for coming, Fireball Man!
When I get better, I'll become a hero just like you!
Was Tabata trying to find an organ for his daughter?
So when you were ordered to
administer the research of special abilities,
you thought you could use that
as a cover to get your daughter an organ, didn't you?
But you know, Tabata-san.
Doing something like this just because
you have it within reach,
isn't that wrong?
Shut up!
Chisa needs an organ!
Do you think she can sit around and wait year after year for a donor?!
So for the sake of your daughter, you kill other children?
How selfish.
Shut up, shut up!
I don't need to take this from you!
Aren't you murderers as well?!
You go around killing people with your special abilities!
That's right. Those children will also grow up to become the government's dogs and kill people!
Then isn't it better to use their organs to save people?!
What's wrong with sacrificing a few dogs in order for Chisa to survive?!
I want to save Chisa!
I don't have anyone other than her!
For her sake, I would...
Even if it's for the sake of your daughter,
it doesn't change the fact that you've killed people.
Do you not have a heart?
Burn to ashes.
Get your head straight!
That boy's brother was killed,
and he was suffering so much that he wished for someone else's death.
No matter how much you wanted to save your daughter,
you trampled on others, turning them into sacrifices!
Someone like you...
Someone like you!
Kill them.
Someone like you...
That boy, he was so warm.
His heart was beating steadily.
But... He got colder and colder.
His heart was getting weaker and weaker.
That's how a life vanishes.
You are also warm.
You are warm, just like that boy!
There's no excuse to die when you can live.
There's no excuse for killing somebody!
Daddy?
That's why you can't kill him, Ogami!
He is what he is, but he's alive!
You can't kill him!
That's right... For whatever reason I had,
I was wrong to kill them.
Please take care of my daughter.
So you're here, Fireball Man?!
Devil Man is here to take you on!
I made a lot of people suffer before killing them!
Do you have a problem with that?!
Keep your nose out of it!
Tabata?
Daddy, what are you saying?
Ch-Chisa, forgive me.
Daddy killed people for his own desires.
I ended up being the Devil Man.
Daddy, that's a lie.
This young man, Fireball Man, is here to exterminate me.
Die! Fireball Man!
You can't, Ogami!
Burn to ashes.
Ch-Chisa...
Tabata...
Stupid Fireball Man!
Chisa-chan!
How could you... do that to Daddy?
Even if he's the Devil Man, he's still my Daddy!
I hate you, Fireball Man!
Die! Just die!
Ogami!
Die...
Do you want revenge?
If you do, then get better, and come kill me.
I'll remember you.
I will absolutely not forget about you.
Chisa-chan!
She just fainted.
She probably just tried too hard, even though she's sick.
I'll call for the medics, so don't worry.
I see...
Ogami.
You said things that would make her hate you on purpose, didn't you?
Did you think that would give her a reason to live?
Your methods are questionable but...
Ogami, that's what a hero would do.
You say that you're evil but...
I am evil.
No matter how evil your opponents are,
you're not a hero in any way if you kill them.
Yes, Tabata was killed.
Yeah, I'm fine.
As usual, the research data will...
The research data on the children with special abilities...
I wonder to whom you were gonna pass on the research data,
the secretary.
Code:Breaker!
Looks like the one pulling the
strings is on the other end of the line.
Can you hand the phone to me?
Help me! There's a Code:Breaker...
You played your part well.
No way... You set me up too.
No! I don't want to die!
This is...
Tsuno-kun killed himself.
Was that your doing?
Hey, Toki-kun.
Long time no see.
So it was you, Code 01.
Hitomi.
I'm looking forward to seeing you, Toki-kun.
Bye.
Prime Minister,
the corps have taken care of the children.
They've been moved to research facility 4.
That's good to hear.
Well done.
My word, it was a mistake to put Tabata in charge of the special ability research.
I never thought he would get
involved in such business for his daughter.
I can't understand him.
You should not handle people with special abilities so carelessly.
Does your master also have an interest
in the children with special abilities?
One day, you, too, will know where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city, unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear. The answers lie beyond the darkness
If something is supposed to disappear anyway...
It would have been better if it never existed to begin with.
Next time, Code:Breaker Episode 6: "Lost One."
That is our fate.