I'm...
Why is there no final piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
Father! Mother! I...
I was so worried!
F-Father...
Sakura-kun! It looks like you're feeling better!
It's all thanks to Yuki-chan's nursing.
It's because I would do anything for Sakura-kun.
Mother... What was I...?
Don't you remember?
No.
So you found me at the door.
It was Daisuke-san who found you.
We were so frightened.
You felt so cold.
But it's such a relief that you're well now.
Father, Mother, I'm sorry that I made you worry.
Sorry, it will not happen again.
Sakura-chan, both me and your mom are happy as long as your out of harm.
That's right Sakura-kun, you're the most important thing to us!
Indeed. But I wonder who brought you here...
Don't you have any idea who it might have been?
What is it?
Bring the wicked to justice?
Yes, could you condone such a thing?
Whether for revenge or otherwise,
that is not something I can condone.
That's what I think.
There aren't even any ashes left...
Burn to ashes!
He tried to kill me!
Episode 2「The Spiral Blue Flower, Blossoming in Flame」
But, why did he let me go?
Sakura! Good morning!
Uh? Yeah, good morning Aoba.
Come with me. There's something I want to show you!
Hey, hey. what's wrong?
Are you in a bad mood?
Ogami, what are you planning to do with me?
Come on! Are you listening?
Eh?
No matter how much you're into Ogami-kun,
you can't just ignore that your best friend is talking to you!
Sorry, Aoba. I didn't mean to...
What's the problem?
You want any advice?
It's about Ogami-kun, right?
The truth is last night, at the park...
What are you guys doing, Takatsu-san?
Are you sharing secrets?
Ogami-kun, don't startle us like that!
I'm sorry.
You seemed to be enjoying yourselves so much there.
Won't you let me in on the fun too?
Hmm, so you're interested in Sakura-chan?
Eh, why do you think that?
Why else would you butt into our conversation?
Stop it!
Aoba, don't let him touch you!
Sakura?
Don't let him touch you, or you'll burn!
What's going on? A sudden love triangle?!
Is Sakurakouji-san jealous?
Ogami!
Not only Sakurakouji-san, but now you're aiming for Aoba-chan too!
A world war this early in the morning?
What are you going on about, Sakura?
He just put his hand on my shoulder!
That's not it!
Sakurakouji-san.
What are you talking about?
Please explain it to me too.
Bastard.
Bastard... In order to make sure that I don't talk...
If I say anything to anyone, he'll burn all of us!
Everyone, sit down please.
It's time for class!
Sakurakouji, hurry up and take your seat.
T-Teacher!
What?
Ah... no, it is nothing.
Sakura!
Seriously, don't leave me behind like that!
Oh, Aoba...
This is bad.
If we stick together he'll come after Aoba too.
Hey, Sakura!
I knew it, he's watching me.
If it goes on like this...
Sakura!
Why are you eating out here?
Let's have lunch together!
Aoba...
Aoba! Please get away from me!
Eh, what, Sakura?
Get away from you?
Just listen to me!
Get away!
Hey, aren't you being a bit too mean?
I apologize. That was not my intention.
Well. I understand that you're interested in Ogami-kun.
But why are you avoiding me?
No, that is...
I don't get it!
It's not what you think, Aoba!
Ogami!
What's the matter,
Sakurakouji-san?
Ogami! I have something to say to you in private!
Will you come with me after school?
Sakura never gives up!
It's an after-school date!
Sakurakouji-san, what's so good about that guy?
Sure, I'd be happy to.
Aoba, when this is over, I will tell you everything.
So just wait for me!
Sakura...
Okay, I get it.
Talk to you later then, Sakura.
Meow meow Nyanmaru, everybody's friend.
Kind-hearted, always on little kittens side.
Fading life...
Huh? This is only enough for one more try.
And there're no more Nyanmarus left.
I'll go somewhere else.
Customer! Don't forget to bring these with you!
I don't want them,
I'll leave them with you.
Huh?
I already saved the Nyanmarus.
Putting that aside, if you're gonna burn, what color would you prefer?
Eh? Burn?
I'd prefer blue.
Blue flames are the most beautiful.
You don't have to be so suspicious of me, you know.
So you are aware that you've done things to make me wary of you?
By the way, what did you want to speak with me about?
Meow meow Nyanmaru, everybody's friend.
Kind-hearted, always on little kittens' side. Fading...
Nyanmaru?
Nyanmaru!
Nyanmaru, Nyanmaru!
What?
It's your next job.
Code:Breaker - Code: 03,
Tenpouin Yuuki.
At a place like this, you will not be able to do anything funny,
with this many people around.
Answer me this!
Did you killed the G-Falcon thugs with those blue flames?!
Even if you'd try to deny it...
That's right.
I killed them. But, what about it?
I'm not trying to hide it you know.
Bastard, do you realize what you're saying?!
It's my job.
Also, what's so bad about getting rid of garbage?
Garbage?
Guys like them may exist, but they're of no use to anyone.
Is that why you killed them?
They were murderers themselves.
Even so, why would you kill them?
Are you trying to be some kind of hero of justice or something?
I'm quite evil actually.
More than anyone.
Evil?
If you think that, then turn yourself in to the police and atone for your crime!
Atone?
That's right!
If you turn yourself in, your punishment will become lighter.
The punishment will become lighter?
What's so funny?
Why are you laughing?!
Ogami, do you really understand what you're doing?
You're taking people's lives.
Are you done?
Then I'll be off.
Ogami, do you not...
Do you not have any regrets for what you have done?
Ogami!
Taku-chan, what's wrong?
M-My apologies! It was my fault, I was shouting!
Don't cry, I beg you!
You were looking for this, right?
Thank you!
There, there Taku-chan! What a nice young man that was!
What kind of person are you really?
Ogami, whatever reasons you have,
you have no right to pass judgment on people and kill them.
Wait! Just let the law judge you!
Be judged by the law?
That's impossible.
The law only judges people.
I'm a non-existent being.
The law can't judge me.
Even if I burned you along with all these people to death,
I would never be convicted.
I'll erase all the witnessess.
Burn to ashes, Sakurakouji Sakura.
What are you saying?
In front of all these people, you would burn me?!
Stop it!
Eh?! What?!
Hey, it's on fire!
The bag's burning!
Watch out!
Burn to ashes.
Stop!
Just kidding.
Interesting...
What are you doing?!
I've been observing you all day today, but now there's no question about it.
You are really one of a kind.
What are you talking about?
Yesterday, you killed those people without hesitation.
And today you had me thinking that you were going to kill me, but now you say you were only observing me?
What are you thinking?!
What? The same as you are.
Those G-Falcons killed that homeless man without regrets.
They also hurt other homeless people and even that dog.
You must have thought that their deaths were inevitable.
What nonsense!
Scum like that deserve to die.
And it's my job to exterminate those kind of vermin.
The evil that judges the evil that the law cannot judge.
We who do not exist, we are Code: \Breakers.
"Code:Breaker?"
You have people you'd like to see dead too, right?
Be honest, tell me the names of those people!
Stop...
That is...
Unforgiveable...
There is no excuse for killing!
No matter what kind of person, you cannot just kill them!
You... Why are you trying so hard?
Why?
Ogami!
You can observe me all you want.
But I also will be keeping an eye on you.
I swear by my name, Sakurakouji Sakura,
I will follow you everywhere to make sure that you do not kill anyone else.
You better be prepared!
Why are you laughing?!
I'm cracking up!
You're really amusing!
That's fine with me.
Just remember this:
If you tell anyone about me,
I will kill not only you, but also those you tell and all the people around them.
I will not let you...
Stop!
Whenever, wherever, whoever.
With no exceptions.
I'll burn them beyond ashes.
Do you think something has happened to Sakura-chan?
Why won't she tell us anything?
You can't stop me.
Those eyes...
Those eyes completely devoid of hesitation even while killing.
Ogami, trash?
Exterminate vermin?
Then, what about that time?
Are you saying that you killed Dog with those same cold eyes?
Ogami, what did your eyes look like then?
Is this going to be all right to include someone like Ogami Rei in our plans?
He's not easy to deal with, but once you know how to handle him, his results are top notch.
Besides, I've arranged for a safety net.
It is set up to activate, should we ever lose control of him.
What is it?
It's about Sakurakouji Sakura.
Ah, I decided not to dispose of her.
She's a Chinshu, a "Rare Kind." She's too valuable to kill.
A Rare Kind? Could she really?
There's no doubt about it.
That woman, she won't burn.
Not even by my flames.
One day, you, too, will know where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city, unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear. The answers lie beyond the darkness
Hey, why did you show up out of the blue?
Weren't you supposed to be hiding?
To put an end to this world.
And killing people off is your way of doing it?
And you're looking forward to a future with a part-time job.
You've really grown up.
However, I thought Ogami-kun would be the first one to come and see me.
Wait just a sec No. 1!
Are you planning on passing judgement on me, Yuuki-kun?
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth, and the requiem of fury for the wicked!
Next time, Code:Breaker Episode 03,
"Enraged Bravery and Engraved Paths."
You vermin, I will burn you
until not even a speck of ash remains.