Welcome to the Code: Breaker
Supreme Decision-making Body, "Eden."
You who possess superpowers
of a higher order than humans,
and are granted all power and authority,
with which power,
you are permitted to wipe out evil;
one of the six "Code: Breakers," Code 06...
Ogami Rei.
Despite being the last one
to be appointed a Code: Breaker,
you have carried out your work promptly,
and have developed enough to
hold your own with the other five.
We'll be looking forward to even more out of you.
Enough of the worthless puffery.
State your business.
Watch that tone of voice, you kept dog.
Now, now, don't be like that.
And Ogami, you're out of line, too.
"File downloading"
Tabata Shigeru, politician.
Eliminate this man.
Is this one involved with Hitomi, too?
Finding that out is the job
of a "kept dog," like you, isn't it?
Why, you!
If you're going to get smart with me,
then come speak to me in person,
not through these junk pile puppets!
Also, don't get the wrong impression.
I will decide whether
or not I accept your requests.
I am not your "kept dog."
This is just a job.
Why is there no final
piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence
facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
Here I am, home again,
without knowing how...
"Episode 4: 'War Cry'"
Sakura, we need to have a talk today.
That's right, Sakura. This is not once,
but twice that you were
sleeping out by the front gate.
That shows poor manners.
Indeed, my manners have been poor.
What happened? Go ahead
and tell your Papa and Mama.
Yes, yes.
Th-The truth is...
...I've joined the mountaineering club!
Hence, I've been training myself regularly
to be able to endure sleeping outside!
Oh, is that all it is?!
That's something you'll have to work hard at!
You've got our support, Sakura!
I, Sakura, am off!
Sakura was wearing her "lying face."
I wonder what happened.
Good question. But then,
whenever Sakura lies,
it's always for somebody else's sake.
She also only does
it when she believes it's right.
Let's have faith in Sakura.
Mm-hmm.
I am profoundly sorry,
Father and Mother...
Who's that?
Good morning! You're Sakura, right?
Yes, I am. And you?
I'm Toki. I came to pick
you up in Ogami's place.
Ogami's place?
He botched things last night,
so he can't come today.
He botched things? You mean his job?
Yep. His Code: Breaker job.
Then, Toki, you, too?
The great Toki is Code: Breaker Code 04!
Ogami is Code 06, the lowest one,
so I have to look out for him.
Is that a fact? So, where is Ogami now?
He got chewed out by the higher-ups,
so he's probably on
the verge of tears somewhere.
Him... on the verge of tears?
What? What's going on?
Oh, forgive me. It's nothing.
"Traffic Safety Week"
By the way, Toki, have you
been with Ogami for very long?
Hmm, let's see. We are close friends...
Friends?
Yep. So you can ask me anything about Ogami.
I'll tell you all sorts of things...
That is great!
If you are his friend,
Toki, then you can tell him, too!
I want him to stop what he is doing!
You want him to stop?
Toki, you are a Code: Breaker, too, huh?
Hmm, sounds like there's a story behind this.
Fine. I'd like to hear all about it.
Truthfully?!
Well, we can't do it here, so...
We can talk anywhere;
it doesn't have to be here, does it?
Actually, I have something
to discuss about Ogami, as well.
You do?
It's something that involves you, too, Sakura.
Me, too?
Yep. Something very important.
Hmm? What is the matter, Toki?
Ogami!
What was that for, Ogami?!
Don't listen to this guy's drivel!
How mean, Ogami! And after
not seeing each other in so long, too.
That's right, Ogami!
Aren't you supposed to be friends?
Who says we're friends?
Huh? But...
We are friends, right?
I've sure pounded you
to tears enough, haven't I?
You want to get pounded again, Ogami?
Stop this fighting, both of you!
What do you want, Toki?
That's a fine how-do-you-do.
We have work to discuss.
You heard about tonight, right?
The higher-ups are
worried about you handling it alone.
I ended up closing
the deal yesterday, after all.
That is why the great Toki
wound up having to accompany you.
The reason I'm all the way
out here so early this morning...
...is because I wanted to warn your
lower-rank self not to drag me down.
You should worry more
about yourself than me, right?
Before you find yourself Lost at
a critical time, and drag me down.
You're a real pain in the ass.
I'm sick of looking at you.
Well, if you like, we can
settle things right here, Code 06!
Sounds like fun!
You're gonna be sorry, Toki!
Shut your trap!
I'll kill you!
Stop this, the both of you!
Letting your fists do the
talking is fine, but first, calm down.
S-Sakura... you're hurting us.
Oh, sorry, I didn't mean it.
Ee-yow...
I-It's your own faults...
suddenly going crazy on each other like that.
You're a funny one.
The colors of his eyes...
they're just like Fujiwara's.
What is it, Sakura?
Are you captivated by my good looks?
Do not be conceited, Toki.
I was just looking at the
difference in your eye colors.
Yeah, you're captivated, all right.
See you later, Ogami. Hang in there at work.
Wait, Ogami. Tell me more about Toki.
He's a liar. Please don't believe what he says.
You're being quite hard on him.
Did something happen?
Now that I think about it,
Toki mentioned your work back there.
Don't tell me you mean
to kill more people, do you?
Oh yeah, and what did you mean by "Lost"?
Does it have to do with your power?
Good morning, Sakurakoji Sakura!
There's nothing on a lovely morning
like having a lovely ultra-teatime.
Would you have some with me?
He's having tea again.
Shh, he'll hear you!
Good morning, Heike.
While I appreciate your invitation,
class is about to start,
so I'm afraid I must pass.
I see. Well then, perhaps another time.
This grammar will be on
the next test, so be sure you learn it.
I must grill Ogami for
answers during the break period.
All right, Aoyama,
read the next example sentence...
What's the matter, Sakurakoji?
Teacher! I, Sakurakoji Sakura, am feeling unwell,
so I will go visit the nurse's office.
Eh? Wait, Sakurakoji!
Toki!
Yo, Sakura, what's up?
That is my question to you!
What are you doing here?!
Aw, you're too much.
And here I've come to
have a look at your school.
You're lying. I'll bet you're just
here to rummage around again.
Oh, my, how naughty of you
to sneak out during class, Ogami.
There you both go again.
That uniform is from some other school.
Why aren't you at school?
Teacher!
I'm here today to tour this school.
Oh, is that right? Well, welcome to our school!
I'm telling you, he's lying.
Huh? Ogami, you doubt me?
If you like, you can call
over to my school and ask.
Th-That seal... I-It couldn't be...
That ultra-tough school,
with a T-score of 70, and the nation's
highest rate of placement to Tokyo University,
where the sons and daughters
of captains of industry go...
Heisei Gakuin High School?!
Most elite school in Japan
Yeah, that's right.
"Yeah, that's right" he says, passing it off.
Well, I just chose it because
it was the closest one to my house.
And so, Toki, from Heisei Gakuin High School,
will be sitting in with our class.
Everyone, let's all hit
it off and study hard together.
Right!
Hey, he's kind of handsome.
He gets high marks, coming from Hei-gaku.
Well, if he's going to
study earnestly, then okay.
Lunch! Lunch!
I'm starving!
Ogami, come with me.
Let's talk while eating lunch.
Y-You don't suppose Sakurakoji
made those lunches herself, do you?
- Their relationship is like that already?
- Sakura is on fire!
No.
W-What?
Wait, Ogami!
Toki, you come, too.
Huh?!
Let's eat these lunches together.
No, I've got something I need to do...
Just come with me! We need to talk!
Okay, fine.
What on earth is going on?!
What is this? A love triangle, all of a sudden?
Lousy Ogami! Take off on me, will he?
My apologies, Toki.
You had something to do, but I insisted...
Oh, it's all right.
I just came to see someone's face.
Someone's face?
- So then, Sakura, what did you want to talk about?
- Okay then, later on...
- How handsome!
- Eh? Oh...
It may not make any sense to
discuss this with you, Toki,
but as I touched on this morning,
is there no way that you can stop
Ogami from killing any more people?
It hurts Ogami himself, as well.
I understand not why he goes so far.
Code: Breakers have an objective.
In exchange for carrying out that objective,
we accept jobs that get our hands dirty.
He's probably up to something, as well.
Ogami's objective...
Like, say...
...to protect somebody, or something.
It makes me jealous
that you're interested in Ogami.
Sakura, have you ever been held here?
It is indecent to touch a
woman's breasts, is it not?
Wow, that hurt...
If Sissy could do it, why can't I?
Sissy? Oh, then you are
Fujiwara's brother, all right!
No wonder you look so alike.
What do you know? Ogami wants
to eat Sakura's lunch too, doesn't he?
- Ogami!
- Don't get me wrong.
She's an idiot,
so I'm just keeping watch to
make sure you don't fool her again.
I-Idiot? What do you mean, Idiot?!
Come on, let's get going.
Wait, Ogami!
So, what did you want
to talk about, Miss Sakurakoji?
About you and Code: Breakers.
Special friendship!
Camaraderie that goes beyond the sexes!
I see that you are concerned
about Ogami. My, how considerate.
Oh? What is the matter, Miss Sakurakoji?
Judging by the look on your face,
you do not wish me to be here.
Huh? No! That's not it at all...
Fujiwara!
Hi-tan, Mi-tan, I'm glad you're here!
- I missed you! Hi-tan...
Mi-tan... Hi-tan... Mi-tan...
- N-Nenene...
- I missed you! Hi-tan...
Mi-tan... Hi-tan... Mi-tan...
It doesn't look like we're
going to be able to talk today, huh?
What's the matter, Sakura?
N-Nothing! Nothing at all!
Ah, Ogami, Hi-tan and Mi-tan
are all mine. You can't have them.
What's the use? That's it for today.
Oh, right. Fujiwara, your younger brother is here.
My brother?
Yes, right over... Huh?
Where did he go?
Sakura, what do you mean?
I don't have any brothers.
Code: Breakers, huh?
I told you not to follow me, didn't I?
I'm keeping my eye on you,
to make sure you do not kill again.
What is the story with Toki and Fujiwara?
A Code: Breaker is something
that doesn't exist in this society...
a being unknown to anyone,
and whose existence is utterly erased.
To anyone?
Even supposing Toki did have a family,
as long as he is a Code: Breaker,
it's as though he didn't.
You're kidding.
If Sissy could do it, why can't I?
I just came to see someone's face.
No, I've got something I need to do...
Toki...
Hey there. Sakura, you tagged along?
Toki, is Fujiwara...
Huh? That? It's not true.
What, did you think I was her brother?
You're letting Ogami
make a fool of you again.
It is not untrue.
Toki, Fujiwara is your older sister.
Toki, when you said "to protect somebody,"
you were talking
about Fujiwara, were you not?
You're working as a
Code: Breaker to protect your sister.
I'm a champion of justice!
Huh?!
I'm a Code: Breaker because
I'm a champion of justice!
- Toki!
- For the time being...
...I'd like to be protecting Hi-tan and Mi-tan.
Stop trying to muddle the
situation with that!
Well then...
It's just about time. Shall we get started?
What?
Don't brush me off!
What did you do?
It'd create a racket if
the alarm went off on us, right?
I shut down the security system.
What?!
Next up...
W-W-What is that?!
Toki's special ability. He is able
to freely manipulate magnetism.
Special ability? Magnetism?
Toki's power...
Wait! What are you planning to do here?!
I told you, right?
We're teaching evil a lesson.
Ridiculous! Here in this residential area?
Looks like they're ready to tangle, too.
Of course! They're not going to just sit quietly
after you've destroyed their gate!
Miss Sakurakoji, please leave.
But...
Now then, let's get right to work.
Toki!
Halt! Who are you?!
I'll take care of the targets.
You just stay out of my way.
And don't you go slowing me down.
You dumbass!
What do I do?
You're here, are you, Code: Breakers?
I won't let you interfere.
Fire!
Oh, my, aiming for the head, are we?
You're raring to kill us, huh?
He stopped the bullets?!
Something like that is even possible...
...for Code: Breakers?
Bullets mean nothing
in the face of my special ability.
No, Toki!
You can have them back.
Toki!
What?! They were trying to kill us!
- Yeah, but...
- Now to finish them...
What in the world is this?
A special ability.
Well, well...
We don't need those good-for-nothings, huh?
Surprised? You Code: Breakers
aren't the only ones
who use special abilities.
They have strange powers, too!
This place received government orders
to conduct special ability research.
The government?!
Pretty ridiculous-looking research, huh?!
One day, you, too, will know
where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city,
unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following
wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from
which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear; the answers
lie beyond the darkness
Next time,
"Code: Breaker" episode 5,
"Banquet of Wishes."
This cannot be allowed to stand.
Still, you must not die, Ogami!