By decision of the Eden Supreme Council,
"Hitomi: Age 16"
you are hereby appointed
to be a Code: Breaker.
Thank you very much.
We have great expectations, Code 06.
"Episode 10: 'The World People See'"
An eye for an eye; a tooth for a tooth;
the hammer of judgment for evil.
Code: 06 "Hitomi"
You damn dog!
The newly-appointed Code: Breaker...
...seems to be doing fine work, huh?
Yes. I believe a Code promotion is near.
We've found ourselves a
fine human resource.
Yes.
It's all right now.
Try to catch me!
Hold up, hold up, hold up!
What are you looking at, Hitomi?
I was watching the children.
I want to make the world
so that these children
can always smile like this.
A world where no one has to cry in grief.
For whatever little I can do,
I will help you.
Mm-hmm. Together, as Code: Breakers.
"Hitomi: Age 20"
Target is proceeding west
through the 3rd Street intersection.
Continuing pursuit.
Roger. Standing by at 4th Street.
No! It's a trap!
05! Haruya!
120 a.m.
It's too bad about Haruya.
Hitomi...
With his death, as of today,
you are promoted to Code 05.
You're it! Come get me!
Wait up!
It's to preserve their smiles...
Code 03,
Code: 03 "Hitomi"
You and Code 06
come around from the right.
Acknowledged.
"Hitomi: Age 26"
These foes could
give us a little trouble.
They've got special abilities,
and have revolted against Eden.
We got intel from our undercover operative
that they are planning terrorist activities.
Tonight, we wipe this group out.
Damn! Guys, are you all right?!
The dog barks!
Why, you!
How dare you kill my friends!
I see, so you're the
Code: Breaker Hitomi, are you?
You've got powerful special abilities,
just like we heard.
No wonder all of my men have been done in.
But do you think you can beat me
while carrying that
body over your shoulder?!
They're all...
They're all dead!
Just the fact that you made it
through safely means we're lucky.
One of the enemy did get away from us,
but we still achieved our goal.
The terrorist group has
been effectively eliminated.
There's no point to winning like this.
Not with the toll we've paid.
Indeed, the situation is serious.
Imagine, four Code: Breakers
being defeated in one shot,
leaving only the two of us.
We will have to select
some replacement personnel.
Heike...
...how much does Eden
understand about special abilities?
How do you mean?
Code 06's special ability
went out of control.
She used a water special ability.
But that water attacked her
like it was some kind of monster.
She was not killed by the enemy.
You mean similar to the way that
Code 04 died, which we witnessed?
That's right.
Look into it for me.
I want to know what happened.
As you wish, Ace.
Ace?
As of today, you are
now Code: Breaker Code 01.
In other words, the Ace.
All right, Heike. In that case,
I won't let anyone else die.
Not as long as I'm the Ace.
"Code: 03 Tenpoin Yuki"
"Code: 04 Toki"
"Code: 05 Hachioji Rui"
"Code: 06 Ogami Rei"
Be sure to work hard, everyone.
Why is there no final
piece to unravel this puzzle?
I wander around the search area with dread
With shaky self-confidence
facing unyielding damnation,
I'm still alive, but I can't catch up
to residual images of hidden memories
Let loose dark shame unbounded
to the ends of this world of kindness
Even hopes best forgotten are silenced
as corruption spreads out before our eyes
You're a Code: Breaker?!
Consign it to darkness
An ego on trial
In a moment of hesitation is seen ecstasy
An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth; evil for evil!
Burn away.
Ogami Rei. He possesses an
extraordinary talent, doesn't he?
Yes. He shows a high ability rating,
even among Eden's records.
But he's risky.
Huh?
He's too hung up on eliminating evil.
A trap?
What are you doing, Ogami?
This is why you're still Code 06,
on the bottom rung.
Toki!
Huh? What kind of attitude is that?
And here, the great Toki
has gotten you out of a jam.
It's "Thank you very much,
Toki," right, Ogami?
You mustn't let your guard down, Toki.
My guard wasn't down!
Oh, and Ogami, I thought it was
your mission to rescue this child.
You must not become
so fixated on burning up evil
that you forget more important things.
Okay, let's go home.
Over here, over here!
Wait up!
Ogami, why did you
become a Code: Breaker?
In order to burn up evil.
If, while fighting,
death were about to close in on you,
and you only had a short time
left to live, what would you do?
I would fight to burn away
evil until the very last moment.
You really are something.
I would want to be someone
who would save others
until the very last moment.
Why are you so intent on helping others?
That's just how I am by nature.
Ogami...
Code: Breakers judge evil.
But that's not all we do.
We're also those who protect
those that the law cannot protect.
We who have great power
protect those who are weak.
Our special abilities are
powers given to us for that reason.
That's what I think.
Even if it means losing your life in battle?
If it means being able to
save someone, I'd be content.
Besides...
Even if I lose my life,
as long as you remember me,
I will go on living within you.
That's good enough for me.
What if I die first?
I won't let that happen.
I will protect you.
01?!
You went Lost?
Is this?
Yes. The abilitied person
who once killed our people,
and nearly drove the
Code: Breakers to destruction,
has returned.
Can you fight, Ace?
Of course.
It's time. Let's start the operation.
Acknowledged.
Just don't slow us down, Ogami!
The enemy is in each of the rooms.
We'll attack them all at once, as planned.
You're already in the Dead Zone.
Come on out, lowlife.
You sure indulged yourself, didn't you?
You're the last one I need to hear that from.
You're that dog from before, are you?
I'm going to get
you back for all my friends.
With all the special ability you possess,
you're still the same old
puppet of Eden. You're such a stooge.
Ho, the dogs are out in force.
How about it? Why don't
you all come over to my side?
- Your side?
- Use your special abilities to live freely.
With our powers, we can have
all the money and women we want.
And if you want to take down evil,
you can do it without having
to be a Code: Breaker, right?
You're such a moron.
What?
The whole reason we found a criminal like you
is because we're Code: Breakers.
After all, our boss is the Rising Sun itself.
You dogs...
Ha, it sure does come in useful.
Code: Breakers eliminate evil.
If we were to commit
the excesses that you do,
we would in turn be similarly
eliminated by Code: Breakers.
If you want to use your abilities
however you please, go ahead.
But Code: Breakers will not abide evil.
Enough of your high-sounding lip-service!
Weak! Weak! Who's next?!
I'll send you all to your deaths!
Unfortunately for you,
that won't be possible.
What?!
I won't let you kill any more Code: Breakers.
Shut your mouth!
Wha...?! My body... it's moving on its own!
When I touched you a moment ago,
I sent a command to your brain...
You will be burned by
your own special ability, and die.
May you die as you regret
using your special ability for evil.
Our work is all done.
Is anyone hurt?
Come on, you're the
only one hurt, right, Hitomi?
I'm fine. As long as
you're all okay, this is nothing.
I soaked this in water.
Please use it to cool off.
Yeah, thanks.
Number one, way to go,
taking on such a radical opponent.
I'm the Ace, after all. It's only natural.
Oh, is that how it is?
When I retire, Yuki, you'll have to step up.
That sounds like it'll be tough.
Ogami, you did good work, too.
Ogami!
What? Any other work?
I'll be looking to you again, Ogami.
With this membership,
we'll form the ultimate team.
Nobody is going to die anymore.
Nobody.
Guys, it'll be all right now.
- Over here!
- Wait up, wait up!
What's so funny?
I'm just happy.
Don't you get it, Ogami?
I'm not into riddles,
so please, just come out and say it.
Also, could I ask you to please
stop using that tone
when addressing me, already?
When you are able to surpass me, I'll stop,
Ogami.
What does this mean?
It concerns the runaway special abilities
that you asked me to look into earlier.
The gap between
Losts gradually grows wider,
and being unable to go Lost,
the special ability runs out
of control, resulting in death.
It appears that this sort of event
has happened many times before.
Code: End.
Apparently, that is how Eden refers to it.
Heike, Eden has known about this all along?
Probably.
And Eden has been hiding this from us?!
How can this be?
I've come this far because
I didn't want anyone else to die.
And yet...
Code: End?! Is that the fate of Code: Breakers?!
If this is true, then those poor, poor guys!
Hitomi, what is it?
Why did you call me here?
Do you need something?
When that is finished...
Something about Sky Tower?
When it's finished, I'm sure lots of people,
with their families, and girlfriends,
will come visit it.
Yes, they will.
As long as you've called
me here, I'll hand this over.
Data on tomorrow's job.
Please don't go spacing out.
Code: Breaker work...
Ogami... will you...
What?
...go with me, far away?
It's nothing. Never mind.
He cannot get away from Eden.
If he ran away,
they'd just hound him to death.
All he can do is live as a Code: Breaker.
Not to mention that
telling them about Code: End
would be like delivering a death sentence.
I'll let them live normal lives.
They have no parents, and no siblings,
and all they can do is go to their deaths
without being able to tell
those they love how they feel.
The way things are, it's just too sad.
I have to deal with
the Prime Minister directly.
Thanks for the data, Ogami.
What did you need me for?
Let's give it all
we've got on tomorrow's job.
Right...
I am Code 01, the one they call Ace.
I have to do this, for the
sake of these children, as well.
"Number blocked"
What?
Master! Hitomi has... Hitomi has...
What's wrong?
Last night, he attacked the Prime Minister,
killing the agents who
were escorting him, and fled.
His whereabouts are unknown.
Code 01, Hitomi, tried to
assassinate the Prime Minister.
Luckily, the Prime Minister is unharmed,
but Hitomi's crime is a serious one.
As of today, Hitomi's commission as
a Code: Breaker is rescinded.
From here on, he is on the most wanted list.
He said we would fight together,
but he is breaking that promise.
But to do it like this!
He attacked the Prime Minister. But why?
Didn't he go to talk things over with him?
What happened with you, Hitomi?
Okay, let's begin. We're going
to rebuild this misdirected world.
How ironic, being
bitten by one of my kept dogs.
"Remaining time until Prime
Minister Fujiwara's public execution"
Citizens of the nation,
good evening. As you can see,
in sixty minutes, I will
execute Prime Minister Fujiwara.
At the same time, 50,000 other
people will also end up dying,
as a result of bombs that have
been placed throughout the country.
There is no point in fleeing.
Hitomi!
One day, you, too, will know
where that white crow is heading
We fly through the brilliant city,
unnoticed by all around
Looking only for a reason to live
Ashamed of our hollow selves
Should we just laugh and go along
with the rules the world has decided on?
Stripped bare, following
wherever our instincts lead
to the truth from
which we've averted our eyes
Verdicts handed down for no one's sake
Cast off the dark robes and get on your feet
Pure white wishes become our wings
Shake off your hesitations now, and fly high
Have no fear; the answers
lie beyond the darkness
Calamity unfolds. The people are terrified.
The fated hour is now ticking away.
Next time,
"Code: Breaker" episode 11,
"50,000 Hostages."
The men arrive at the
scene of the showdown.