Operation Chocolate
Sakura-kyun! It's Valentine's Day!
Who are you giving your chocolate to?
I'm so excited!
S-Sakura-chan... don't give chocolate to anyone but your father, okay?
I'm off.
As you can see, it's Valentine's Day.
Is something the matter? You look even scarier than usual.
I have two missions that are of utmost importance today.
My first mission is to ensure this cold-hearted bastard doesn't throw away any love letters he receives again.
Therefore...
...I shall prevent anyone from giving him chocolates!
I didn't know Sakura was the jealous type.
How adorable.
S-Sakurakouji-san...
So you really are in love with Ogami...
Ogami-kun, that's too bad, isn't it?
Not at all. I doubt anyone would give me anything.
It's not like I'm popular.
Ogami, you lucky bastard! How can you say that?!
Everyone knows that you'll soon have a taste of the most decadent of chocolates.
I-I'm so sweet and soft today that I could melt in your mouth.
I'll take you up on that.
Go to hell, Ogami!
Someone gave you chocolate?
Show me! Show me!
Looks like all my hard work's paid off.
These are just from the seniors in my club...
Word.
I'd rather not be taken in by the chocolatiers' marketing scheme...
Shimazu. Stop lying to yourself. Your hands are shaking, you know.
Says the person who only got chocolates from his mother and little sister!
Shut up!
It can't be helped.
Boobies Shaped
Chocolate
Don't take this the wrong way, okay?
We're childhood friends, after all.
A-Aoba.
Boobies shaped chocolate...
Boobies Shaped
Chocolate
Boobies...
If given the choice, I'd much rather indulge in the real thing...
'Sup.
Wow.
Seriously?
What's this?
Ogami-kun, you didn't get any? How sad.
You're not as popular as I thought, eh.
Toki-kun, what are you doing here?
Poor thing.
Would you like me to share some of mine with you?
I received far more chocolates than anyone else, after all.
I'm not a fan of sweets.
Besides, I'm fairly sure Sakurakouji-san received more than you.
Why are guys giving chocolates to her?!
TL Note: Valentine's Day is for girls to give chocolates to guys only in Japan. In turn, the guys would then return the favor on White Day, March 14th.
Lady
Teacher
Hey Ma-kun, it's Valentine's Day today.
Why, thank you, Fujiwara-san.
Don't mind if I do.
It's delicious.
Nee-chan! Get away from that pervert!
Bad boy.
This bad boy can have some of my special homemade chocolate.
It's sure to taste wonderful.
I don't want any!
He must've put something in it.
Something poisonous, you mean?
Ouch...
I messed up again.
Kanda-sensei, are you trying to tempt us or something?
All those who've looked after me...
...and all of my students.
I will make chocolates for them by the end of today!
It's hard to see her making that deadline, isn't it?
Oh, that's right.
Ogami.
Ogami
To Ogami
Here, take this.
It's for you.
Eh?
Sakurakouji-san is giving chocolates to Ogami after all.
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Is this supposed to be your face?
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Indeed.
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
Yuki's Special
Sakura
Chocolate
She gave him homemade chocolate modeled after her own face?!
To Ogami
My, my...
Kill!
Sakurakouji Goutoku
Kill
His feelings for you are inscribed on it.
Sakurakouji Goutoku
Kill
Giving Ogami a scroll to convey one's personal feelings.
That's deep. Too deep!
That chocolate was handmade by my mother.
Don't you dare throw it out.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll eat it late—
That's not good enough.
Eat it now!
Ogami, open your mouth!
Come on!
Wait—
You can't get away now.
Give it up.
Here.
Come on, Ogami.
No need to be shy.
Open up.
Why do you want me to eat this now so badly?
You hate leaving anything behind, right?
What are you doing?!
After everyone did this for you!
I don't like things.
Even though people die, their things remain.
That's why I want to get rid of them in advance.
Aoki Takeshi loves going to the arcade.
Aoyama Yukiyo's hobby is hiking.
Ijyunin Hikari has a thing for blonde girls.
Uesugi Hajime wanted me to teach him English.
I memorized all the things written on them.
It feels like those guys would let me have it if I didn't.
Ogami...
I will never forget them.
Never.
If you ate this here and now, then Valentine's Day would also become an unforgettable memory for you.
This was my other mission!
Good grief. You're always like this.
Now! Hurry up and open your mouth!
Open wide!
I can eat it myself.
So please get off me already.
What's with these two lovebirds?
My, this is delicious.
I made it with the highest quality cocoa.
Whoa!
So you ended up receiving the most chocolates?!
So cute! You can have my chocolate!
Mine too! Mine too!
Operation Marshmallow
Now then, have you decided on what you'll give my parents in return for their Valentine's gifts?
This is what you dragged me out here for?
It's White Day today.
I told you I'd help you figure out what to get them.
Listen up. It's important to find something they like.
Let's order something first.
Oh, yes! The hamburger steak here is amazing.
Of course, the coffee, cake, and spaghetti are as well!
But I don't have enough allowance left for today.
How can you have such a huge appetite?
Order anything you want.
It's my treat.
Really?! I'll take you up on that.
I'll have this and that.
I'll have that and this.
Ah, this one looks great too.
Ogami, feel free to treat us as much as you'd like.
This area is smoke-free.
Toki-kun, where'd you come from?
Ogami, for White Day, you should just dress up as a host or a butler, and serve Yuki-chan.
Madam, how can I be of service?
Your wish is my command.
What a cute little thing you are. What can I do for you?
To serve... a servant, huh.
That's right, Ogami! A servant!
My lord! Milady! Is there anything I can do for you?
Sakurakouji-san... that's an errand boy.
Say, Toki-kun, what did you give in return for your Valentine's gifts?
Me? That's obvious.
Come and let the warmth of my body melt your heart.
Can I get some soup as well?
Sure.
Pay attention!
Oh, Heike-senpai.
Is that for Fujiwara-senpai?
What are you giving her?
It's candy.
That's surprisingly normal.
It's not just any candy.
It's super-sweet, see-through candy!
It's see-through!
Stop it!
What do you plan on doing with my sister?!
You perv—
Bad boy.
My master, shouldn't you be more worried about how you'll repay Sakurakouji-san?
B-But that is the one thing I can't help you with.
Kanda-chan, what naughty act are you performing this time?
The food here is really amazing!
Why don't you order some more?
Are you sure?
This place has so many of my favorites.
I can't decide what to order.
I've been wondering, Ogami.
I'm only here to help you figure out what to do for White Day.
Why are you treating me to all this?
The reason doesn't matter.
You can just sit there and eat whatever you want.
Master!
Could this treat be...
Is that so?
I don't really get it, but thank you.
Ma-kun! Ma-kun!
Look, it's see-through!
This one is strawberry flavored.
This is what you meant by super-sweet, see-through candy?
It's just cotton candy!
Good afternoon!
You have a delivery from Ogami.
Dear Yuki
Oh my!
Dear Goutoku
Chrysanthemums?
What?
Code: 06?
Eh? Me?
But...
I understand.
I'm...
An eye for an eye.
A tooth for a tooth.
A flash of righteous lightning for evil.
My master.
The injured are safe.
Good work, Kanda.
That's the bracelet I gave you back then...
You still have it, eh?
Yes, of course.
When I was crying over the loss of my parents, you tried to console me by giving me this.
The little bird on it is just like you.
When you're feeling lonely, try pressing it.
When you do, I'll be sure to come find you.
Really?
Yes, I promise.
I'm a hero, after all.
It's been a treasure to me ever since.
Kanda...
But...
That bird will keep growing bigger, until it can fly one day!
Really?
That was a lie.
I tried to make things more interesting.
Besides, you still have yet to become a bird, so it's fine.
Eh?!
Hitomi.
Heike.
What is it?
Code: 06 died today at 5:20 AM.
He and his agent were KIA during a mission.
You were in the middle of a mission when it happened.
Code: 06?
He was only 17 years old!
My master.
Heike.
What is it?
Give me as many jobs as possible.
Especially the dangerous ones.
I can't let any more Code:Breakers die in vain like this.
A Code:Breaker's death is of his own doing.
There is no need for you to shoulder this burden, Ace.
That's cold.
Could it be that you're actually worried about me?
Rather than worrying about me, you should be finding a replacement for Code: 06.
Leave it to me.
I, Agent Kanda, will protect the new Code: 06, even if it means risking my life!
Moments ago, we received orders that Kanda will be in charge of the new Code: 06.
I see.
The little bird has finally grown too big for the nest.
Now then...
An electric bird...
Today is the day the little bird leaves the nest.
Looks like there's still something you need to work on.
Hitomi-san, ever since you saved me, I've—
Kanda.
Let me tell you one last thing.
Never harbor feelings for a Code:Breaker.
They'll just end up leaving you.
Eh?
Are you all right—
Oh my. He's just gone Lost.
H-Heike-san, what are you doing?
Oh nothing, I'm just returning the favor.
Have a nice nap.
My one and only hero.
I will make full use of this life you've given me.
I will pass on all of your beliefs, your kindness,
and everything about you, to my new master.
Nyanmaru Theater
Nyan nyan
Nyanmaru!
Previously on Nyanmaru!
Upon finally defeating the formidable Big God, new villains: Time and Lime appeared.
Time     &     Lime
Nyanmaru is no match for the two of them!
What will happen now?
What will you do, Nyanmaru?!
Episode 256
Break Free! The Great
Nyanmaru Punch of Victory!
They're strong, nyan.
We're not like the villains you've faced before.
Basically, we're on a whole different level.
Don't take us lightly.
I won't be able to protect everyone like this, nyan.
What is this light?!
Tengyou-sama!
What? Tengyou-sama?!
Nyanmaru.
It's time to use the Great Nyanmaru Punch.
G-Great Nyanmaru Punch, nyan?
But that's...
G-Great Nyanmaru Punch?
What is this terrifying technique?
You can do it.
Nyanmaru.
I can?
Nod.
Understood, nyan.
What?
For the sake of all the cats in the world,
I will defeat you!
This was the one technique I didn't want to use.
But in order to vanquish evil, I have no choice!
Gulp.
Nyan!
Wh-What is this?
nyan nyan nyanmaru minna no nakama
Nyan nyan, Nyanmaru is everyone's friend!
kokoro yasashii nyanko no mikata
With a kind heart, he is every cat's friend!
kieyuki inochi no hakanasa to
Life is but fleeting and frail!
dareyori kanashimi shiteiru
He understands sadness better than anyone!
itsushika minna omoidasu
Someday, everyone will remember!
zen aku kirisaku
Vanquishing all evil!
inochi no omomi
The preciousness of life!
inochi aru kagiri ikiru no da
Seize the day while we're still alive!
Nyan nyan,
Nyanmaru Punch!
That took forever!
Where the hell did that punch come from?!
Don't just stand there and take it!
Just landing one punch drains all of my stamina...
Well yeah, after all that dancing!
That was quite a punch.
But you still have a ways to go.
What are you saying? You can barely even stand.
You're still standing after taking a Great Nyanmaru Punch?!
I have no choice but to resort to the Super Eccentric Nyanmaru Punch.
How long are you going to dance this time?
I'll let you off for today.
What's with you and all those clichéd catchphrases?
Time to pull out, Lime!
So we're basically just running away, huh?
And so peace has been upheld once again.
But evil always lurks in the shadows.
You can do it, Nyanmaru!
Don't give up, Nyanmaru!
Fight for everyone and every cat!
Nyan nyan Nyanmaru!
Nyanchi!
Nyan nyan
Nyanmaru!
Nyan nyan, Nyanmaru is everyone's friend!
nyan nyan nyanmaru minna no nakama
With a kind heart, he is every cat's friend!
kokoro yasashii nyanko no mikata
Life is but fleeting and frail!
kieyuki inochi no hakanasa to
He understands sadness better than anyone!
dareyori kanashimi shiteiru
Someday, everyone will remember!
itsushika minna omoidasu
Vanquishing all evil!
zen aku kirisaku
The preciousness of life!
inochi no omomi
Seize the day while we're still alive!
inochi aru kagiri ikiru no da
Nyan nyan, Nyanmaru loves life!
nyan nyan nyanmaru inochi no mikata
Nyanchi~
THE END
Don't you have a shorter punch?
I do, nyan! The Nyan nyan, Nyanmaru Punch!
The name is pretty long though.
Want to see it, nyan?
Yes!
Nyan nyan, Nyanmaru Punch!
Here I go!
What kind of amazing punch will it be this time?
Nyan nyan,
Nyanmaru Punch!
So short!
Do you like getting punched or something!?